<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>WAFTI News</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/feeds/all.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://news.wafti.org.uk/</id><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><entry><title>40-Year-Old Beatles Songs Discovered In The Charts</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/entertainment/40-year-old-beatles-songs-discovered-in-the-charts" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:entertainment/40-year-old-beatles-songs-discovered-in-the-charts</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
Music pundits and the listening public alike were feeling fine today as Apple Corp announced the discovery of hundreds of Beatles songs in 
the upper reaches of the Top 40. However, experts have expressed doubts as to their&amp;nbsp;authenticity.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The initial announcement of the discovery was made by James Female, a hardback writer and part-time Conservative councillor from Upminster. &amp;#8216;I&amp;#8217;ve 
been an admirer of The Rolling Beatles for as long as I can remember,&amp;#8217; he told &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt;. &amp;#8216;I happened to be sitting at home browsing the interweb when I 
accidentally typed in the wrong website navigation code and found myself looking at the front screen of something called Amazon. And there I saw 
listed this huge box of rock and roll song-cycles by Ringo and the rest. I couldn&amp;#8217;t believe it, quite frankly, so I quickly pinged off an e-letter to 
Apple Corp and within minutes it was all over the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;RSSSSS&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;feeds.&amp;#8217;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class="sideinfo"&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Things that happened in the&amp;nbsp;60s&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1961: the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;USSR&lt;/span&gt; became the first nation to be transported into&amp;nbsp;space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1963: President Kennedy announces he is to have an&amp;nbsp;affair&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1965: Bob Dylan spots a cow at the Newport Folk&amp;nbsp;Festival&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1969: The 60s are finally outlawed as&amp;nbsp;pointless&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The Beatles were thought to be a band, invented in the early 1960s, although little else is known of their career and work. Folklorists&amp;#8217; writings and 
vagrants&amp;#8217; tales form much of the small amount of information available. Songs generally accepted to have been written by them include the far-sighted 
animal rights anthem &amp;#8216;I Am The Walrus&amp;#8217; and the wedding party favourite &amp;#8216;Hey, Bulldog&amp;#8217;. They are speculated, however, to have produced more than two 
songs; indeed, experts have said that one in every 8 people may have heard one at some point in their&amp;nbsp;lives.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
It is understood that the find, thought to be the first find of its kind, contains most of the Beatles&amp;#8217; back catalogue, but musicologists 
speculate that they may not, in fact, be authentic original recordings. &amp;#8216;My colleagues and I have been studying these records since they were first 
brought to our attention,&amp;#8217; said Dr Adrian Bong, of the London College of Music and a world expert on music. &amp;#8216;The mood at first was electric. We tried 
to act naturally, but, whatever. However, after a more analytical approach ensued, we realised that what we were hearing could not be&amp;nbsp;authentic.&amp;#8217;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Dr Bong theorises that the recordings may have been tampered with by some form of electronic agent, prior to being transferred onto separate media 
and sold on to the public. &amp;#8216;Although we have absolutely no way of knowing this for certain, we feel sure that the waveforms have been digitally 
tweaked, fixing holes, if you will,&amp;#8217; said Dr Bong, &amp;#8216;and hence, what can be heard on these discs is perhaps not identical to what the group originally 
laid onto tape. This, of course, does not affect in any way the sheer apathy of a large cross-section of the music-listening public to this&amp;nbsp;find.&amp;#8217;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
It is not known how long the collection will remain within the top 40, but the Met Office has speculated that a new girl band is showing signs of 
forming somewhere in the Southeast of the country within the next decade or so, which may have a significant impact on the masters&amp;#8217; placing within 
the 
hit&amp;nbsp;parade.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; has not been able to investigate, verify or establish via hear&amp;#8217;say any of the information previously stated in this article, but the board  
of directors of &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt;&amp;#8217;s parent organisation, &lt;span class="caps"&gt;HP&lt;/span&gt; Bulmer Ltd, is adamant that it&amp;#8217;s all&amp;nbsp;true.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>American TV Show Writers Accidentally Write Plot</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/entertainment/american-tv-show-writers-accidentally-write-plot" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>Carl</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:entertainment/american-tv-show-writers-accidentally-write-plot</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
While desperately searching for the next question,
writer Paul O&amp;#8217;Paulsky stumbled upon an answer. This 
weekend viewers of Ambigous Situation will find 
themselves in a slightly reduced state of bewilderment 
after they see the newest&amp;nbsp;episode.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;I guess it had to happen eventually,&amp;#8221; O&amp;#8217;Paulsky said in
a packed press conference. &amp;#8220;We had so many loose ends
flying around that when trying to write a new one, I 
accidentally wrote in some&amp;nbsp;continuity.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Network chief Milkit Ahlot played down the incident.
&amp;#8220;This doesn&amp;#8217;t diminish our ability to string out the 
show much longer than necessary. We will still be able
to bleed its originality dry before we have to cancel.
We aren&amp;#8217;t in danger of doing a &amp;#8216;Battlestar Galactica&amp;#8217; and
plugging the plot holes. Shareholders have nothing to
worry&amp;nbsp;about.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
It remains to be seen whether or not the viewing public
will stand for such shenanigans however. Unwelcome and
unexpected elements of shows, such as referencing past
events, have been known to upset the audience. Ambiguous 
Situation and especially lead characted Captain Standard
will need to get back to their hard-hitting mundanity sooner 
rather than later or their 24th season could be their&amp;nbsp;last.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Anniversary of Moon Landing Reignites Conspiracy Claims</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/science/anniversary-of-moon-landing-reignites-conspiracy-claims" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:science/anniversary-of-moon-landing-reignites-conspiracy-claims</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
Previously waning lunacy was in full view this month as the 40th anniversary of the Apollo 11 mission sparked up fresh controversy over whether or not the moon was&amp;nbsp;faked.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
On July 20th, 1969, the United States landed the first
white, male human beings on the surface of the Earth&amp;#8217;s
moon with an estimated 1 billion eyes witnessing the
historic moment. Despite these 500 million observers,
many conspiracy theorists maintain the accusation that
the entire moon is a hoax concocted by &lt;span class="caps"&gt;NASA&lt;/span&gt;, the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;US&lt;/span&gt;
Government and the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;TUC&lt;/span&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;There is absolutely no way for the moon to be possible,
let alone for a man to walk on it,&amp;#8221; scoffs Geoffrey Van Allen,
founder of Lunar Sceptics, a moon-denying interest&amp;nbsp;group.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;We have analysed 1000s of photographs taken of the moon
and every single one shows signs of tampering. The famous
shot of Buzz Aldrin taken on its surface could easily
have been taken in any Asda car park and touched up in a&amp;nbsp;studio.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Critics of the hoax claims point to the continuing
visibility of our lunar compadre as seen through
several devices such as telescopes, binoculars or&amp;nbsp;eyes.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;Look; it&amp;#8217;s right there,&amp;#8221; a scientist&amp;nbsp;explains.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The &amp;#8220;people&amp;#8221; of the conspiracy theory publication,
&amp;#8220;Moon? Yeah, right&amp;#8230;&amp;#8221; are still not convinced
by this salient&amp;nbsp;evidence.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;We have testimonies from several Hollywood experts
that expose a secret project experimenting with sky
projection technology capable of maintaining something
such as a picture of a moon in our skies perpetually.
We have hard evidence this project dates back years
before the moon itself,&amp;#8221; explains Chief Editor
Roy O&amp;#8217;Rovers in a drawn-out game of&amp;nbsp;charades.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Other attempts to debunk the claims point to evidence
from tidal patterns across the globe &amp;#8212; now known
by most outside of the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;USA&lt;/span&gt; to be due to the
gravitational effect of the moon and not&amp;nbsp;Poseidon.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;It&amp;#8217;s very clear that the wave machines used in
novelty swimming baths today were the side product
of the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;NASA&lt;/span&gt; tide project,&amp;#8221; continued Mr. O&amp;#8217; Rovers
fervently. &amp;#8220;We have detected the main points at
which &lt;span class="caps"&gt;NASA&lt;/span&gt; has stationed wave generators to force
a tidal effect &amp;#8212; all part of an elaborate scheme
to act as if there were a moon pulling on the&amp;nbsp;seas.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Most astronomers were too busy with real work to
respond to these claims, but a group of &lt;span class="caps"&gt;GCSE&lt;/span&gt;
Science students were able to tell &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; they
consider moon hoax proponents to be &amp;#8220;a bunch
of saddos[sic].&amp;#8221; Their parents were unavailable to&amp;nbsp;comment.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Ashes Series In Chaos After Mishap</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/entertainment/ashes-series-in-chaos-after-mishap" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:entertainment/ashes-series-in-chaos-after-mishap</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
The Ashes test series between England and Australia was thrown into 
disarray this afternoon after it was revealed that the urn had been knocked over 
last night and its contents&amp;nbsp;lost.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The news was revealed at a joint press conference given today by the English and Australian team captains and their wives or partners, held in a 
multiplex cemetary near the Oval. Full details have yet to emerge of the dusty incident, but England captain Andrew Strauss attempted to play down 
fears of a&amp;nbsp;bloodbath.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;I can tell you that, at approximately midnight last night, the celebrated Ashes trophy, for which we have for over a century pitted our best 
cricketers against the fine Australian boys, was accidentally dis-uprighted and the filling inside was lost&amp;#8221;, said Strauss. &amp;#8220;Whilst this incident 
will no doubt come as a shock, we can categorically state that the ethic of the team will not be affected, and we will continue to go out onto the 
field and lose for our country, as we have been doing for many&amp;nbsp;years.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Neither Strauss nor Australian captain Ricky Ponting gave any indication 
as to the cause of the mishap, although some details have been leaked to &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; 
from a disenchanted spin bowler. The England team were attending a private party hosted at Longstanton Crematorium by Moira Stuart, having taken the 
urn with them to ward off bad luck. It is alleged that one member of the England party, having consumed a large quantity of alcoholic whiskey, picked 
up the urn to play with it. He then attempted to climb into the urn and paddle it across the local aquaduct, and subsequently got into&amp;nbsp;difficulties.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Shortly afterwards, he was observed capsizing the urn, emptying its contents into the canal. The source then stated that the player returned to the 
party and, with the aid of a caddy, attempted to refill the urn with ashes swept from the crematorium floor. They then replaced the urn. The 
deception was discovered the following morning by the crematorium&amp;#8217;s Urn Curator, who noticed that the urn had been replaced not into its display 
hemisphere, but between the breasts of a dozing Moira Stewart behind the&amp;nbsp;pulpit.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The offending team member&amp;#8217;s behaviour is described as &amp;#8216;not a complete surprise&amp;#8217; by our source, likely intended as a way of letting off steam after a 
very tense start to the series. &amp;#8220;We were under constant pressure through the afternoon&amp;#8221;, said Strauss. &amp;#8220;They tormented us with their swing-off back 
launch propagation until the 7th clause. By the time we&amp;#8217;d levelled the score to 154-53-6.666&lt;57, Collingwood had short-tailed out and under for a 
blimp, and Panesar and Cook just couldn't scrummage the dildo-transfer to a 7-under-4 until collapsing the stork at 23. From the 4th timequarter, we 
picked up a bag of gossamer hits, maintained the left stick and finished with a pair of bereavements to seal the switch-draw. Although of course, 
that is still no excuse for&amp;nbsp;silliness."
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Whilst the offending cricketer&amp;#8217;s name has not yet been made public, his identity will surely be known to the incensed England coach, Andy Flower. &amp;#8220;To 
be honest, when I heard the news, I was bowled over, literally hit for six&amp;#8221;, said Flower, his forehead creased. &amp;#8220;I&amp;#8217;m stumped as to how one of my team 
could get caught out in such a fashion. From what I&amp;#8217;ve heard, he bails on the party, runs out for a duck into the river and gets caught out sinking 
the urn. How&amp;#8217;s that going to look to the supporters? He really hit the boundary last night, I can tell you. He&amp;#8217;s had a good innings, that boy, but 
he&amp;#8217;s in for a sledging now. Severely tests my patience.&amp;#8221; Asked how the incident would affect the team&amp;#8217;s performance in the remaining matches, he 
said, &amp;#8220;Well, there&amp;#8217;s definitely a corridor of uncertainty now, and I don&amp;#8217;t know how the Duckworth-Lewis we are going to be able to perform at our 
peak. All we can do is give it a damn good&amp;nbsp;googly.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The &lt;span class="caps"&gt;MCC&lt;/span&gt; was unavailable for comment today; Lords knows&amp;nbsp;why. 
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Bruce Springsteen Declared Sharia Compliant</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/entertainment/bruce-springsteen-declared-sharia-compliant" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:entertainment/bruce-springsteen-declared-sharia-compliant</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;caption &amp;#8216;These are all mine,&amp;#8217; says&amp;nbsp;judge&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a major blow to shirt-wearing rifle patriots across the lower states, hero Bruce Springsteen was declared compatible with the teachings of the 
Koran by the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UK&lt;/span&gt;&amp;#8217;s foremost Sharia&amp;nbsp;court.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Boss was said to be &amp;#8216;intrigued&amp;#8217; by the fatwa, which will now permit the playing of one of his albums during Islamic bank holidays. His family 
are also said to be alive and well at time of going to &amp;#8216;the Gutenberg&amp;#8217;. &amp;#8216;This is a great big boon to us all,&amp;#8217; said Springsteen,&amp;nbsp;megalomaniacally. 
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The decree was somewhat surprising, in the light of past animosity towards Him by every non-American. This includes Muslims and possibly some 
parakeets. Parakeets were not noted as fans of Himself prior to the 1970s, which was presumably when he released his first records. It is speculated 
that he has released several albums since. Astonishment was also expressed by some Springsteen analysts at the fact that the American midwest 
gave an excreted monkey-toss about what the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UK&lt;/span&gt;&amp;#8217;s opinion might be on something. No explanation has yet been offered by the spokesman for the&amp;nbsp;midwest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The director of the Muslim Religion of Dudley, Dr Wang Ping, confirmed &amp;#8216;Something about this whole thing didn&amp;#8217;t strike us as kosher, which was the 
final straw that clinched the albatross brain-fart.&amp;#8217; He contradicted himself with an official press release via a Printmaster 3000, stating 
&amp;#8216;Islamists will welcome this decision by the Sharia Court of Britain to recognise the wonder and beauty of His&amp;nbsp;creations.&amp;#8217;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whilst the playing of His music will be permitted during public holidays, his fast songs must be confined to daylight hours. This is due to the 
fact that tempos above 130bpm (bodies per minaret) have been shown, via studies, to affect the geological structure of the bedrock in certain 
areas of the oil-rich states, something which America is keen to avoid. &amp;#8216;It is paramount that the middle eastern area is kept as stable as 
possible, and we will do anything within our power to ensure this,&amp;#8217; our American spokesman told&amp;nbsp;us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The news will be a blow to Yusuf Islam, who has actually been striving for this accolade for several years. Other artists known to have been 
shortlisted for potential Sharia compliance include Cliff Richard, the Israeli Breakfast Quartet and the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DJ&lt;/span&gt; Vishnu&amp;nbsp;Experience.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Business Chiefs Announce Merger</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/business/business-chiefs-announce-merger" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:business/business-chiefs-announce-merger</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Excitement was approaching today when the leaders of two of Britain&amp;#8217;s largest companies announced that they were going to meld&amp;nbsp;together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;P&gt;David Axe, &lt;span class="caps"&gt;CEO&lt;/span&gt; of Corporate Leisure Impalements, and Bill String, chairman of Liquid-Based Ethanol Endrinkment Solutions Ltd, spoke today at a 
joint press conference revealing their intentions to fuse their vital organs into a single, malleable&amp;nbsp;individual.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="quo"&gt;&amp;#8216;&lt;/span&gt;Business leaders in this country have been the public&amp;#8217;s whipping boys for many months,&amp;#8217; said Mr Axe, &amp;#8216;and my partner and I have decided to put an 
end to this situation by announcing this merger. The aquisition of the operations arm of Mr String&amp;#8217;s body, by my own, is intended to create a 
streamlined, 
attractive model to better withstand the vibrations of the corporate violin.&amp;#8217; &amp;#8216;Our companies are natural partners,&amp;#8217; agreed Mr String, &amp;#8216;and it is 
essential that we are able to work together to ride out the tough wave of no money effectively. The best way to achieve this is for us to undergo
extensive surgery to create a fantastic dual&amp;nbsp;human.&amp;#8217; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is thought that the procedure would constitute an aggressive takeover bid for Mr String&amp;#8217;s cranial areas and thighs by a consortium of Mr Axe 
and some surgeons, likely backed by a set of complex instruments. The head, or &amp;#8216;nodule&amp;#8217;, of the subject&amp;#8217;s body would then be progressively devalued 
and several slices of the initiator&amp;#8217;s brain data inserted. Given the overlapping business interests of the relevant arms of the two companies, there 
is likely to be some duplication of resources; more specifically, lots of duplication. As a result, reductions in size will need to be made, although 
analysts say that this will largely be achieved by natural wastage, with compulsory loss of staff and body tissue kept to a&amp;nbsp;minimum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This event will mark the first time that such an operation has been attempted, and details of the plan are scant, however the companies in 
question both have vast capital pools. The resultant uber-organisation is therefore likely to pursue a rapid hostile aquisition of the nearest dog 
food processing facility. Publicans have speculated that the cost of the entire procedure could run into billions of something. Commentators 
themselves have given mixed responses to the news. &amp;#8216;I&amp;#8217;m quite mixed about it&amp;#8217;, said John Motson. Murray Walker&amp;#8217;s estate was unable 
to comment with the required amount of enthusiasm, and Tony Gubba&amp;#8217;s response was incorrect. 

&lt;p&gt;It is difficult to describe the kinds of hideous, neurotic wrangling that took place behind the scenes in this deal. Mr Axe&amp;#8217;s company, a 
recreational stabbing specialist, has a very strong market base in the London region. Axe himself is known as one of the corporate world&amp;#8217;s most 
enlightened pianists, and would have beaten down with every shred of his fibre any aggressive bid by String&amp;#8217;s company. String himself is likely
to have been on the ropes for much of the proceedings as it went eventually to the wire. Others say that String fought back cannily, and that 
the deal was hanging by a thread until a cabled bond exchange released Axe&amp;#8217;s head from the block and the pendulum swung&amp;nbsp;back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The outcome of the man-meld is awaited excitedly by the Bank of England, who have a&amp;nbsp;sweepstake.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Darling Budget Scuppers Plans to Run Cars on Cider</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/politics/darling-budget-scuppers-plans-to-run-cars-on-cider" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:politics/darling-budget-scuppers-plans-to-run-cars-on-cider</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
The rising practice of circumventing &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UK&lt;/span&gt; fuel duty by
converting vehicles to run on cider has come under
attack from Chancellor Alistair Darling in his final
Budget before the&amp;nbsp;election.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
An increase of 10% above inflation has been announced
for the duty on ciders this&amp;nbsp;year.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Over the last 12 months, several rural cider makers
have supplemented their incomes by selling off surplus
amounts of their stronger products as an alternative
to&amp;nbsp;petrol.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The Discovery was first made by Matthew Bramley during
a Gala in his home town of Knobbed Russet, Sussex. He
was notably not fond of green apples, but found the Red Delicious,
so would make cider from them. On first tasting of a new
batch, his wife Katy remarked that it tasted like&amp;nbsp;petrol.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The fruitful scheme requires some conversion work
to be carried out on the core of the car&amp;#8217;s engine, but
a cider-powered family car saves its owner an
average of £20bn a year &amp;#8212; up to 50% of the average
household&amp;#8217;s total credit&amp;nbsp;debt.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
However, the latest measures laid out in the Darling
Budget seek to close what the Chancellor refers to
as a &amp;#8220;loophole&amp;#8221; to avoid the tax on&amp;nbsp;petroleum.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;If we allow people to use alternative materials as
fuel, then we will lose millions to fuel duty not paid,&amp;#8221;
&lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; assumes he&amp;nbsp;said.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Those most affected are companies based entirely on
cider-fueled transporation, such as Braeburn Buses
&amp;#8212; a business based in Bedford, bringing biofuel benefits
to Bedfordshire-bound&amp;nbsp;beings.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;It&amp;#8217;s daylight roggery,&amp;#8221; fumes Managing Director,
John Yak, using the letter &amp;#8216;g&amp;#8217; where he has run out of &amp;#8216;b&amp;#8217;s
due to using up all of his in the company slogan. &amp;#8220;I can&amp;#8217;t gelieve
those gastards are trying to gleed more money out of us like this.
I don&amp;#8217;t like this one&amp;nbsp;git.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The public awaits a response from David Cameron on the
report, which many
experts are predicting to be&amp;nbsp;&amp;#8220;untelligible&amp;#8221;.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Economic Crisis Forces Golf Courses to Reduce Number Of Holes</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/business/economic-crisis-forces-golf-courses-to-reduce-number-of-holes" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>Carl</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:business/economic-crisis-forces-golf-courses-to-reduce-number-of-holes</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
Mild reductions of bonuses at large financial companies, caused by stern headlines in the Daily Mail, have curtailed the feel-good fancy free attitudes of bankers everywhere, and it&amp;#8217;s the golf courses who are&amp;nbsp;suffering.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Once, hitting the fairway was enough to avoid the obstacles, 
but old favourites like the water hazard have been joined by a 
swathe of bleary-eyed bankers. Angry old men used to be considered
a staple of the golfing experience. Now, they are finding themselves
upstaged by angry middle-aged&amp;nbsp;men.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Gary Quickwin works at Shortsighted Holdings. &amp;#8220;It&amp;#8217;s hard. We only have 
our salaries to live on, and who can manage on six figures alone? It&amp;#8217;s a disgrace.&amp;#8221; 
He paused to berate his caddy. &amp;#8220;I didn&amp;#8217;t plan ahead and have no savings, and I
also have a huge house. Who&amp;#8217;s going to pay for that I ask&amp;nbsp;you?&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
His colleague, Tony Dontlook-Toohard, nodded in agreement. &amp;#8220;It&amp;#8217;s like, I do
all this work inventing money from nothing, right, and now I&amp;#8217;m not getting
to keep it. Where&amp;#8217;s the&amp;nbsp;justice?&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
They are not the only ones. All across Fritteraway Park,
there are hundreds of disgruntled investment bankers and&amp;nbsp;economists. 
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Who is the worst affected by this crisis however? The golf course owners 
themselves. A spokesman for the International Golfcourse Operators Association 
spoke to &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; News earlier today. &amp;#8220;It&amp;#8217;s terrible,&amp;#8221; he said. &amp;#8220;We can&amp;#8217;t stock
Blue Label in the clubhouse any more, noone buys it. Everyone&amp;#8217;s back on 
Maker&amp;#8217;s Mark. We&amp;#8217;ve had no choice but to reduce the number of holes -
we just can&amp;#8217;t afford to pay someone to rake the cigarette butts out of the
bunkers any&amp;nbsp;more.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Asked whether the players themselves were upset at this, he responded 
&amp;#8220;Not really - they&amp;#8217;re just happier with their lower par. Noone seems
to have noticed that actually there&amp;#8217;s less than they think there&amp;nbsp;is.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Economics teaching under scrutiny in US</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/politics/economics-teaching-under-scrutiny-in-us" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:politics/economics-teaching-under-scrutiny-in-us</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Kansas school board came under significant pressure this week over the content taught in economics lessons in its&amp;nbsp;schools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proponents of the so-called &amp;#8220;Intelligent Market&amp;#8221; theory have claimed that current teaching methods are overly biased towards free market theories by the likes of Adam&amp;nbsp;Smith.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;We respect work of people like Mr. Smith, but it needs to be understood that works like &amp;#8216;The Wealth of Nations&amp;#8217; contain &lt;em&gt;theories&lt;/em&gt; and, as such, should not be taught as if they are the only explanation for our economy,&amp;#8221; &lt;span class="caps"&gt;IM&lt;/span&gt; campaigner tells &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; today. &amp;#8220;We think we owe it to our children to hear both sides of the&amp;nbsp;debate.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For years now, economics lessons have focused entirely on the idea that our economy is driven by &amp;#8220;market forces&amp;#8221;; seemingly random decisions by directors can be beneficial or detrimental to a company, which guides its development. Free market economists say that pressures from the consumer base kill off failing companies and help successful ones to&amp;nbsp;survive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Free market economists call this process of natural selection &amp;#8220;competition&amp;#8221;. The limited resources and finances available nationwide means that every successful company we see today has evolved from ancestor companies that at some point made better decisions than the other ancient companies we longer see today. The only record we have of such extinct companies today is fossilised annual tax returns which researchers have been unearthing at varying layers of the Inland Revenue&amp;nbsp;archives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, supporters of the &amp;#8220;Intelligent Market&amp;#8221; model in the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;USA&lt;/span&gt; cite laws of entropy as evidence that the market could not be as chaotic as it is today through random decisions guided by market&amp;nbsp;forces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;It is clear to us now that such a high level of chaotic mess in our economy could not have happened without some influence from a higher power,&amp;#8221; say a controversial report from top researchers at the California Market Science Institute. &amp;#8220;Such a complex level of disorder could not have been arrived at by subtle forces alone. Our modern day economic state must surely be the result of nearly eight years of tariff imposition, deficit spending and generally bad decisions by a top-level&amp;nbsp;power.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The controversial issue is to be debated at emergency school board meetings across 17 different states&amp;nbsp;tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Environment Minister Admits “I Have No Idea What I’m Doing”</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/politics/environment-minister-admits-i-have-no-idea-what-im-doing" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:politics/environment-minister-admits-i-have-no-idea-what-im-doing</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;At a shiny press conference this morning, Vera O&amp;#8217;Rally-Spectacular, Minister for the Environment, confessed that she had no clue as to how to 
perform her role&amp;nbsp;effectively.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She went on to admit she&amp;#8217;s not even sure how she got the job nor why she&amp;#8217;s been able to stay in it for so long. A stunned and damp audience of 
rampant journalists immediately pounced on her, verbally. She was forced to admit that she was given the job because she had been the only candidate 
who did not get lost on the way to the&amp;nbsp;interview.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="quo"&gt;&amp;#8216;&lt;/span&gt;I was a complete failure at almost everything,&amp;#8217; she observed. Her former headmaster, now her private secretary, agreed. &amp;#8216;Even on the journey here 
today, I tripped over seven times, and lost my housekeys twice. Further, these files in my hand mean nothing to me. They might be important 
government white papers for all I&amp;nbsp;know.&amp;#8217;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This revelation has come about during recent criticism of the government&amp;#8217;s attitude towards environmental issues. Pressure group Stupid Planes 
said &amp;#8216;We have always maintained that this government thinks that the environment is silly. This announcement today only provides further proof that 
they have been really naughty.&amp;#8217; Ms O&amp;#8217;Rally-Spectacular admitted herself that she was not environmentally aware, having thought it was a 
brand of cough medicine. When asked about her hand in the decision to expand Heathrow Airport, the minister simply responded, &amp;#8216;well, all those people 
from the plane companies were awfully nice. I didn&amp;#8217;t want to make them&amp;nbsp;sad.&amp;#8217;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The shadow Environment spokesman, Mr Frogsworth, remained adamant. &amp;#8216;This is merely yet another blunder by this Labour government. I have 
personally seen Ms O&amp;#8217;Rally-Spectacular&amp;#8217;s school exam results, and she completely failed O-Level Latin. I assure you that no Tory minister is 
lacking in such a fundamental qualification. Our Environment minister scored brilliantly on all the Classical languages. He is, unlike most Labour 
ministers, a brilliant academic, having once heard Rachmaninoff&amp;#8217;s piano&amp;nbsp;concertos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Labour has yet to make an official announcement on the issue as Ms O&amp;#8217;Rally-Spectacular has lost the keys to the Government and forgotten the 
password to the&amp;nbsp;computer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ms O&amp;#8217;Rally-Spectacular refuted suggestions that she was a moron, saying &amp;#8216;I have voted Church of England all my&amp;nbsp;life.&amp;#8217;&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Field Geologist Considers Lunch</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/science/field-geologist-considers-lunch" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:science/field-geologist-considers-lunch</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
Experienced geologist Dr Petro Logical, 46, revealed yesterday to his field colleagues that he was thinking about putting down his hammer and having 
some&amp;nbsp;lunch. 
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Dr Logical, based in Wapping, was in Canada at the time of the incident, investigating speciments of Nectocaris in part of the Burgess Shale 
Formation in British Columbia. At approximately 12.30pm, whilst he was separated from the rest of his party and just concluding a detailed study of a 
particularly well-preserved fossil of Nectocaris which he had been working on for several days, he shocked colleagues and co-workers by announcing 
that he was going to down tools and eat some&amp;nbsp;lunch.  
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The news sent longitudinal shock waves through the field party. &amp;#8216;In the 27 years that I have known Petro, he has never, to my knowledge, eaten food,&amp;#8217; 
said a colleague  working in the area, &amp;#8216;before 1pm.&amp;#8217; Others present were similarly amazed. &amp;#8216;I&amp;#8217;ve never heard of anything like this ever happening 
before,&amp;#8217; said another worker, understood to a be one of Dr Logical&amp;#8217;s research students. &amp;#8216;Some people are saying that he simply finished his morning&amp;#8217;s 
work earlier than usual, and decided to have an early lunch, but I just cannot accept&amp;nbsp;that&amp;#8217;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Breakfast at normal&amp;nbsp;time&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
It is understood that, prior to yesterday&amp;#8217;s incident, Dr Logical was a man of regular habit, having got out of bed nearly every day in the last 40 
years. The religiousness of his daily life was corroborated by another of his colleagues, Prof Adolf Hitlerino. &amp;#8216;Right from when I first knew him, 
Petro was never a man,&amp;#8217; said Prof Hitlerino, &amp;#8216;to do things spontaneously. We once worked together in Pompeii in 1978, and I can clearly remember that 
he always ate breakfast just after he got up. He never ate dinner after he had gone to bed, and his showers were always taken before he got to the 
office. He was just that sort of&amp;nbsp;guy.&amp;#8217;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; 
Much of the uproar surrounding the Doctor&amp;#8217;s early lunch stems from his reputation as an extremely dedicated worker. &amp;#8216;He has only two loves: geology 
and his medical experimentation,&amp;#8217; said a former aquaintance, who is unable to be named to due to a mistake. &amp;#8216;I can tell you that he spends all of his 
free time conducting medical tests on his favourite subject, who he married several years ago. If anything, that is his passion, rather than geology. 
It takes up all his time, bombarding her with gamma rays, spiking her with sticks, dosing her up with experimental drugs. He has no time for 
relationships; he&amp;#8217;s married to his&amp;nbsp;wife.&amp;#8217;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Sheer&amp;nbsp;terror&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Many of Dr Logical&amp;#8217;s friends and colleagues are too terrified to speculate as to what time he will take his lunch break tomorrow. &amp;#8216;It&amp;#8217;s just not 
something that I feel I can comprehend at this point in time,&amp;#8217; said Prof Hitlerino. &amp;#8216;The enormity of yesterday&amp;#8217;s events haven&amp;#8217;t quite sunk in yet. We 
are all hoping and praying that he won&amp;#8217;t bring out his lunchbox and thermos before at least five past one tomorrow. But I&amp;#8217;m just not confident. If he 
eats lunch early again, may God have mercy on us&amp;nbsp;all.&amp;#8217;
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Google Announces Web-Based Pie and Mash</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/technology/google-announces-web-based-pie-and-mash" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:technology/google-announces-web-based-pie-and-mash</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
Search engine giant Google has achieved another technological feat by unveiling the world&amp;#8217;s first online pie and mash&amp;nbsp;shop.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The announcement is being seen by analysts as another attempt by the software behemoth to cash in on gaps left open by its rivals, including 
Microsoft and Apple, in the new and emerging market of meat and vegetables. The product was revealed this morning in the canteen at the firm&amp;#8217;s 
headquarters in Mountain View, California, in Google&amp;#8217;s inimitably quirky style, with invited journalists and software executives handed pork pies in 
the shape of pork pie-shaped mounds of mashed&amp;nbsp;potato.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The new venture is intended to exploit the vegetable-loving habits of teenage children, which until now have been ignored by most major greengrocers 
and software corporations. Google&amp;#8217;s Director of Thinking, Jono Pfthan, said &amp;#8216;This announcement comes in response to a growing trend in America of 
people beginning to adore pies and mash. It follows the unveiling of our new operating system, Chrome, developed in response to a strong demand for 
operating systems from people who own PCs.&amp;#8217; &amp;#8216;We always aim to score&amp;#8217;, he added&amp;nbsp;mysteriously.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Google&amp;#8217;s new Cockney-esque website is designed to offer the authentic experience of East End cuisine from the convenience of your own cybercafe. The 
site currently offers around 17,000 varieties of pie, although Google have stated their intention to ramp up the product count going foward. The page 
also offers various varied varieties of vegetable side dishes, including bean sprouts, aubergines, avocados, peas, lentils, garlic bread,
brocolli, squash, samphire, spinach, peppers, mushrooms, kale, chinese cabbage, yams, split peas, zucchini, rutabaga, celery, lima beans, water 
chestnuts, rhubarb, monorail onions, lemongrass, chard, Mexican sour gherkins, winged beans, Malabar gourds, Davidson&amp;#8217;s radish, epicurian shallotts, 
okra and even potatoes. Carrots are also projected to be offered at a later date, subject to logistical&amp;nbsp;considerations. 
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The site is not yet fully developed, and is currently still in beta-carotene, but plans exist to introduce new techniques to channel foodstuffs 
directly to users&amp;#8217; PCs via VoIP (vegetables over &lt;span class="caps"&gt;IP&lt;/span&gt;). Google announced it has developed a test system which allows jellied eels to be hurled across a 
river, but have not released any further details. The company expects demands for its pie and mash products to be high, particularly from areas of 
the world traditionally associated with&amp;nbsp;food. 
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Microsoft have stated that they have no plans to introduce a rival to Google&amp;#8217;s latest offering, stating through a spokesdude that they were 
concentrating on maintaining their fiefdom in other, probably more evil, ways. Apple told &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; that vegetables are the company&amp;#8217;s natural enemy, and 
therefore they were going to run away and hide and invent a talking mattress in response. The Linux empire could not comment as it had gone to the&amp;nbsp;pub.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>“Iced Rain” Baffles Scientists</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/science/iced-rain-baffles-scientists" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:science/iced-rain-baffles-scientists</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
Scientists in the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UK&lt;/span&gt; are still unable to explain the unusual shift in weather experienced throughout much of the country over the last&amp;nbsp;week.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The British Isles has always been home to much
wetness, but its residents were faced over the last seven days
with a rather
unusual difference. Since Monday last week, there
were several reports of a phenomon of white, icy
particles falling from the&amp;nbsp;sky.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;It&amp;#8217;s almost as if the rain froze before falling
to Earth,&amp;#8221; suggests Patrick Thistle, head of Water
Sciences at Nottingham Trent&amp;nbsp;University.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;There&amp;#8217;s no good explanation at this early stage,
but we&amp;#8217;ve been able to collect samples and are
running several tests. We hope to be able to
describe the origin of this phenonenom&amp;nbsp;soon.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Many of the country&amp;#8217;s roads and train lines have
been closed off as Gordon Brown declared a state
of emergency on Thursday. Many commuters complained
of unusual behaviour from their&amp;nbsp;cars.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;This stuff is really bizarre,&amp;#8221; reports Sid Cup from
Letchworth. &amp;#8220;I was doing my usual commute to London
and my car was sliding all over the road. My wife
tried to blame it on the white russians I had with
my cereal, but I know this stuff was involved&amp;nbsp;somehow.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Mary Snowflake, chairperson of the Milton Keynes council
informs she had to shut down the whole mass transit
system. &amp;#8220;We started getting reports of some bizarre,
white substance falling from the sky that was affecting
local drivers&amp;#8217; ability, so we decided to take no
risks. At a time where nobody should be out in their cars,
the most sensible thing to do is to shut down all&amp;nbsp;buses.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;All that is known so far is the substance appears to be
similar to or composed of ice, perhaps alike the ice
content of a&amp;nbsp;snowcone.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Many Milton Keynes residents have alikened the precipitate
to the ground covering inside the local indoor ski slope,
known as the &amp;#8220;&lt;span class="caps"&gt;SNO&lt;/span&gt;!zone&amp;#8221;. However, management
denies any&amp;nbsp;connection.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
What is known is that such a phenomenon has never been observed
in the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UK&lt;/span&gt; before. The Met Office has confirmed that its records
show much cold rain, but never anything comparable
to recent&amp;nbsp;events.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The government has sent a fact-finding group abroad to the
Bahamas to hope to acquire some scientific findings from
our international&amp;nbsp;partners.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>John Lewis Decimates Business Landscape With “2.0” Bombshell</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/business/john-lewis-decimates-business-landscape-with-20-bombshell" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>Carl</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:business/john-lewis-decimates-business-landscape-with-20-bombshell</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
The John Lewis Partnership today announced plans to revolutionise retail by
updating the business model of their 27 department stores across the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UK&lt;/span&gt; to
catch up to the Internet&amp;nbsp;age.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
As of the 31st of August, the stores will distribute their products for free, 
while advertising will be the sole income for the stores. The goods 
themselves will act as loss leaders to entice the consumer to the store. 
Advertisments will be placed on walls, floors and the soon to be erected 
stands decicated to displaying both static and video adverts. Approximately
70% of existing shop floor space will be converted to advert space to 
increase the ratio of income generating floorspace to attraction only&amp;nbsp;floorspace.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The move is stunning, but not without precedent. The burgeoning success of 
&amp;#8220;Web 2.0&amp;#8221; strategies as successfully employed by such trend-setters as Facebook 
and Twitter has caused many business experts to predict its appearance in
the more traditional world of bricks-and-mortar&amp;nbsp;stores. 
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Facebook was valued at approximately $15bn dollars when they raised capital 
by selling stock to Microsoft; Twitter&amp;#8217;s value was said to be $500m when 
Facebook attempted to buy them with an offer of that value of Facebook stock
in a move that many now discredited experts would have described as trading 
clouds only two decades ago. Both have done so by concentrating on finding 
audience for adverts rather than the clearly defunct approach of having a product 
that customers are willing to pay&amp;nbsp;for.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;We have to move with the times,&amp;#8221; said Bertram Yardy, the manager of the 
Newcastle branch. &amp;#8220;These days success isn&amp;#8217;t about profits or sustainability. 
The number of customers you attract defines your worth as a business and we 
want to tap into&amp;nbsp;that.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
What sort of adverts will be displayed? &amp;#8220;The plan is to have a better quality
of advert as well as a greater number. For example, we have one - you&amp;#8217;ll love
this - where you have to try to swat the fly. If you do, you can win prizes! I
think it&amp;#8217;ll really add to the experience of shopping in a John Lewis store
and will certainly augment the product we have in a way that we just couldn&amp;#8217;t
do before with sales staff and tasteful presentation,&amp;#8221; Yardy&amp;nbsp;said.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The partnership aims to have more than tripled the number of customers coming 
into their stores by 2011. While the revenue from advertsing will be unimportantly 
less than that of selling products, Yardy feels that a smaller profit from a larger
number of people is an acheivable goal. &amp;#8220;Free is such an enticing concept, and 
getting something for free will make people want to spend money on the products
we&amp;#8217;re advertsing,&amp;#8221; he&amp;nbsp;explained.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Leading Shampoo Brands now “More Nutritious than Cereal”</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/health/leading-shampoo-brands-now-more-nutritious-than-cereal" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>Carl</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:health/leading-shampoo-brands-now-more-nutritious-than-cereal</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;News has emerged this morning that the nutritional content of shampoo is often higher than that of breakfast&amp;nbsp;cereals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Rising uses of vitamin-rich ingredients such as aubergine in hair cleaning products means taking a shower can now count as one of your&amp;nbsp;five-a-day&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Scurvy and&amp;nbsp;Dandruff&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Captain Cook was reputed to have used Panone, an early forerunner of the vaunted Pantene 
range, to prevent his sailors catching scurvy and to keep their flowing locks shiny 
and free of split ends. His exact recipe is still unknown; however leading shampoo
chefs are confident they have, if not an exact replica, something of equivalent benefit
to both hair and&amp;nbsp;digestion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1821, George Stephenson, inventor of rockets, created similarly tasty head-soap. He
invented a method of growing straight cucumbers, and the experimentation leading up to
his eventual success left him with a veritable gourd plethora. He used this excess to
create the first anti-dandruff shampoo exclusively for&amp;nbsp;babies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Shortage&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Great Everything Shortage of the late 19th century led to a schism in the industry,&amp;nbsp;however.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These days Pantene is very much &amp;#8220;pro-vitamin&amp;#8221;, in stark contrast to Kellog&amp;#8217;s anti-thiamin stance.
With the increased use of other minerals such as iron and pyrite as shampoo ingredients 
Kellog&amp;#8217;s are coming under increased pressure to reconsider their long disparaged&amp;nbsp;position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A spokesperson of the Flouride Advocacy Group was contacted for a statement,&amp;nbsp;however&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kellog&amp;#8217;s were unavailable for&amp;nbsp;comment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Here&amp;#8217;s The Nescience&amp;nbsp;Bit&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gerbins also warned people against interchanging the two products however.
&amp;#8220;We don&amp;#8217;t yet understand the long-term effects of cleaning your hair with
Crunchy Nut Cornflakes,&amp;#8221; he said, &amp;#8220;so we strongly advise against&amp;nbsp;trying&amp;#8221;.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Local authorities remove oxygen from town centres</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/politics/local-authorities-remove-oxygen-from-town-centres" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:politics/local-authorities-remove-oxygen-from-town-centres</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Millions of proud Britons all over England, and some parts of Wales, have not only been disallowed from celebrating Christmas by the government, but are now being told that they are no longer allowed to respire with oxygen - our national gas for&amp;nbsp;centuries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new measures were drawn up by a Labour think-tank in order &amp;#8220;not to cause offence to the other gases now common in our country.&amp;#8221; It was revealed in a report last year that our country&amp;#8217;s air is now less than 30% oxygen. Unfounded reports have already come forward saying that Birmingham City Council has renamed its air &amp;#8220;Diverse Mix of Gases&amp;#8221;, much to the outrage of the newspapers fabricating these&amp;nbsp;reports.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;What I&amp;#8217;ve read in this morning&amp;#8217;s paper is unacceptable,&amp;#8221; says Norman Housemartin, the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;BNP&lt;/span&gt; spokesperson for gases. &amp;#8220;This is an oxygen country and if people don&amp;#8217;t like our gases, they can go back to the country where they came from.&amp;#8221; When asked to cite the cases that enraged him the most, Mr. Housemartin says &amp;#8220;I&amp;#8217;ve not seen any real cases of this name change myself, but anecdotally, I think we have a real issue&amp;nbsp;here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A government spokesman denies any allegations of a proposed &amp;#8220;Anti-oxygenic Task Force&amp;#8221; that will enter citizen&amp;#8217;s homes and ensure they aren&amp;#8217;t respiring any oxygen. &amp;#8220;We just don&amp;#8217;t have that capability,&amp;#8221; admits Roger Flatpack, minister for chemical affairs, &amp;#8220;if it were up to us, we&amp;#8217;d be able to invoke and enforce bans with the efficiency of Oliver Cromwell himself. I don&amp;#8217;t think any of us have achieved that, but certainly everyone in parliament aspires to the level of the greatest Statesman in British&amp;nbsp;history.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;We&amp;#8217;ve seen these reports springing up everywhere that&amp;#8217;s we&amp;#8217;re bringing in bans on our beloved gas, but the truth is we&amp;#8217;re just not competent enough to carry through such plans. We did discuss plans to reduce the amount of oxygen in our public areas to ease tensions from the nitrogen community, but we&amp;#8217;ve found it near impossible to prevent people respiring as they will. In fact Birmingham City Council themselves are respiring as much as&amp;nbsp;anyone.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span class="caps"&gt;BNP&lt;/span&gt; yesterday released an official statement citing these reports as proof that &amp;#8220;The &lt;span class="caps"&gt;PC&lt;/span&gt; brigade have gone mad&amp;#8221; and called for anyone expressing any form of sensitivity to anyone else to be sectioned under the Mental Health&amp;nbsp;Act.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>McDonalds Sues Man</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/business/mcdonalds-sues-man" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:business/mcdonalds-sues-man</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
McDonalds, the most litigious company in the universe, have
sued a Scottish man because his name contains the prefix&amp;nbsp;&amp;#8220;Mc&amp;#8221;.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
A company spokesman said &amp;#8220;He&amp;#8217;s&amp;nbsp;gay.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; would like to point out that McDonald&amp;#8217;s 
spokesmen are in no meaningful way
homophobic, that McDonald&amp;#8217;s is not necessarily the most litigious 
company in the universe, and that whilst the company may sometimes break
&lt;a href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/education/1466398.stm"&gt;child labour 
laws&lt;/a&gt;,
mislead the public over the contents of its
&lt;a href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/1348296.stm"&gt;products&lt;/a&gt; and 
implement a Blairite 45-minute policy on
&lt;a href="http://www.guardian.co.uk/uk_news/story/0,,2225434,00.html"&gt;dining&lt;/a&gt;,
it is, in many ways, of fundamental importance to British&amp;nbsp;society.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
In other news, Conservative leader David Cameron has recently stated that British society is
&amp;#8216;broken&amp;#8217;. This pronouncement marks the first and only time that &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; will ever side itself with
the fawning, preening, amoral, jumped-up, bandwagon-leaping, superlatively misguided, 
may-I-polish-your-curling-irons-Mrs-Thatcher cringeworthy, brain-bloated piece of abject pomposity 
Mr Cameron. 
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; would also like to point out that it is quite possible that a McJobsworth will identify the
above headline and opening paragraph as something warranting a vastly expensive and frivolous
lawsuit, which, given McDonald&amp;#8217;s previous litigation record against smaller business interests,
would be nothing short of sheer moronic pointlessness. However, we will not.

We would like to apologise for any intentional hurt&amp;nbsp;caused.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Minister Criticised for ‘Bashing Bishop’</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/politics/minister-criticised-for-bashing-bishop" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:politics/minister-criticised-for-bashing-bishop</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
Shock and awe spread throughout the House of Commons yesterday as the Minister for Mammals, David Spert, was heard making derogatory remarks about a senior member of the Church of&amp;nbsp;England.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The exact wording is yet to be confirmed by &lt;span class="caps"&gt;HP&lt;/span&gt;
sources, but the minister&amp;#8217;s comments are claimed
to have been derisory towards the hat belonging
to Bishop John&amp;nbsp;Thomas.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Anglican officials are said to be &amp;#8220;deeply offended&amp;#8221;
by the comments which they claim to have asserted
their hats to be &amp;#8220;almost as silly&amp;#8221; as their&amp;nbsp;faith.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;We can all take a joke as much as the next religion,&amp;#8221;
claims Gregory Peck, a church spokesman. &amp;#8220;But, we draw
the line when the seriousness of our commitment
to dress sense is brought into&amp;nbsp;question.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Some have compared the incident to comments made last
year by the Home Secretary over ill-fitting 
Jewish footwear. A full
apology was immediately
demanded by the Jewish Council, which was
then only delivered sarcastically through a string&amp;nbsp;telephone.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The Church of England is yet to make a formal request
for retribution, but preliminary reports suggest they
are likely to be&amp;nbsp;ignored.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;I won&amp;#8217;t be able to keep a straight face if they
ask for an apology wearing those silly hats,&amp;#8221; Mr.
Spert is alleged to have said yesterday evening
after half a bottle of&amp;nbsp;Lambrini.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Monkeys excel at grammar</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/science/monkeys-excel-at-grammar" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:science/monkeys-excel-at-grammar</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
Studies on monkeys have shown their grasp of grammar to outshine that of the average 14-16 year&amp;nbsp;old.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The journal Monkey Tales has today published
research in which cotton-top tamarins were
able to spot incorrect syntax and word usage
far better than the average &lt;span class="caps"&gt;GCSE&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;student.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
They familiarised the monkeys with introductary
reading to the works of Roald Dahl, Charles Dickens
and Jeffrey Archer as well as conversational
classes, then recorded their reaction to
Internet forums, Facebook profiles and a sample
of several Twitter&amp;nbsp;accounts.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
In the experiment, they were shown so-called
&amp;#8220;status updates&amp;#8221; as well as comment posts across
several websites. The aim was to investigate
the ability to spot flagrant misuse of words
as well as incorrect&amp;nbsp;spellings.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The monkeys were trained to indicate what
they deemed an abuse of the English language in mild
cases with a gesture of placing their palm over their
faces; larger mistakes were indicated with head-desk&amp;nbsp;interaction.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The same experiment was repeated with a sample of
British &lt;span class="caps"&gt;GCSE&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;students.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The results indicated that monkeys were 20% more
likely to recognise cases of &amp;#8220;of&amp;#8221; being misused
as a verb, 15% more likely to spot the incorrect
use of homophones such as &amp;#8220;there&amp;#8221; and &amp;#8220;their&amp;#8221; and
a staggering 89% more likely to know when
an apostrophe should and should not be&amp;nbsp;used.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;Simple temporal ordering is shared with non-human animals,&amp;#8221;
the lead researcher tells &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; News while drying his hair.
&amp;#8220;This means we&amp;#8217;d expect basic levels of language skill
to be achievable even to&amp;nbsp;monkeys.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;However, it seems such simple aspects escape the
generation now entering the workplace. It&amp;#8217;s a prospect
that is certainly cause for concern. If their language
skills are in fact lower than those of other primates,
then we could see them losing out on jobs to&amp;nbsp;them.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The government has yet to comment on pressure to
help protect British, human workers from losing
out to more competent immigrants from the same
biological&amp;nbsp;order.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;We need the government to put a stop to these monkey&amp;#8217;s
coming into our country and taking our jobs just
because they are willing to work for peanut&amp;#8217;s,&amp;#8221; rants
a red-faced member of the British Numpty Party on
a group called &amp;#8220;&lt;span class="caps"&gt;BRITTISH&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="caps"&gt;JOB&lt;/span&gt;&amp;#8217;S &lt;span class="caps"&gt;NOW&lt;/span&gt;!!!&amp;#8221; on social
networking site Facebook. &amp;#8220;Saying
their more qualified or more smarter is just &lt;span class="caps"&gt;PC&lt;/span&gt; gone&amp;nbsp;mad.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The European Union is assembling a panel to investigate
the research and its significance in light of recent
calls to expand the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;EU&lt;/span&gt; borders into the animal&amp;nbsp;kingdom.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Police Chief Calls For Abolition Of The Moon</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/science/police-chief-calls-for-abolition-of-the-moon" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:science/police-chief-calls-for-abolition-of-the-moon</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
The Metropolitan Police today called for the Moon to be removed from existence after numerous working problems were experienced by their&amp;nbsp;forces.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Coleman Balls, the Deputy Assistant Commissioner, called on
theorists to reconsider the position and effectiveness of the Moon,
as it was proving a threat to effective policing in the
London&amp;nbsp;area.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Mr Balls explained, &amp;#8216;The Moon is proving particularly
counterproductive to the safe policing of the capital&amp;#8217;s
streets, especially in conjunction with the Theory of
Special Relativity. As it is obvious that this theory
has withstood experimental test and cannot be reworked,
it has to be that the Moon must&amp;nbsp;go.&amp;#8217;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Asked by our correspondent to explain his position,
Commissioner Balls continued &amp;#8216;Einstein&amp;#8217;s theory
postulates that photons of light have momentum,
and that some of this momentum is imparted to an
object when they interact with it. At night, the
Moon pours photons down onto the criminals on the
streets, supplying them with extra momentum and
giving them the ability to outrun our dedicated
team of patrol officers.&amp;#8217; When asked to comment 
on why his officers did not feel the same benefits
of this effect as the criminals, he pointed out that
&amp;#8216;criminals are usually black. I mean, wear black.
Dark substances act as black bodies and absorb more
radiation, and therefore the effect is more pronounced
on these&amp;nbsp;scoundrels.&amp;#8217;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The Commissioner&amp;#8217;s idea would have important ramifications
if it was accepted by scientists. Without the Moon&amp;#8217;s
presence, the tides would fail, destroying sea life,
and the seasons would cease to meaningfully exist, and
the Earth may possibly spiral in towards the Sun,
causing certain death for all&amp;nbsp;Londoners.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The Home Office, when contacted, could not return our
calls. However, Commissioner Balls&amp;#8217; idea is sure to be
discussed at next week&amp;#8217;s Meeting of Scientists in&amp;nbsp;Cheshire.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Police Constable sectioned in Nottingham</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/health/police-constable-sectioned-in-nottingham" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:health/police-constable-sectioned-in-nottingham</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
A member of the Nottingham Constabulary was today admitted to a local psychiatric ward after a series of reports questioning his state of&amp;nbsp;mind.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
It was revealed that Police Constable Frank Bang was confirmed by doctors
to be suffering from paranoia and delusional behaviour. Concerns were
first raised by senior officers as early as November last year when &lt;span class="caps"&gt;PC&lt;/span&gt; Bang
was showing &amp;#8220;significant signs of paranoia&amp;#8221; and &amp;#8220;repeated delusions of&amp;nbsp;conspiracy.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
According to colleagues, Frank increasingly seemed convinced of the
existence of a conspiracy to control his mind and his behaviour. &amp;#8220;He
kept telling us there as some group of people out there intent on
telling him what to say and think,&amp;#8221; said &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WPC&lt;/span&gt; Kelly Boson, a close colleague.
&amp;#8220;We would try and reason with him, but nothing would convince him&amp;nbsp;otherwise.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The paranoia eventually extended to the public side of Frank&amp;#8217;s work.
&amp;#8220;He came into work one day in November this year claiming that there
was some force intent on stealing Christmas,&amp;#8221; explained Sergeant Chris
Cross in an official press release. &amp;#8220;He attempted to start a campaign
to save it from being stolen and he was unswayed in the belief that
there was a brigade set out to stop him doing&amp;nbsp;so.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Calls for &lt;span class="caps"&gt;PC&lt;/span&gt; Bang to be sectioned finally came when his delusional
actions spread into writing letters fueled by his paranoia to the
publications &lt;em&gt;The Sun&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;The Daily Mail&lt;/em&gt;. He tried
to convince readers that &amp;#8220;They&amp;#8217;re trying to ban&amp;nbsp;Christmas.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;This was the final straw,&amp;#8221; said Sergeant Cross. &amp;#8220;This was a clear case
of a &lt;span class="caps"&gt;PC&lt;/span&gt; gone mad. The decision was taken to limit the damage from
Constable Bang&amp;#8217;s paranoia and see that he gets the help he&amp;nbsp;needs.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
It is believed that &lt;span class="caps"&gt;PC&lt;/span&gt; Bang is to be held for thorough diagnosis and
&amp;#8220;whether he is to be held for longer is unclear at this&amp;nbsp;stage.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Prostitutes More Smarter Than Previously Thought</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/science/prostitutes-more-smarter-than-previously-thought" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:science/prostitutes-more-smarter-than-previously-thought</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;A group of some scientists have revealed that prostitutes have a 
sophisticated grasp of mathematics, including the discovery of concepts 
hitherto unknown to mainstream&amp;nbsp;research.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Research carried out by psychoscientists at Brixton University has 
demonstrated that prostitutes only ever congregate on street corners in 
prime numbers. Prior to this, it had long been assumed that prostitutes 
employed basic dynamic processes as an evolutionary consequence of 
dealing with drunken customers. Prof. Abject Poverty of the University&amp;#8217;s 
department said &amp;#8216;Hookers were always thought to have evolved to tout for 
business according to the logistic equation of population growth, and 
were therefore limited by the natural resources that a stretch of 
pavement could provide. However, these results suggest that some new, 
hidden, factors could be determining their&amp;nbsp;distribution&amp;#8217;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prof. Poverty and his colleagues have been able to show that the 
random walk process, when applied to slags, is intrinsically flawed, as 
they are subject to a previously unknown factor termed &amp;#8216;insubordinate 
dependence&amp;#8217;. This effect causes the women to be financially attracted 
towards supplies of narcotics, which distorts the mathematical things of 
the random walk theory. Prof. Poverty&amp;#8217;s team has observed that a 
superposition of prostitutes&amp;#8217; attractors bears similarities to the 
distribution of prime numbers, and may eventually lead to a more 
thorough understanding of non-integer-dimensional surfaces. 
&lt;p&gt;The results have aroused controversy in the scientific community, 
however. Dr Brian Awsh of &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UCL&lt;/span&gt; said &amp;#8216;the whole thrust of their argument 
is likely wrong. Their sample size of 412 prostitutes in the Milton Road 
area of Cambridge is far too small to be representative of the 
neighbourhood as a whole&amp;#8217;, while his colleague Dr James Ypres added 
&amp;#8216;Look at my face.&amp;#8217; However, Laris Hilson, of the Collectors&amp;#8217; Guild of 
Prostitutes, said &amp;#8216;This research may yield some interesting insights for 
the analysts of the sex industry. The idea that prostitutes could 
influence the proof of the Riemann hypothesis is not a new one, but a 
public vindication of their relevance in this field is long&amp;nbsp;overdue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is some way to go before the ladies of the night are able to 
provide any relevant research data. However, the identification of two 
previously unrelated branches of science has many researchers excited. 
&amp;#8216;Who knows what this could lead to?&amp;#8217; asked Prof. Poverty, questioningly. 
&amp;#8216;There is new research being undertaken on infinite series of 
prostitutes that should hopefully be able to provide further insight 
into what, I think, is a very attractive young area.&amp;#8217;&lt;P&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Shadow Minister: Government has “eaten all the pies”</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/politics/shadow-minister-government-has-eaten-all-the-pies" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:politics/shadow-minister-government-has-eaten-all-the-pies</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
Parliament yesterday erupted into chaos after a member of the shadow cabinet accused the current Government of having eaten &amp;#8220;all the&amp;nbsp;pies&amp;#8221;.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Such claims came from the right
honourable David Mouse, &lt;span class="caps"&gt;MP&lt;/span&gt; for Taunton&amp;#8217;s
cider farms, in the light of recent
controversy over the number of pies MPs
have been&amp;nbsp;eating.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Traditionally, every member of the house
would be entitled to a pie every lunch
from the Westminster canteen, but documents
leaked under the Freedom From Information Act
2004 have shown that most MPs are claiming
at least two&amp;nbsp;pies.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;It makes a mockery of the whole system,&amp;#8221; claims
Martin Mocherie, founder of the &amp;#8220;Fewer pies,
fewer lies&amp;#8221; campaign, a frugality and honesty
advocacy&amp;nbsp;group.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;At a time when pie stocks are at their lowest,
these politicians are claiming more pies than
they&amp;nbsp;need.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The system was originally set up in 1968 when
the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UK&lt;/span&gt; elected its first Houses of Parliament
representative from Melton Mowbray. It was voted
that members of parliament travelling to London
from regions where pie consumption was normally
higher could claim more than the one statutory pie
allowance, which benefitted those coming from the
far North and the West Country, as well as
the larger members from the Isle of&amp;nbsp;Wight.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
However, there have been many calls over the last two weeks
for the system to be reviewed due to many
members claiming a second pie they arguably
do not&amp;nbsp;need.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Steven Kidney, &lt;span class="caps"&gt;MP&lt;/span&gt; for Crawley, defends MPs&amp;#8217;
actions, stating that &amp;#8220;many members travel
some considerable distance to reach
parliament and can be very hungry as a&amp;nbsp;result.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;If our politicians are expected both to represent
their local constituency and attend parliament,
they need to be able to claim as many pies as
they&amp;nbsp;need.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Mr. Mouse, who cannot be named in a normal
voice, accuses the current Government of
going &amp;#8220;too far&amp;#8221; and says Britain is in a
&amp;#8220;real danger&amp;#8221; of running out of pies &amp;#8220;very&amp;nbsp;soon&amp;#8221;.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;I fear the current Government is going to go
down in history as the one that ate all the pies,&amp;#8221;
the minister tells &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; through a&amp;nbsp;straw.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
An official response is to be made by the Prime
Minister in the house tomorrow after all the mess
has been cleaned&amp;nbsp;up.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Sir Richard Branson unveils Virgin University</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/education/sir-richard-branson-unveils-virgin-university" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:education/sir-richard-branson-unveils-virgin-university</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;After its worst financial year in over six months, Nottingham Trent could be a target of a takeover bid by Virgin to rescue and rebrand the struggling educational&amp;nbsp;establishment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Sir Richard Branson, the volant Chairman of the Virgin Group, says he has &amp;#8220;tremendous plans&amp;#8221; for the instituion, but isn&amp;#8217;t giving too much away at this&amp;nbsp;stage.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;I&amp;#8217;m sure we&amp;#8217;ll do something with it, &amp;#8221; he forecasts.
&lt;p&gt;
Nottingham Trent will be the seventh didactic institution acquired by the porgonophile and certainly the first worth mentioning. With this acquisition, the Virgin Group will manage two universities, one grammar school, three colleges and one art school under the Virgin Scholar&amp;nbsp;brand.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="sideinfo"&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;History of &amp;#8220;Virgin&amp;nbsp;Scholar&amp;#8221;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In 1996, Sir Richard Branson wins London Art College in a poker tournament. He leaves it largely unchanged, except all &amp;#8220;still life&amp;#8221; arrangements are switched from bowls of fruit to cans of Virgin&amp;nbsp;Cola.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Three years later, Virgin buys Anglia Polytechnic University (now Anglia Ruskin University) and founds the Virgin Scholar&amp;nbsp;brand.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;By 2004, Virgin Scholar has expanded to include Boston Grammar School, Barking College, Plymouth College of Art and Design and Tresham Institute of Further and Higher&amp;nbsp;Education.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From 2005 onwards, all degrees, certificates and exam results included the Virgin logo and £10 free credit on Virgin&amp;nbsp;Mobile.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Company&amp;nbsp;Perks&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Benefits that are brought to a Virgin Scholar institution include discounted rates on Virgin Holidays in the Summer, increased signal strength for Virgin Mobile phones, free Virgin Cola between 2pm and 4pm weekdays, preferencial rates on Virgin Books and free shuttle buses to Virgin&amp;nbsp;Festivals.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Any student radio is assimilated into Virgin Radio, campus eating facilities are incorporated into Virgin Catering and the top five students in any course are given free balloon&amp;nbsp;flights.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Finance&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
However, a proposal to provide student loans to Virgin Scholar customers through Virgin Money raised at least 7 eyebrows at the Student Loans Company Ltd., the usual source of student funding since&amp;nbsp;1990.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;We&amp;#8217;re meant to be doing that,&amp;#8221; sighs long-time director David Firth with an air of 1990 Post-Thatcher&amp;nbsp;ennui.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
New students, however, are warm to the idea of a loan company that will answer the phone. &amp;#8220;Virgin Mobile customers will be allowed straight through without delay,&amp;#8221; promises an optimistic&amp;nbsp;Branson.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Epilogue&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The takeover proposal is due to go before Nottingham Trent Chancellor Sir Michael Parkinson first thing tomorrow morning, after he picks up his dry&amp;nbsp;cleaning.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Sony Music Entertainment achieves UK Christmas #1</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/entertainment/sony-music-entertainment-achieves-uk-christmas-1" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:entertainment/sony-music-entertainment-achieves-uk-christmas-1</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
In a neck and neck dash for the country&amp;#8217;s most pretigious
award, Sony Music Entertainment finally came out on
top with the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UK&lt;/span&gt; best-selling single for Christmas over
close rival: Sony Music&amp;nbsp;Entertainment.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The surprise win was part of a campaign on Facebook
and other social networking sites to get Sony Music
Entertainment to the godly number one spot in protest
at yet another number one from Sony Music&amp;nbsp;Entertainment.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UK&lt;/span&gt; number one selling single was announced at 7pm on Sunday
by the Queen as part of her popular culture round-up of 2009 on
Radio Four. She remarked it as being a historic moment in the entire
Commonwealth and a real testament to the power of the people.
She noted it as dwarfing lesser events such as the
Storming of the Bastille and the miners&amp;#8217; strikes in the&amp;nbsp;1980s.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;Finally, after all the historic, but frankly rubbish, events
of people organising to make a difference to their world, we
have something we can hold up as a shining example of human
achievement. All those involved should pat themselves on the
back, but I suspect they already have, &amp;#8221; rambled her&amp;nbsp;Majesty.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;For the past five years, Sony Music Entertainment has
had that Christmas number one spot with its manufactured
pop music,&amp;#8221; says Richard Porcupine, founder of the group
&amp;#8220;Sod Sony; let&amp;#8217;s get Sony to number one!&amp;#8221; on&amp;nbsp;Facebook.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;It&amp;#8217;s refreshing to get Sony Music Entertainment to number one
instead as a fart in the face of crap music and capitalism. I
am proud to have spear-headed this campaign and I think
everyone who made the effort to download a whole &lt;span class="caps"&gt;MP3&lt;/span&gt; should be proud&amp;nbsp;too.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Fans and supporters of the group are said to be &amp;#8220;mental&amp;#8221; with
delight at the news. One fan tells &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt;: &amp;#8220;I&amp;#8217;m just so well glad
we&amp;#8217;ve made such a difference in our world tonight. I&amp;#8217;m proud
to bring up my children in a world with the majority
of the country agreeing with my personal taste in music. This
must be how the Germans felt when the Berlin Wall&amp;nbsp;fell.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Mr. Porcupine&amp;#8217;s group was the fastest growing group on Facebook,
far outdoing groups such as &amp;#8220;A campaign to end the war in
Afghanistan&amp;#8221;, &amp;#8220;People opposed to the Digital Economy Bill&amp;#8221; and
&amp;#8220;We support curing cancer, saving sick puppies, declaring world
peace and methods to convert human pollution into&amp;nbsp;gold.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;I think people latched onto our cause as the most worthy for backing,&amp;#8221;
drones Dick Porcupine over his Twitter account. &amp;#8220;People saw something
terribly wrong with our world and worked their hardest to
fix it. Until today, people had to endure the hardship of a song
they didn&amp;#8217;t like being the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UK&lt;/span&gt; number one&amp;nbsp;single.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
A press release from Sony Music Entertainment describes
the company as &amp;#8220;chuffed&amp;#8221; that they came out on top
against Sony Music Entertainment. &amp;#8220;The best way to win in
a free market is to get competition between two of your own
products,&amp;#8221; laughed fat cat, Simon Custard over a large
class of Château&amp;nbsp;Latour.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Killjoy tosspots formed an apathy-driven campaign
called &amp;#8220;We don&amp;#8217;t give a flying panda&amp;#8217;s testicle what the
number one is&amp;#8221; on Facebook, but not on Twitter as the title
alone exceeded the character limit for Twitter&amp;nbsp;posts.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Their campaign manager finally got back to our enquiries
last week with the statement: &amp;#8220;we really don&amp;#8217;t care.&amp;#8221; Critics
have called his words &amp;#8220;succinct&amp;#8221; and &amp;#8220;missing the&amp;nbsp;point.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Rumours have indicated that Richard Porcupine may be nominated
for the Nobel Prize for&amp;nbsp;twattery.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Telescope Discovers Earth-Like “Sauna World”</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/health/telescope-discovers-earth-like-sauna-world" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:health/telescope-discovers-earth-like-sauna-world</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;An astronomical telesope in the Canary Islands has discovered the first known health spa on an extra-solar planet, it was reported this&amp;nbsp;week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The announcement is a shot in the arm for beleagured health chiefs, who have emerged as an unexpected casualty of the recent economic&amp;nbsp;downturn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="quo"&gt;&amp;#8216;&lt;/span&gt;As a result of the contraction of the economy in recent months, we have seen a dramatic decline in the number of people being sent to us 
requiring healing&amp;#8217;, said Dr Mehkmi Lesille, of the Kent Primary Care Trust, &amp;#8216;but we have been unable so far to fully capitalise on this. &amp;#8216;We&amp;#8217;ve
closed huge numbers of wards and spend vast amounts of money hiring, training and paying off managers over the last decade in preparation for
this, but we are still falling well short of government targets. What the health corporation in this country really needs now is to offload even 
more patients to lower class facilities, so we can continue our program of utter obliviousness to what Britain&amp;#8217;s ageing population needs. We hope 
that this new discovery may be the&amp;nbsp;key.&amp;#8217;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The discovery of the new health complex was a serendipitous event. Astronomers at the Galileo National Telescope complex in La Palma were scanning 
a sector of the sky known as &amp;#8216;sigma phi beta&amp;#8217;, which is known to contain above-average numbers of rocking-out party planets, but they have discovered
among them a new planet, whose surface is covered entirely by saunas. Its discovery was announced by an international coalition of scientists at a 
press conference in Tenerife, inexplicably hosted by Bob&amp;nbsp;Holness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="quo"&gt;&amp;#8216;&lt;/span&gt;Positive identification was difficult because of noise pollution within the sector,&amp;#8217; said Prof. Harlow Essex, the planet&amp;#8217;s co-discoverer. &amp;#8216;but we 
were able to make use of very recent noise-reducing algorithms and after that it was a piece of&amp;nbsp;piss.&amp;#8217;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The planet is located over 65 light-years from Earth, and scientists are currently investigating the best method of transportation. Due to its 
remote location, traditional space-travel methods like titanium escalators fall just too short of the required range, so researchers are studying the 
idea of simply throwing people there. &amp;#8216;Geoff Capes has already shown an interest in the task,&amp;#8217; said Prof. Essex, &amp;#8216;and we are investigating the 
feasibility of encasing overweight patients in hollow tree trunks to achieve good aerodynamic efficiency.&amp;#8217; Patients would be expected to provide 
their own entertainment for the long journey, likely to last millions of&amp;nbsp;years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for the sauna world itself, early indications suggest that it is likely to match the luxury of the best that Earth has to offer. Analysis has 
shown that the planet has large natural deposits of receptionists, and several thick layers of small, square towels around its equator. Researchers 
also say that they have tentative evidence suggesting the presence of German women, but this has been denied by project leaders. Health workers 
remain generally upbeat about the discovery, however. &amp;#8216;If we can offload all our ill people onto this planet and earn twice as much for the privilege, 
only then will I be happy,&amp;#8217; said Dr&amp;nbsp;Lesille.</summary></entry><entry><title>“Things not what they used to be,” says study</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/science/things-not-what-they-used-to-be-says-study" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:science/things-not-what-they-used-to-be-says-study</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
A study recently commissioned by the British Legion has confirmed that several aspects of modern culture such as fashion, values and mainstream music have changed over the last six&amp;nbsp;decades.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Several claims have been made by aged pressure
groups for a number of years, but this is the
first time a comprehensive paper has been written
up with a notable amount of&amp;nbsp;rigour.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Conclusions drawn by the report include
indications that young
girls wear notably less clothing in public
situations as they did pre-1960 &amp;#8212; an act frequently deemed
unacceptably deplorable by elderly interest&amp;nbsp;organisations.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Other findings included a detailed confirmation that
music isn&amp;#8217;t the same as that being performed
between 1950 and&amp;nbsp;1959.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;They really knew how to sing a proper song back then;
music today is just too loud,&amp;#8221; concludes the first
chapter of the two chapter dossier, which sampled
2,500 music recordings from the last sixty years for
a thorough aural&amp;nbsp;examination.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;The youth of today don&amp;#8217;t know they&amp;#8217;re born,&amp;#8221; opens
the second and final chapter. Later, it reveals,
&amp;#8220;many years ago, one would be able to acquire
goods and services at lower&amp;nbsp;prices.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Perhaps the most surprising revelation to some
was the uncovering of how poor current
television programming is compared to how it has
been in that&amp;nbsp;past.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;Everything these days is all noise, sex and violence,&amp;#8221;
a concerned Patrice Loganberry, 68, tells &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; over
tea and biscuits. &amp;#8220;I spend 8 hours of each day watching
the telly and none of it is worth watching. Except
that Bruce Forsyth; he&amp;#8217;s&amp;nbsp;lovely.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
A parliamenary response to the report is still pending.
James Mandelbrot, the cabinet minister for nostalgia,
was no longer available to comment like he used&amp;nbsp;to.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Tory Party’s Nanny In Fraudulent Claims Kerfuffle</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/politics/tory-partys-nanny-in-fraudulent-claims-kerfuffle" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:politics/tory-partys-nanny-in-fraudulent-claims-kerfuffle</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
The Conservative Party&amp;#8217;s last remaining woman of toil has been forced to defend her conduct after it emerged that she has been 
accused of financial indiscretions regarding her second&amp;nbsp;home.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tiffany Castro, who is employed by all 193 current Tory MPs, is under accusation of gross misconduct by the Committee on Standards in Public Life 
after reportedly claiming a Social Security allowance while living in her second home after the Tory Party exploded her first&amp;nbsp;home.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="quo"&gt;&amp;#8216;&lt;/span&gt;My family have been living in this English country for eighty-seven years, and I have never known what was going on,&amp;#8217; said Castro today. &amp;#8216;I 
therefore took a job with a Tory &lt;span class="caps"&gt;MP&lt;/span&gt;. My duties at first were light bookkeeping and sometimes undertaking cleaning of places in the house, but I 
didn&amp;#8217;t really understand what was going on. Then he made me employable by his boy friend, another Tory &lt;span class="caps"&gt;MP&lt;/span&gt;. I soon was employed by many Tory&amp;nbsp;MPs.&amp;#8217;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
It has emerged this week that, following an unpublicised internal crackdown on MPs&amp;#8217; expenses claims, the Conservatives have been devising some 
inventive ways to save their brass, and despite her nonplussed demeanour, Castro&amp;#8217;s portfolio of clientele has rocketed. &amp;#8216;I recommended Tiffers like a 
shot. I even go as far as to occasionally call her Spiffers,&amp;#8217; said one grandee. &amp;#8216;I may be a racist, but I know a clean pot when I kick one,&amp;#8217; said 
another. At the peak of her client base, Castro was earning fuck&amp;nbsp;all.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
In July this year, however, Castro&amp;#8217;s council house in Balham, the Gateway to the South, was detonated by political mentalist Joshua Cheese-Pussy in a 
failed attempt to disprove the Big Bang theory and the place was reduced to smouldering rubble. She subsequently did not continue to live there any 
more, naturally. She overtook a new house moored on the Thames near Shadwell whilst continuing to generate hand-stitched monogrammed pants and 
produce vintage ports for her employers. Her cousin Lupejo, a 
professional Mexican, said, &amp;#8216;She really did some great things during 
her, as yet 
unterminated,&amp;nbsp;life.&amp;#8217;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Once the Tory party established via solid evidence and considered, empathetic thought that Castro was taking assistance from the state, they set out 
to discredit her by claiming that she was related to the notorious Communist dictator Nicolai Ceaucescu, before giving up and letting the Committee 
take&amp;nbsp;over.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The outcome of the Committee&amp;#8217;s investigation has yet to be announced but they&amp;#8217;re bound to come up with something or&amp;nbsp;other.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Virgin birth prompts review of abstinence-only programmes</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/science/virgin-birth-prompts-review-of-abstinence-only-programmes" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:science/virgin-birth-prompts-review-of-abstinence-only-programmes</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Judean officials have confirmed reports of a pregnant
teenager giving birth today despite new abstinence-only
programmes now entering their second year of&amp;nbsp;running.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sources close to King Herod informed &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; that they
received news this morning that a teenager named Mary has
in fact successfully given birth in the small town of
Bethlehem, Gloucestershire. This birth is controversial
as the Bethlehem district has, for over 18 months now, been
a forerunner in the campaign for teenage abstinence as
a form of birth&amp;nbsp;control.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Judean governmental figures have long cited abstinence
as &amp;#8220;the only form of birth control to be 100% effective&amp;#8221;
and in August 2 B.C., the Herod administration brought in a
Judean-wide campaign to educate teenagers as to its&amp;nbsp;benefits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, protest groups have been claiming since the
programme&amp;#8217;s introduction that it is intrinsically flawed.
&amp;#8220;We&amp;#8217;ve said from the start: this programme is founded on
untruths,&amp;#8221; claims Helen Trout, head of Leave Your Hat On, a
pro-condom pressure group, &amp;#8220;The simple fact is that
if we are to promote real birth control, then we must
be educating our youngsters that they need to be safe whatever
decisions they choose to make. This incident is a kick in
the face to our government&amp;#8217;s ill-advised&amp;nbsp;schemes.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;It&amp;#8217;s a hard issue, certainly and, at a stretch, we could
see teenage sex figures going down, but when it comes down to it
our only shot at stopping this flow is to promote safe
usage of condoms. This incident has brought the issue to a head
and I hope now we see a push in the right&amp;nbsp;direction.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This morning&amp;#8217;s birth has certainly stirred a lot of controversy
and it remains to be seen how the government will move in light
of these revelations. A source close to King Herod informs
&lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt;, &amp;#8220;The King is deeply troubled by the birth of this child.
It is unacceptable that such an anomaly should be allowed to
ruin such a beneficial programme and King Herod has promised
to take whatever action is needed, however&amp;nbsp;drastic.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Virgin Broadband Customer Loads Google</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/technology/virgin-broadband-customer-loads-google" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:technology/virgin-broadband-customer-loads-google</id><summary type="html">&lt;P&gt;An ecstatic customer of a well-known internet service provider 
announced today to a packed press conference that Google had finally&amp;nbsp;loaded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The breakthrough, occuring at 01.30 this morning, could herald a new era for consumers, meaning they may soon be able to occasionally access 
basic websites in the very small hours. &amp;#8216;This could quite literally change my life, and many others&amp;#8217;, the mystery customer was heard to say between the
elbows of photographers. &amp;#8216;I confidently predict that I may now be able to conduct a Google search query by the middle of next&amp;nbsp;year.&amp;#8217;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This incident marks the first time that a consumer of what broadband companies term a &amp;#8216;service&amp;#8217; has been able to achieve a full page load without 
inducing severe foot-based damage to their machine, let alone the downloading of any material. In July 2008, a user in Pitlochrie reported the successful 
downloading of a small string of text, but was widely criticised for concocting the story for publicity&amp;nbsp;reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is understood that the customer, who did not want to be named, and the internet service provider in question, which could not bear to be named, 
have been affiliated which each other for several years. The affiliation has been described by acquaintances of the customer as a 
&amp;#8216;relationship of extreme inconvenience&amp;#8217;. Sources have informed &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; that there has been almost no contact between the two, the company 
seemingly having preferred to maintain a somewhat elusive presence. It is said to have employed various changes of identity in the last 
few years in order to avoid being tracked with swords. However, it is reported that the company has been less than thorough in covering its tracks. 
Observers point to the fact that, upon its last renaming, the company initiated a multi-million pound publicity campaign announcing the 
rebranding. &amp;#8216;If this company existed in compact physical form,&amp;#8217; said the customer, &amp;#8216;then I would throw it into a&amp;nbsp;pond.&amp;#8217;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;P&gt;The specific cause of the unnamed customer&amp;#8217;s dissatisfaction was evident, once identified. &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; has managed to track down a packet of 
the customer&amp;#8217;s internet traffic, after it was remanded for not following the standard internet protocol. The packet was observed acting irrationally at an 
optical-elecrical junction, shortly before it was intercepted by an entity acting for the company who would identify herself only as Janet. The 
suspect packet was evidently frustrated at being detained, and was observed quoting its quantum numbers forcibly several times. 
According to nearby datapackets employed by &lt;span class="caps"&gt;BT&lt;/span&gt;, the packet was initially cooperative, but after being refused a handshake several times was bundled 
violently to the floor and only managed to escape due to an unexpected quantum tunnelling&amp;nbsp;event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; managed to capture covert film footage of the confrontation, which was today described by experts as &amp;#8216;of little help.&amp;#8217; &amp;#8216;Our analysis 
suggests that &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt;&amp;#8217;s actions in viewing the incident resulted in alteration of the measurements recorded by the detecting equipment, which had the 
effect of making the situation appear much worse than it would otherwise have been,&amp;#8217; said an expert. However, other experts disgreed. &amp;#8216;It may be that 
&lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt;&amp;#8217;s timely intervention has prevented a catastrophe,&amp;#8217; claims one. &amp;#8216;Had this packet successfully reached its destination earlier in the 
evening, it could have spawned an influx of literally tens of this &lt;span class="caps"&gt;ISP&lt;/span&gt;&amp;#8217;s customers being able to access the internet, severely overloading the 
company&amp;#8217;s infrastructure and causing the internet to burn&amp;nbsp;down.&amp;#8217;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There has since been no comment or attempt at a pithy one-liner supplied by the company responsible. Sources quoting the president of the company 
referring to customers as &amp;#8216;one hundred percent cuboidal arsepiping&amp;#8217; have since been nearly all proven drunk or were confused by his beard. The story 
has not, in fact, been taken up by the Daily Mail, which has since not twisted the issue into a polemic piece on the state of the housing market 
or given it a Nazi-sympathetic twist. The &lt;span class="caps"&gt;ISP&lt;/span&gt; itself has not been contacted by &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt;, as they were considered too incompetent to respond with a 
statement that was not&amp;nbsp;patronising.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;We apologise for this broadband story being erroneously listed under &amp;#8216;Technology&amp;#8217;. This oversight will be corrected once our new 
section, &amp;#8216;Wagon Wheels: The Internet Of The 18th Century&amp;#8217;, is&amp;nbsp;complete.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Were Vikings the first on the moon?</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/science/were-vikings-the-first-on-the-moon" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:science/were-vikings-the-first-on-the-moon</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
The authenticity of 15th century Viking map clearly depicting the moon five centuries before Neil Armstrong&amp;#8217;s arrival has been confirmed by a great&amp;nbsp;Dane.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The map has been terribly controversial since its discovery
in 1988, at which time it was dismissed as Roman Catholic
tomfoolery intended to discredit Christopher Columbus during
an intellectual property dispute. Lars Supper, grand
commissioner of the Danish Map School, claims that there
is no sign of&amp;nbsp;forgery.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;We have run extensive tests between games of Cluedo
and not once have we seen evidence this was Catholic
monkeyshines,&amp;#8221; Prof. Supper tells &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; via &lt;span class="caps"&gt;SMS&lt;/span&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The map shows Europe, Greenland and a large, round
entity labelled &amp;#8220;Møøn&amp;#8221;. The drawing is poor, but
historians are quick to remind that art teachers
were not invented until the Great Depression in the
1930s. Also, the distance between Greenland
and what we now know today as the Moon,
 is totally inaccurate compared to what we can
determine by modern &lt;span class="caps"&gt;GPS&lt;/span&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The settlement of the area has now been linked to the
Icelandic sagas of Norsemen under Leif &amp;#8220;Sony&amp;#8221; Eriksson
from around 1000 &lt;span class="caps"&gt;CE&lt;/span&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Despite these shortcomings, Prof. Supper maintains the map
is clear evidence the vikings were the first to send
a ship to the moon. However, many killjoy scientists
remain&amp;nbsp;sceptics.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Opponents have alledged that the ink used on the map
contains a substance known as mayonase titanium bromide,
which today is only used in felt-tip pens &amp;#8212; something
not invented until the 16th century. This has now
been disproved in light of recent discoveries
showing that Michaelangelo had used felt tips
on the ceiling of the Sistine&amp;nbsp;Chapel.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;It&amp;#8217;s clearly silly; everybody knows Christopher Columbus
was the first to discover America,&amp;#8221; hints Ronald Watermelon,
leading historian and director of Columbus Tours. &amp;#8220;Anything
to the contrary is just pissing in the&amp;nbsp;wind.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
A British archeologist first discovered the map hanging
from a telegraph pole in Basingstoke, Nottinghamshire in 1957.
It was then traded to the director of the British Museum
in 1965 for a David Beckham &amp;#8220;shiny&amp;#8221; during a lunch&amp;nbsp;break.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
There the map has remained until late 2008, when it was
released for study. Professor Lars Supper will present
his findings during the Coronation Street advert
break next&amp;nbsp;week.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Ordinary Britons feel ‘swamped’ with anti-immigrants</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/politics/ordinary-britons-feel-swamped-with-anti-immigrants" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:politics/ordinary-britons-feel-swamped-with-anti-immigrants</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Large numbers of regular hard-working ordinary families complain that they feel
&amp;#8220;swamped&amp;#8221; and &amp;#8220;overrun&amp;#8221; with anti-immigration policy drives, a study by the
think-tank has&amp;nbsp;shown.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Policy and Legislation Examination Board (&lt;span class="caps"&gt;PLEB&lt;/span&gt;) has revealed in their
research that the majority of hard-working, ordinary, hard-working families feel
that the Britain’s cultural identity is being eroded by an increasing volume of
extreme-right anti-immigration&amp;nbsp;views.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;It’s just getting completely out of hand,&amp;#8221; said Tony Normal, a hard-working
worker from Workington. ‘You go into the town centre, go into Primark, and
everywhere you go there’s just anti-immigrant views. It makes me feel like a
stranger in my own&amp;nbsp;country.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;My daughter was brought up here, she’s being trying to get a job for months but
there’s nothing left,&amp;#8221; said Irene Bog-Standard, from Hull. &amp;#8220;She just wants a
normal job in Conservative policy research like any other girl, but they’ve all
been taken by these anti-immigration types who’ve come in and pushed out the
local people. It’s like an open door, isn’t&amp;nbsp;it?&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A similar picture is being seen in formerly chilled-out and bitchin’ places such
as Surrey in the south of England. &amp;#8220;I used to able to just walk in here for a
marguerita on a Wednesday afternoon and have a good chat about the benefits of
multiculturalism or the best way to make Baba Ganoush&amp;#8221;, says Bill Bowe, standing
outside the Woking Working Mens’ Club. &amp;#8220;But now I can’t even get to the bar.
It’s just full of smelly honkys with pints in their hands banging on about
stockbroking and white power.&amp;#8221; Asked what he thought was the cause of the change
in culture, he responds &amp;#8220;Well, they’re after the benefits aren’t they? They come
here, don’t contribute anything, just spend their time playing golf and living
off the state. And the way they talk, you can’t even understand them can you? I
mean, what the hell is a tax&amp;nbsp;haven?&amp;#8221;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Research undertaken by &lt;span class="caps"&gt;PLEB&lt;/span&gt; does seem to bear out these views. It has recorded a
sharp rise in anti-immigration across Europe, up 16 per cent on last year. The
underlying cause of the spike is unclear, but it is thought to be related to a
rise in grassroots activism in response to a knee-jerk irrational phobia of
brown&amp;nbsp;people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;New activist platforms have sprung up in the last few months, such as the
extreme-right pressure group &lt;span class="caps"&gt;NIMBYBBB&lt;/span&gt;, Not In My Backyard You Black Bastards
(B), formed after Not In My Backyard You Black Bastards (A) was disbanded
following confusion. In Europe, the German organisation Pergoda has recently
seen a surge in support, although when contacted, did not know what its policies&amp;nbsp;are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Professor Dominic Senile, an expert in culture studies at a university, believes
that countering the problem requires long-term commitment to the issue. &amp;#8220;Some
would say that the best solution would be the education of these Nazis and their
normalisation and integration into society. However, we have seen that other
countries have had success with aimless protest, lazy reactionism and complete
and utter ignorance. So before we think about killing, we should try&amp;nbsp;that.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Britain’s worst criminal brought to justice</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/uk/britains-worst-criminal-brought-to-justice" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-01:uk/britains-worst-criminal-brought-to-justice</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Thames Valley Police put yet another feather in its cap after arresting a woman accused of 50 separate crimes shortly after brunch this&amp;nbsp;morning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anne Sheep, from Milton Keynes, was first reported to have been in charge of caring for her child without the appropriate Childcare Licence. Ofsted says looking after children this way without being registered and licenced contravenes the Nanny Act as the care lasted for longer than two hours and constituted receiving &amp;#8220;a&amp;nbsp;reward&amp;#8221;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;A neighbour reported Ms. Sheep saying she found raising her son &amp;#8216;very rewarding&amp;#8217; so this is in clear violation of the measures we put in place to protect children from their mothers,&amp;#8221; an Ofsted inspector wrote on his Myspace&amp;nbsp;blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Civil Liberties campaigners and other whingers were said to be outraged at the incident and have responded in full force by drawing Hitler moustaches on photographs of the Minister for Children, Roger&amp;nbsp;Duck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Livid&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In an interview over Facebook chat, Ms. Sheep told &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt;: &amp;#8220;When the inspector called, the first thing she did was wipe her feet. Then she distracted me with a card trick while another officer handcuffed&amp;nbsp;me.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She was then taken to the police station and only allowed one phone call and to be able to check Facebook for 10 minutes, whilst her child was taken into&amp;nbsp;protection.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Local Man Decides Not To “BIt”</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/business/local-man-decides-not-to-bit" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-01:business/local-man-decides-not-to-bit</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;A North Stratford man has taken a decisive stand against the age-old home refurbishment edict by deciding not to use B&amp;amp;Q as the supplier for his minor home improvement&amp;nbsp;projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The years-old inane advertising slogan encouraged its listeners to repair to their nearest B&amp;Q store and &amp;#8216;do it&amp;#8217; with their selection of &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DIY&lt;/span&gt; ephemera, but Tony Ottoman-Sideboard decided to rise above the innuendo and reject B&amp;Q&amp;#8217;s&amp;nbsp;philosophy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="quo"&gt;&amp;#8216;&lt;/span&gt;It always seemed to me that B&amp;Q and their competitors had been fixing prices on chipboard&amp;#8217;, said Mr Ottoman-Sideboard, a part-time conspiracy theorist, &amp;#8216;and so I decided to renounce the entire industry and only use organic produce in my wardrobing.&amp;#8217; Mr Ottoman-Sideboard was reluctant to say where his organic products were sourced, but his estranged cousin and former business partner, Roger Flatpack, from Cheadle, was happy to speak to &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="quo"&gt;&amp;#8216;&lt;/span&gt;Tony&amp;#8217;s always been a bit of a leftie,&amp;#8217; said Mr Flatpack, now Minister for Chemical Affairs, &amp;#8216;and always stood out in our family. I&amp;#8217;m not one to eulogise on family history, but the great Statesman himself had no problems with mass-produced softwood fixtures.&amp;#8217; Mr Flatpack refused to elaborate&amp;nbsp;further.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The reason for Mr Ottoman-Sideboard&amp;#8217;s actions remain a mystery. B&amp;Q ceased the offending advertising campaign several years ago, and the company has since concentrated its efforts in claiming that they are the cheapest company around for all &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DIY&lt;/span&gt; purchases, whether the claim is true or&amp;nbsp;not.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Met Office Announces Upgrade Of The Weather</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/uk/met-office-announces-upgrade-of-the-weather" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-01:uk/met-office-announces-upgrade-of-the-weather</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Met Office has today announced a multi-million pound program designed to improve the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UK&lt;/span&gt;&amp;#8217;s&amp;nbsp;weather.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In what the Met Office has described as a &amp;#8220;knee-jerk reaction&amp;#8221; to the Arctic weather conditions prevailing across much of middle England 
throughout January, it has secured government funding to begin a series of stepped improvements to the general climate of the country. A total of 
£22m has been earmarked by the Home Office to increase the frequency of warm, sunny conditions and reduce rain showers and snow and&amp;nbsp;wind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is understood that nobody knows anything about the project, but &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; fortunately managed to find a spokesman to tell us something. &amp;#8220;This 
exciting new development opportunity will end the miserable weather we have been seeing across the country recently, and bring some 
much-needed warmth and cheer to a depressed population&amp;#8221;, claimed Tony 
Danza, head weather designer at the Meteorological&amp;nbsp;Office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Danza managed to indicate that a program of bright, sunny periods will be rolled out by mid-May, followed by prolonged warm, sun-bathed days 
and sticky, humid nights envisaged to begin around August. However, current funding is projected to last until the beginning of September, after 
which the future of the initiative remains unclear. Commentators predict a return to chilly, windy conditions by November, and even the possibility 
of recurrent snow-storms going into the new&amp;nbsp;year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Danza believes, though, that the project will not suffer. &amp;#8220;We expect to receive further funding by 
July to continue the project for the next couple of years, once initial results have been analysed,&amp;#8221; said Danza. &amp;#8220;Of course, at this early stage we 
cannot comment on the situation &amp;#8220;4th quarter&amp;#8221;, but confidence among both the investors and government remains&amp;nbsp;high.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What form the project would take, if extended beyond the new year, is still being heavily thought up, but is thought to entail a gradual 
phasing-in of temperature extremes, oscillating chaotically with increasing frequency, until the trees are rent from the very earth and all land-life 
is purged in a dust-bowl of dead, sulphurous brimstone. It is likely that rail disruption could increase during this&amp;nbsp;period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Several other proposals were considered before the current one, known as &amp;#8220;Nero&amp;#8221;, was settled upon. Plans to postpone Autumn by three months were 
vehemently opposed by train companies, fearing that their sophisticated leaf-removing equipment would be unable to cope with being operated in 
slightly colder weather. Another proposal to distribute free whisky to airport baggage-handlers throughout the winter season was rejected as&amp;nbsp;unnecessary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The initiative has been met with a cautious welcome by business leaders and all the other special interest groups that there are. It has, however, 
been strongly opposed by various environmental campaigners, although they werent sure why. &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; contacted one prominent green group for their opinion,
and was met with gales of&amp;nbsp;laughter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;England&amp;#8217;s Bruce Forsyth was generally more upbeat, saying &amp;#8220;This stuff sounds great. It&amp;#8217;d be nice to see them come and speak to me about it, as a 
human being&amp;#8221;. &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; also contacted a Home Office spokesman for a statement, but he was talking too&amp;nbsp;quietly.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>New archæological finds dispute existence of Wales</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/uk/new-archaeological-finds-dispute-existence-of-wales" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-01:uk/new-archaeological-finds-dispute-existence-of-wales</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
A lacklustre archæological excavation conducted near the bantam town
of Ross-on-Wye, Hertfordshire, by local serfs has unearthed significant
evidence to dispute the long-held-until-today claim that Wales&amp;nbsp;exists.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The discoveries include lost documents indicating a conspiracy orchestrated
by the Roman governor of Britain, Publius Ostorius Scapula, in which he
attempts to impress emperor Claudius by inventing military conquests. Historically,
historians have always attributed the first invasion of the area of Wales to Ostorius,
but it now appears his account was purely fabricated because he had run out of real
places to&amp;nbsp;invade.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;The whole basis of the history of Wales stemmed from the Romans first conquering the
area,&amp;#8221; explains Brian Superior, a Welsh historian. &amp;#8220;With the credibility of that
event blown out of the water, there&amp;#8217;s little reason to accept Wales as having existed
at&amp;nbsp;all.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The startling revelations have stirred up controversy in Westminster with MPs
questioning the expense of devolution for a country that doesn&amp;#8217;t exist. Calls have been
made by several backbenchers to cut back on Welsh MPs&amp;#8217; expenses as well. Ieuan Wyn Jones,
the current leader of Plaid Cymru is expected to appear before an inquiry
to explain what the party has actually been doing for the last 44&amp;nbsp;years.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Leeked papers from the Welsh Assembly show that up to 40% of its members may well
have been aware they were legislating for a nonexistent country and were
fully aware it was little more than a Roman clerical&amp;nbsp;error.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
News of the controversy has caused much unrest amongst Welsh citizens, with
public demonstrations being held in Cardiff, Swansea and Newport. Mass walk-outs
have been staged at the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DVLA&lt;/span&gt; in protest at the possibility of removing powers
from the Welsh&amp;nbsp;Assembly.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;These allegations that we don&amp;#8217;t exist are discriminatory and unfair,&amp;#8221; reads the
largest sign we could read from our hotel room. Another placard read: &amp;#8220;The
goverment should tread very&amp;nbsp;Caerphilly.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Virgin trains are &amp;#8220;taking precautions&amp;#8221; and have cancelled all services to Cardiff
for fear they may have been plunging them into the Irish Sea this whole time. Arriva
Trains Wales however insists it is maintaining &amp;#8220;business as usual&amp;#8221; and is also not
running any&amp;nbsp;trains.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The results of the inquiry are expected to be broadcast by the end of the week.
Television bosses are yet to confirm whether they will bother showing it on &lt;span class="caps"&gt;S4C&lt;/span&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Man arrested for killing his mother in Essex</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/uk/man-arrested-for-killing-his-mother-in-essex" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2009-09-07T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2009-09-07:uk/man-arrested-for-killing-his-mother-in-essex</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;An unbalanced man from the village of Tilty, Essex wanted for murdering his own mother in the county last week was picked up by Northumberland authorities today as he was attempting to flee to&amp;nbsp;France.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. Alan Tiledamage &amp;#8212; a Geography teacher at Braintree Upper School &amp;#8212; was a primary suspect after his mother, Sharon Tiledamage, was found dead in her home in Great Dunmow on Friday. He is currently being questioned by the Morpeth&amp;nbsp;constabulary. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. Sharon Tiledamage was found beaten to death by her own loofah in the pagoda in her back garden, just next to the prize-winning gardenias. The gardineas are to have statements taken by officers from Braintree in the next few&amp;nbsp;days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;aside class="sideinfo"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Where did it all go&amp;nbsp;wrong?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
      The name &amp;#8220;Essex&amp;#8221; derives from the Old English &amp;#8220;Ēast Seaxna&amp;#8221; which translates to &amp;#8220;Easy Sex&amp;#8221; and stems from the loose nature of the Saxon women who settled there so they could be close to London for the&amp;nbsp;shops.
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
    This reputation caused an influx of questionable characters from both the Saxons and the Angles&amp;nbsp;nearby.
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
      Due to lack of the numeracy required to read train timetables, few families have moved from the area leading to a small gene pool based on these medieval troublemakers and&amp;nbsp;slags.
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
    Essex County Council was formed in 1889, but by then it was too late and all hope was&amp;nbsp;lost.
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
    The boundary with Greater London was established in 1965 so that Londoners could disassociate themselves with their Essex&amp;nbsp;neighbours.
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/aside&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Morpeth police are yet to release a statement, except this&amp;nbsp;one:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;We can confirm that Mr. Tiledamage is being held in custody over the death of his mother in Essex. We are taking this matter very seriously as it&amp;#8217;s a dying shame for anyone to spend their final days in Essex,&amp;#8221; Sergeant Pepper reads from an edible press release at a press conference held during breaks in the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;US&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;Open.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Harsher penalties were brought in for murder in the county back in November 2008 after the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;EU&lt;/span&gt; Court of Human Rights declared it an &amp;#8220;affront to human dignity for anyone&amp;#8217;s last memories of life on Earth to be of Essex.&amp;#8221; Several petitions were circulated in Chelmsford to fight the legistlation, but few could write their own name on the&amp;nbsp;sheet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;It&amp;#8217;s well crap,&amp;#8221; Councillor Jodie Marsh, Conservative chair of the Essex Country Council, tells &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; during a glamour photoshoot. Defiant over the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;EU&lt;/span&gt; ruling, she adds, &amp;#8220;I never fort[sic] someone would kill their mum, but Essex is well nice and definitely the best place to do&amp;nbsp;it.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; sent several correspondents to Essex to get reactions from family and friends, but only one returned alive. We all wish him a speedy recovery from his injuries to report his findings in due&amp;nbsp;course.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Government looks to glasses ban to curb violence</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/uk/government-looks-to-glasses-ban-to-curb-violence" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2009-08-31T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2009-08-31:uk/government-looks-to-glasses-ban-to-curb-violence</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Despite protests from those not so keen on the idea, the Government squeezed out an early day movement this morning that looks to ban glasses in pubs by&amp;nbsp;2011.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Home Office insists the idea is &amp;#8220;fine&amp;#8221; and that they &amp;#8220;really know what they&amp;#8217;re doing&amp;nbsp;here.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year in England and Wales, 99% of attacks that took place in or outside public houses were committed by people who could see. The Home Secretary hopes that preventing visually impaired individuals from accessing corrective glasses will reduce this percentage&amp;nbsp;signficantly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The British Beer Drinking association were indignant, claiming such a measure would impact on their drinking as well as their ability to find the pub at&amp;nbsp;all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Not&amp;nbsp;impressed&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;For the bevvy aficionado, finding the pub is a top priority,&amp;#8221; chorused the regulars at the King&amp;#8217;s Prawns, Cheddington during a &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; school trip. &amp;#8220;I have no idea how I can even begin to get blind drunk without my glasses,&amp;#8221; added the&amp;nbsp;baritone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An unelected spokestenor went on to explain that they would most certainly not welcome any attempt to take away their glasses, threatening to create a spectacle if they were to attempt to do&amp;nbsp;so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;Why should we be punished when we&amp;#8217;re not causing any trouble at all? Us myopics cause the least amount of trouble around here &amp;#8212; whoever heard of someone with glasses getting into a fight? It&amp;#8217;s those 20-20 bastards you need to watch&amp;nbsp;closely.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Economic&amp;nbsp;pressures&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Prawns landlord &amp;#8212; a wonderful countertenor &amp;#8212; says he fears increased financial pressures would result from the proposed&amp;nbsp;legislation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;Half of those twats that come in &amp;#8216;ere are blind as bats without their specs,&amp;#8221; sings he, with an irreverent, yet melodic feel. &amp;#8220;There&amp;#8217;s bound to be extra spillages and breakages if they&amp;#8217;re prone to knocking over their drinking&amp;nbsp;vessels.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;This proposal is incredibly short-sighted and I don&amp;#8217;t think the Government is looking at the big picture. Our politicians really lack vision on these matters and I don&amp;#8217;t see how they think this will work. We&amp;#8217;ve had enough of them blindly throwing legislation about like&amp;nbsp;this.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Yeah,&amp;nbsp;whatever&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ministers behind the proposal were dismissive of all negative claims and are looking forward to seeing this measure&amp;nbsp;through.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;People forget there was a time when nobody wore glasses,&amp;#8221; explains Gavin Fairweather &lt;span class="caps"&gt;MP&lt;/span&gt;. &amp;#8220;We all had to adjust from not having glasses to having them, so in time we feel people will accept this paradigm shift. Besides, they can wear contact&amp;nbsp;lenses.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pub-goers are said to be &amp;#8220;furious&amp;#8221; at the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;MP&lt;/span&gt;&amp;#8217;s remarks. &amp;#8220;Contact lenses, my eye!&amp;#8221; exclaims the tallest&amp;nbsp;one.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>East London DIY Shop Reported As Difficult To Locate</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/uk/east-london-diy-shop-reported-as-difficult-to-locate" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2009-08-17T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2009-08-17:uk/east-london-diy-shop-reported-as-difficult-to-locate</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
The blackened, sooty streets of Shadwell&lt;br&gt;
Glowed in ochre, dingy dark&lt;br&gt;
and twisted, inky shades were formed&lt;br&gt;
with Lucifer&amp;#8217;s heretic mark&amp;#8230;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Inert and silent stillness rested,&lt;br&gt;
Draped across the dampened ground&lt;br&gt;
And flitting, dancing figures flew&lt;br&gt;
Above me, all without a sound.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
A distant light came intermittent&lt;br&gt;
Struggling through the misty rain&lt;br&gt;
A traveller, a hardy fool&lt;br&gt;
Who&amp;#8217;d ventured far from his domain.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Approaching ever louder, brighter&lt;br&gt;
Bearing down with startling force&lt;br&gt;
And suddenly they fade away.&lt;br&gt;
I turn and leave the beaten course;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Amongst the dripping filth and moistness&lt;br&gt;
Hid by arches in the gloom &lt;br&gt;
I met a man whose life was done&lt;br&gt;
To listen to his tale of doom.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="quo"&gt;&amp;#8216;&lt;/span&gt;You&amp;#8217;re late!&amp;#8217; he spat. &amp;#8216;The midnight&amp;#8217;s past.&lt;br&gt;
Now, listen to my tale of doom.&lt;br&gt;
Your Auntie Enid&amp;#8217;s on to me&lt;br&gt;
&amp;#8216;bout doing up the old spare room.&amp;#8217;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
I seek a place, quite near to here;&lt;br&gt;
a vending place, for paint and paste.&lt;br&gt;
For &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DIY&lt;/span&gt;, in other words,&lt;br&gt;
Where I may rush with hen-pecked haste.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
I summoned you, oh nephew dear&lt;br&gt;
because you know this idle place&lt;br&gt;
and may, perchance, assist me in&lt;br&gt;
my half-arsed aim to save my face.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="quo"&gt;&amp;#8216;&lt;/span&gt;Oh, do you know of such a shop?&amp;#8217;&lt;br&gt;
he cried. &amp;#8216;Why yes,&amp;#8217; I reassured.&lt;br&gt;
&amp;#8216;I came upon it last week gone&lt;br&gt;
while I was wand&amp;#8217;ring, deathly bored&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
and waiting for the match to start - &amp;#8216;twas&lt;br&gt;
Ajax versus Feyenoord.&lt;br&gt;
And lo, there was I, visilin&lt;br&gt;
the subject of your previous words,&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
A merchant&amp;#8217;s house without compare,&lt;br&gt;
A smorgasbord of &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DIY&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;br&gt;
where any home-improvement scheme&lt;br&gt;
is possible!&amp;#8217; I hoarsly cried.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="quo"&gt;&amp;#8216;&lt;/span&gt;Oh, joy!&amp;#8217; he yelled. &amp;#8216;It must reveal&lt;br&gt;
Its manifold delights to me!&amp;#8217;&lt;br&gt;
I briefly thought to tease him but&lt;br&gt;
he touched me with his abject plea.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="quo"&gt;&amp;#8216;&lt;/span&gt;The place you seek is very near.&lt;br&gt;
You take a right, then left, and then&lt;br&gt;
you pass the demon traffic lights&lt;br&gt;
which are not fit for God nor men&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
and then proceed to yonder street.&lt;br&gt;
And there, Valhalla you will mark.&lt;br&gt;
&amp;#8216;You king of men!&amp;#8217; he thanked me, and&lt;br&gt;
we parted in the dingy dark.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>OED to remove word “gullible”</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/uk/oed-to-remove-word-gullible" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2009-06-29T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2009-06-29:uk/oed-to-remove-word-gullible</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#8217;s been the time-honoured joke of the schoolyards, workplaces and even safari parks: &amp;#8220;gullible is not in the dictionary.&amp;#8221; The irony stems from the fact that only the gullible would believe such a claim, but the Oxford English Dictionary team are seeking to bring an end to this long-running mirth&amp;nbsp;device.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As part of their ongoing fun-prevention campaign,
the makers of the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;OED&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#8212; a long-standing lexicographic
institution &amp;#8212; have voted 14 to 3 to remove the
word gullible from the pages of the great word&amp;nbsp;tome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;The joke has gone on long enough,&amp;#8221; explains Colin
Waterman, &lt;span class="caps"&gt;OED&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="caps"&gt;CEO&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;span class="caps"&gt;OBE&lt;/span&gt; and brother to star of
1970s police drama &lt;em&gt;The Sweeney&lt;/em&gt;,
John Thaw. &amp;#8220;It amused a few of us when the joke
first started, but we&amp;#8217;ve decided it has to come to an
end. We&amp;#8217;ve removed the word altogether so if
anyone does fall for it again, they will be ones
in the right, thus negating the&amp;nbsp;whimsy.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whilst futurists are speculating a reduction in
lexicographic tomfoolery in 2010, several groups
are claiming the move by the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;OED&lt;/span&gt; will not solve
the&amp;nbsp;problem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;It&amp;#8217;s obvius, innit?&amp;#8221; claims the Minister for Education,
&amp;#8220;peeple will jst make jokes bout uther werds.&amp;#8221; Several
comedy pressure groups have also suggested that
the joke may invert itself with proponents
simply telling their victims the word &amp;#8220;gullible&amp;#8221; has been
returned to the&amp;nbsp;dictionary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The origins of the original joke are speculative at worst
and at best, pretty well-known. According to banter
historians, the joke dates as far back as 1584 when Sir
Walter Raleigh was known to use it as an ice-breaker
on encountering people native to the Americas. On first contact,
while trying to establish communication, he would joke
that our language had no word for gullible. Once they
understood the joke, it was said to have helped ease colonial&amp;nbsp;tensions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even the word itself is said to be coined by the explorer. As
a small boy, he would perform magic tricks to seagulls in Cornwall
and found that out of all sea birds, they were the easiest
to fool. Thus, he would talk about &amp;#8220;gulling&amp;#8221; people who were
easy to trick and referred to them as&amp;nbsp;&amp;#8220;gullable&amp;#8221;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 1814, the first Edition of The Times was printed, but with
poor timing as news had yet to be invented. The writers for the
paper had to resort to filling pages with their shopping lists,
anecdotes from their holidays and the rest was padded
out with pages and pages of the letter &amp;#8220;A&amp;#8221; over
and over. This caused a great shortage in the
letter A for other publications, thus many words ending in &amp;#8220;able&amp;#8221;
were changed to &amp;#8220;ible&amp;#8221; &amp;#8212; along with &amp;#8220;gullible&amp;#8221; &amp;#8212; giving
the modern spelling as we know it&amp;nbsp;today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new edition of the Oxford English Dictionary
will be out in time for Christmas and is said
to be the first edition with the word removed altogether.
Language scholars are yet to comment on whether this
will affect day to day conversation as they are all on&amp;nbsp;holiday.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Fire Chief Warns Over Miniature Fire Truck Danger</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/uk/fire-chief-warns-over-miniature-fire-truck-danger" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2009-04-10T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2009-04-10:uk/fire-chief-warns-over-miniature-fire-truck-danger</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
The head of the fire service in England and Kent has expressed his reservations over the deployment of 4-foot fire engines in the fight against&amp;nbsp;conflagrations.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Sir Malcolm Burnley told &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; that the Labour government&amp;#8217;s plans to 
deploy miniature fire trucks filled with little weak shrunken men to man 
them could seriously affect the fire service&amp;#8217;s effectiveness in doing 
whatever it is they&amp;nbsp;do.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="quo"&gt;&amp;#8216;&lt;/span&gt;The Home Secretary has clearly not thought this one through&amp;#8217;, said 
Sir Malcolm, on the eve of his wife&amp;#8217;s birthday yesterday. &amp;#8216;Anyone who&amp;#8217;s 
ever seen Thunderbirds  will know that most fires will easily reach the 
height of an average interstellar spacecraft, and in this day and age, 
we need bigger fire trucks, not smaller&amp;nbsp;ones.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The initiative is understood to have been introduced in response to 
sweeping budget cuts flying across Whitehall. &amp;#8216;Simple mathematics 
dictates that when the dimensions of a solid are reduced by a factor of 
2, its volume will decrease by a factor of 8&amp;#8217;, said a Home Office 
spokescomedian. &amp;#8216;Therefore, by merely halving the length of a fire 
truck, the government can reduce its expenses by nearly 88 per&amp;nbsp;cent.&amp;#8217;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="quo"&gt;&amp;#8216;&lt;/span&gt;Of course, this will mean that they will only be able to carry one 
eighth of the water that they could previously carry, and all of the 
personnel would have to speak in high-pitched voices and brandish their 
fists regularly at no-one in particular, but we do not feel that the 
service will be compromised at all.&amp;#8217; When asked to justify this clear 
lie, he declined&amp;nbsp;loudly.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; understands that, if successful, the downsizing scheme could be 
rolled out to the other emergency services, and possibly then to theatre 
producers such as Andrew Lloyd Webber and Cameron Mackintosh. There is 
even understood to be rumours about the Home Office of the entire 
country being shrunk in order to fit into the middle of France, allowing 
the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UK&lt;/span&gt; to save billions on the renting of expensive prime real estate in 
the eastern Atlantic&amp;nbsp;Ocean.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; has since discovered that these rumours in fact came from 
&amp;#8216;Chemotherapy Bob&amp;#8217; of Borough High&amp;nbsp;Street.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>World’s Youngest Baby Born</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/uk/worlds-youngest-baby-born" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2009-04-03T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2009-04-03:uk/worlds-youngest-baby-born</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;A dilapidated hospital earmarked for destruction was celebrating today after hosting the birth of the world&amp;#8217;s youngest ever&amp;nbsp;baby.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guy&amp;#8217;s Hospital in London was, until today, scheduled to be blown up in the government&amp;#8217;s anti-hospital white paper 
published last week. Standards have been falling consistently over the last several decades, as a result of shabby 
work practices and some annoying syringes. But the staff and patients&amp;#8217; malais turned to jubilation this morning as a 
baby was born that could spell the end of the hospital&amp;#8217;s&amp;nbsp;woes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;My husband and I had lots of sex about nine months ago&amp;#8221;, said Tracy Smithford from her bed, &amp;#8220;but it was still quite 
a shock when I found out I was pregnant. So I travelled here to Guy&amp;#8217;s in the Toyota. Before I came here, I just 
assumed that I&amp;#8217;d be having a normal, boring baby, and I never even imagined that I&amp;#8217;d give birth to such a little&amp;nbsp;miracle.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doctors monitoring the baby&amp;#8217;s progress estimated that a few minutes after birth, the child was only a couple of 
minutes old, one of the youngest babies ever to have been born. Subsequent research showed that, prior to this, the 
baby was likely to have been less than one minute old for a brief period, thus claiming the title of youngest baby 
ever recorded. Speculation that the baby could have been exactly 0 minutes old for an infinitesimal period was rife 
among mathematicians, and confirmation is expected within a few&amp;nbsp;days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The accolade has delighted management at Guy&amp;#8217;s Hospital, who are hoping that the notoriously bandwagon-jumping Labour 
government will reverse their closure decision, pump millions of pounds into new equipment and staff and paint 
the building in nice gold paint. An order is expected to be placed for a large banner device to be dangled from the 
exterior frontage of the building in commemoration of the Gulf&amp;nbsp;War. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;We love that this couple chose to have their baby here&amp;#8221;, said senior nurse Colin Wang Tang. &amp;#8220;We&amp;#8217;ve all been 
wondering what this child will achieve in its life, after this great 
start it&amp;#8217;s had,&amp;#8221; said his colleague, head porter 
Vicenzo Chianti. &amp;#8220;My view is that he&amp;#8217;ll attend one of the great public schools, graduate from Oxford Brookes, and run 
a successful shipping law firm, before losing his fortune on the horses and late-night pay-per-view and ending his 
life in a ditch in Guildford on&amp;nbsp;fire.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Following the record-breaking birth and the money and publicity that it brought, parents everywhere are now likely 
to be humping maniacally in the hope of claiming the title for their little child. At this stage, however, experts 
suggest that the likelihood of a baby being younger than one minute old, even for a few seconds, is just a pipe dream 
for&amp;nbsp;most.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Punctuation Error Causes Train Derailment</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/uk/punctuation-error-causes-train-derailment" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2009-03-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2009-03-20:uk/punctuation-error-causes-train-derailment</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;17 people were injured, some lightly, when a commuter train derailed at Tring this morning, causing widespread delays across the entire rail 
network and to some shipping&amp;nbsp;lanes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;London Midland train company couldn&amp;#8217;t believe it today when the 06.48 service from Northampton left the rails just north of Tring station with 948 
people compressed on board. The cause of the accident is speculated to have been a punctuation error in the recent London Midlands timetable. Arnie, 
of London Midland, said &amp;#8216;The train was approaching Tring station when it left the track at approximately 08.23. We immediately shut down the 
surrounding area and summoned emergency personnel to the site to coordinate a press release. We are unable to comment further at this&amp;nbsp;time.&amp;#8217;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whilst the damage to infrastructure was significant, injuries seemed to be slight. A passing hospital reported a small number of walking 
wounded attending A&amp;E, with afflictions ranging from damaged wallets to an amalgamated orgasm. One passenger was admitted with advanced head cancer, 
although this is thought to be unrelated to the accident. No-one is believed to have been killed in the crash, but a number of people were seen 
wandering the track, confused and dazed and unsure what to do. Network Rail denied reports that engineers were at work on the line that&amp;nbsp;morning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;London Midland have, apparently, begun an inquiry into the incident. Alexander Domestic-Appliances, editor of the suspected timetable, told &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt;, 
&amp;#8216;It appears that a full stop was accidentally inserted into the Northampton to Euston section of the timetable, immediately after the word &amp;#8216;Tring&amp;#8217;. 
This ad hoc punctuation was detected by our train&amp;#8217;s Automatic Semantics System, &lt;span class="caps"&gt;ASS&lt;/span&gt;, and caused the train to bounce off of the rails at this point. 
Whilst we regret the loss of dignity suffered by our passengers, this does show that the system is operating as designed.&amp;#8217; Asked whether the 
offending timetables will be withdrawn and corrected, Mr Domestic-Appliances lit a cigarette and leaned against a nearby fridge&amp;nbsp;casually.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The incident has raised concerns over London Midland trains&amp;#8217; &lt;span class="caps"&gt;ASS&lt;/span&gt;. The crash recalls an incident on a British Rail train in 1985, which collided 
with an emu near Chipping Sodbury after a performance of &amp;#8216;Die Fledermaus&amp;#8217; at a local theatre interfered with the trackwork. In both of these cases, 
the train&amp;#8217;s technology responded to something stupidly unlikely to affect passenger safety. As a result, a recent resurgence in the popularity of light 
opera and grammar in the Home Counties has caused lesser publications to speculate on the likelihood of a much more serious accident in the near 
future. Network Rail has been unable to comment until it has completed its internal investigation of the tracks and signalling in the area, and has 
initiated engineering work to ensure that the Straussian conductivity of the rails is within the limits specified by some government&amp;nbsp;guy.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Runcorn Honoured in Video Game Legacy</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/uk/runcorn-honoured-in-video-game-legacy" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2009-03-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2009-03-02:uk/runcorn-honoured-in-video-game-legacy</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Locals to the Cheshire town of Runcorn today received news of an accolade of a very high order as they were chosen as the namesake of a new character in the Pokemon video game series, produced by&amp;nbsp;Nintendo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nintendo will be releasing &lt;em&gt;Pokemon: The Silver Jubilee Edition&lt;/em&gt;
in Autumn this year which will be 26th in the
series of video games in which players battle with
small, fictional creatures called &lt;em&gt;Pokemon&lt;/em&gt;,
which is short for &amp;#8220;Pokey&amp;nbsp;Monsters&amp;#8221;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was said that the Japanese games giant had
shortlisted several &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UK&lt;/span&gt; settlements to be
the inspiration for the new character
introduced in the latest game in the&amp;nbsp;franchise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amongst the towns that didn&amp;#8217;t make the final
choice were Gateshead, Slough and Chipping Sodbury.
It is understood that the town of Skegness was
also approached, but declined to be shortlisted
on moral&amp;nbsp;grounds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;Naturally, we&amp;#8217;re delighted,&amp;#8221; gleeful Runcorn
councillor Peter Chu tells &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; in his first
interview since parole. &amp;#8220;This is going to be
a tremendous boon for all the people of&amp;nbsp;Runcorn.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Early estimates forecast an approximate
growth in tourism of 1.41% when the new
video game appears in the shops on 31st
October. Walking down the High Street,
it can be seen that local businesses are already
celebrating the&amp;nbsp;honour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;This is the best thing to happen to
the town since the building of the
Bridgewater canal,&amp;#8221;
gushes Agnes Cream, a local travel agent
who is already negotiating discounted
B&amp;amp;B rates in the area for any Japanese&amp;nbsp;visitors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A special parade will be held through the town
this Sunday, but those taking part are
struggling with the fact the nearest Pokemon
costume shop is in&amp;nbsp;Manchester.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;The parade will most definitely go ahead,&amp;#8221;
confirms Gareth Silo, head of the town council,
adorning full Pikachu&amp;nbsp;dress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A spokesperson from Nintendo adds they
chose Runcorn after a painfully rigorous
decision process and they look forward
to having the town&amp;#8217;s namesake spearhead
the latest game as its star&amp;nbsp;character.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He tells us that &amp;#8220;Runcorn is the perfect
pokey town for our&amp;nbsp;pokemon.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Serial Killers “Very Sorry” for Mass Murder</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/business/serial-killers-very-sorry-for-mass-murder" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2009-02-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2009-02-11:business/serial-killers-very-sorry-for-mass-murder</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
Police recordings released under the Freedom from Information Act 2010 have revealed the surprising accounts of several convicted serial killers apologising for their&amp;nbsp;actions.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
In what some are calling a bold and unexpected move,
mass murderers such as Harold Shipman and Peter
Sutcliffe can be seen giving their heartfelt
apologies for the acts they committed and the lives
they&amp;nbsp;affected.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;I acted entirely out of my own selfish desires
and for that I am deeply, very sorry,&amp;#8221; an apologetic
Harold Shipman is heard to say on video footage
acquired by &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; through entirely legitimate&amp;nbsp;means.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
A remorseful Peter Sutcliffe says, &amp;#8220;I&amp;#8217;m incredibly
sorry for my actions and the lives they&amp;nbsp;affected.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Similar statements can be heard from Myra Hindley,
Fred West and Trevor&amp;nbsp;Hardy.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Whilst these statements have been a surprise to many,
many people have been calling it &amp;#8220;too little, too&amp;nbsp;late&amp;#8221;.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;I&amp;#8217;m not having it,&amp;#8221; says Jane Button, a caretaker
from Crewe. &amp;#8220;An apology this late is all well and good,
but it&amp;#8217;s not going to get my husband&amp;#8217;s pension
back or pay our&amp;nbsp;mortgage.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Will Fully-Ignorant, head of Lock Em Up &amp;#8212; a prison
advocacy group &amp;#8212; says he won&amp;#8217;t accept the apologies.
&amp;#8220;This is simply not good enough. It merely tells us
they knew full well what they were doing was wrong,
but they only cared about themselves. I&amp;#8217;m not
having it. Lock them up, that&amp;#8217;s what I&amp;nbsp;say.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The government is yet to release a statement on the
matter, but it believed that they will be looking
to divert even more tax money into bailing some of these
criminals out of&amp;nbsp;prison.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Famous Singer Caught Banking in Public Toilets</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/business/famous-singer-caught-banking-in-public-toilets" rel="alternate"></link><updated>1998-04-07T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,1998-04-07:business/famous-singer-caught-banking-in-public-toilets</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The entertainment industry shat itself this morning when reports leaked out that
a famous singer had been arrested last night for financial&amp;nbsp;indecency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The singer could not be named for aural reasons, but details of the case so far
indicate that the celebrity was found by authorities banking in the cubicle of
recently constructed public amenities near York&amp;nbsp;Minster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;The new York public toilet facilities were certainly not intended for such
use,&amp;#8221; rants Martin McBee, Head of the Flushable Facilities Department of York
council, speaking through an&amp;nbsp;interpreter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;Wee intend to flush out all of these types from our cistern. We will not duck
away from this toilet issue. This man may be a celebrity, but he made a fecal
mistake thinking we would not prosecute such behaviour.&amp;nbsp;Bogbrush.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Police sources have confirmed the man was found committing indecent financial
acts at approximately 23:02 last&amp;nbsp;night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;There were reports that people patronising the urinals could hear the distinct
sound of hard selling,&amp;#8221; confirms the first man we found wearing a policeman&amp;#8217;s&amp;nbsp;helmet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;A call was logged with the local constabulary and upon arrival, we apprehended
the man before his third return on&amp;nbsp;investment.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A official police statement released today reminds people that those wishing to
bank would be best advised to do it at&amp;nbsp;home.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry></feed>