<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>WAFTI News</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/feeds/business.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://news.wafti.org.uk/</id><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><entry><title>Business Chiefs Announce Merger</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/business/business-chiefs-announce-merger" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:business/business-chiefs-announce-merger</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Excitement was approaching today when the leaders of two of Britain&amp;#8217;s largest companies announced that they were going to meld&amp;nbsp;together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;P&gt;David Axe, &lt;span class="caps"&gt;CEO&lt;/span&gt; of Corporate Leisure Impalements, and Bill String, chairman of Liquid-Based Ethanol Endrinkment Solutions Ltd, spoke today at a 
joint press conference revealing their intentions to fuse their vital organs into a single, malleable&amp;nbsp;individual.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="quo"&gt;&amp;#8216;&lt;/span&gt;Business leaders in this country have been the public&amp;#8217;s whipping boys for many months,&amp;#8217; said Mr Axe, &amp;#8216;and my partner and I have decided to put an 
end to this situation by announcing this merger. The aquisition of the operations arm of Mr String&amp;#8217;s body, by my own, is intended to create a 
streamlined, 
attractive model to better withstand the vibrations of the corporate violin.&amp;#8217; &amp;#8216;Our companies are natural partners,&amp;#8217; agreed Mr String, &amp;#8216;and it is 
essential that we are able to work together to ride out the tough wave of no money effectively. The best way to achieve this is for us to undergo
extensive surgery to create a fantastic dual&amp;nbsp;human.&amp;#8217; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is thought that the procedure would constitute an aggressive takeover bid for Mr String&amp;#8217;s cranial areas and thighs by a consortium of Mr Axe 
and some surgeons, likely backed by a set of complex instruments. The head, or &amp;#8216;nodule&amp;#8217;, of the subject&amp;#8217;s body would then be progressively devalued 
and several slices of the initiator&amp;#8217;s brain data inserted. Given the overlapping business interests of the relevant arms of the two companies, there 
is likely to be some duplication of resources; more specifically, lots of duplication. As a result, reductions in size will need to be made, although 
analysts say that this will largely be achieved by natural wastage, with compulsory loss of staff and body tissue kept to a&amp;nbsp;minimum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This event will mark the first time that such an operation has been attempted, and details of the plan are scant, however the companies in 
question both have vast capital pools. The resultant uber-organisation is therefore likely to pursue a rapid hostile aquisition of the nearest dog 
food processing facility. Publicans have speculated that the cost of the entire procedure could run into billions of something. Commentators 
themselves have given mixed responses to the news. &amp;#8216;I&amp;#8217;m quite mixed about it&amp;#8217;, said John Motson. Murray Walker&amp;#8217;s estate was unable 
to comment with the required amount of enthusiasm, and Tony Gubba&amp;#8217;s response was incorrect. 

&lt;p&gt;It is difficult to describe the kinds of hideous, neurotic wrangling that took place behind the scenes in this deal. Mr Axe&amp;#8217;s company, a 
recreational stabbing specialist, has a very strong market base in the London region. Axe himself is known as one of the corporate world&amp;#8217;s most 
enlightened pianists, and would have beaten down with every shred of his fibre any aggressive bid by String&amp;#8217;s company. String himself is likely
to have been on the ropes for much of the proceedings as it went eventually to the wire. Others say that String fought back cannily, and that 
the deal was hanging by a thread until a cabled bond exchange released Axe&amp;#8217;s head from the block and the pendulum swung&amp;nbsp;back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The outcome of the man-meld is awaited excitedly by the Bank of England, who have a&amp;nbsp;sweepstake.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Economic Crisis Forces Golf Courses to Reduce Number Of Holes</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/business/economic-crisis-forces-golf-courses-to-reduce-number-of-holes" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>Carl</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:business/economic-crisis-forces-golf-courses-to-reduce-number-of-holes</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
Mild reductions of bonuses at large financial companies, caused by stern headlines in the Daily Mail, have curtailed the feel-good fancy free attitudes of bankers everywhere, and it&amp;#8217;s the golf courses who are&amp;nbsp;suffering.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Once, hitting the fairway was enough to avoid the obstacles, 
but old favourites like the water hazard have been joined by a 
swathe of bleary-eyed bankers. Angry old men used to be considered
a staple of the golfing experience. Now, they are finding themselves
upstaged by angry middle-aged&amp;nbsp;men.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Gary Quickwin works at Shortsighted Holdings. &amp;#8220;It&amp;#8217;s hard. We only have 
our salaries to live on, and who can manage on six figures alone? It&amp;#8217;s a disgrace.&amp;#8221; 
He paused to berate his caddy. &amp;#8220;I didn&amp;#8217;t plan ahead and have no savings, and I
also have a huge house. Who&amp;#8217;s going to pay for that I ask&amp;nbsp;you?&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
His colleague, Tony Dontlook-Toohard, nodded in agreement. &amp;#8220;It&amp;#8217;s like, I do
all this work inventing money from nothing, right, and now I&amp;#8217;m not getting
to keep it. Where&amp;#8217;s the&amp;nbsp;justice?&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
They are not the only ones. All across Fritteraway Park,
there are hundreds of disgruntled investment bankers and&amp;nbsp;economists. 
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Who is the worst affected by this crisis however? The golf course owners 
themselves. A spokesman for the International Golfcourse Operators Association 
spoke to &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; News earlier today. &amp;#8220;It&amp;#8217;s terrible,&amp;#8221; he said. &amp;#8220;We can&amp;#8217;t stock
Blue Label in the clubhouse any more, noone buys it. Everyone&amp;#8217;s back on 
Maker&amp;#8217;s Mark. We&amp;#8217;ve had no choice but to reduce the number of holes -
we just can&amp;#8217;t afford to pay someone to rake the cigarette butts out of the
bunkers any&amp;nbsp;more.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Asked whether the players themselves were upset at this, he responded 
&amp;#8220;Not really - they&amp;#8217;re just happier with their lower par. Noone seems
to have noticed that actually there&amp;#8217;s less than they think there&amp;nbsp;is.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>John Lewis Decimates Business Landscape With “2.0” Bombshell</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/business/john-lewis-decimates-business-landscape-with-20-bombshell" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>Carl</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:business/john-lewis-decimates-business-landscape-with-20-bombshell</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
The John Lewis Partnership today announced plans to revolutionise retail by
updating the business model of their 27 department stores across the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UK&lt;/span&gt; to
catch up to the Internet&amp;nbsp;age.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
As of the 31st of August, the stores will distribute their products for free, 
while advertising will be the sole income for the stores. The goods 
themselves will act as loss leaders to entice the consumer to the store. 
Advertisments will be placed on walls, floors and the soon to be erected 
stands decicated to displaying both static and video adverts. Approximately
70% of existing shop floor space will be converted to advert space to 
increase the ratio of income generating floorspace to attraction only&amp;nbsp;floorspace.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The move is stunning, but not without precedent. The burgeoning success of 
&amp;#8220;Web 2.0&amp;#8221; strategies as successfully employed by such trend-setters as Facebook 
and Twitter has caused many business experts to predict its appearance in
the more traditional world of bricks-and-mortar&amp;nbsp;stores. 
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Facebook was valued at approximately $15bn dollars when they raised capital 
by selling stock to Microsoft; Twitter&amp;#8217;s value was said to be $500m when 
Facebook attempted to buy them with an offer of that value of Facebook stock
in a move that many now discredited experts would have described as trading 
clouds only two decades ago. Both have done so by concentrating on finding 
audience for adverts rather than the clearly defunct approach of having a product 
that customers are willing to pay&amp;nbsp;for.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;We have to move with the times,&amp;#8221; said Bertram Yardy, the manager of the 
Newcastle branch. &amp;#8220;These days success isn&amp;#8217;t about profits or sustainability. 
The number of customers you attract defines your worth as a business and we 
want to tap into&amp;nbsp;that.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
What sort of adverts will be displayed? &amp;#8220;The plan is to have a better quality
of advert as well as a greater number. For example, we have one - you&amp;#8217;ll love
this - where you have to try to swat the fly. If you do, you can win prizes! I
think it&amp;#8217;ll really add to the experience of shopping in a John Lewis store
and will certainly augment the product we have in a way that we just couldn&amp;#8217;t
do before with sales staff and tasteful presentation,&amp;#8221; Yardy&amp;nbsp;said.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The partnership aims to have more than tripled the number of customers coming 
into their stores by 2011. While the revenue from advertsing will be unimportantly 
less than that of selling products, Yardy feels that a smaller profit from a larger
number of people is an acheivable goal. &amp;#8220;Free is such an enticing concept, and 
getting something for free will make people want to spend money on the products
we&amp;#8217;re advertsing,&amp;#8221; he&amp;nbsp;explained.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>McDonalds Sues Man</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/business/mcdonalds-sues-man" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:business/mcdonalds-sues-man</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
McDonalds, the most litigious company in the universe, have
sued a Scottish man because his name contains the prefix&amp;nbsp;&amp;#8220;Mc&amp;#8221;.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
A company spokesman said &amp;#8220;He&amp;#8217;s&amp;nbsp;gay.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; would like to point out that McDonald&amp;#8217;s 
spokesmen are in no meaningful way
homophobic, that McDonald&amp;#8217;s is not necessarily the most litigious 
company in the universe, and that whilst the company may sometimes break
&lt;a href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/education/1466398.stm"&gt;child labour 
laws&lt;/a&gt;,
mislead the public over the contents of its
&lt;a href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/1348296.stm"&gt;products&lt;/a&gt; and 
implement a Blairite 45-minute policy on
&lt;a href="http://www.guardian.co.uk/uk_news/story/0,,2225434,00.html"&gt;dining&lt;/a&gt;,
it is, in many ways, of fundamental importance to British&amp;nbsp;society.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
In other news, Conservative leader David Cameron has recently stated that British society is
&amp;#8216;broken&amp;#8217;. This pronouncement marks the first and only time that &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; will ever side itself with
the fawning, preening, amoral, jumped-up, bandwagon-leaping, superlatively misguided, 
may-I-polish-your-curling-irons-Mrs-Thatcher cringeworthy, brain-bloated piece of abject pomposity 
Mr Cameron. 
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; would also like to point out that it is quite possible that a McJobsworth will identify the
above headline and opening paragraph as something warranting a vastly expensive and frivolous
lawsuit, which, given McDonald&amp;#8217;s previous litigation record against smaller business interests,
would be nothing short of sheer moronic pointlessness. However, we will not.

We would like to apologise for any intentional hurt&amp;nbsp;caused.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Local Man Decides Not To “BIt”</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/business/local-man-decides-not-to-bit" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-01:business/local-man-decides-not-to-bit</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;A North Stratford man has taken a decisive stand against the age-old home refurbishment edict by deciding not to use B&amp;amp;Q as the supplier for his minor home improvement&amp;nbsp;projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The years-old inane advertising slogan encouraged its listeners to repair to their nearest B&amp;Q store and &amp;#8216;do it&amp;#8217; with their selection of &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DIY&lt;/span&gt; ephemera, but Tony Ottoman-Sideboard decided to rise above the innuendo and reject B&amp;Q&amp;#8217;s&amp;nbsp;philosophy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="quo"&gt;&amp;#8216;&lt;/span&gt;It always seemed to me that B&amp;Q and their competitors had been fixing prices on chipboard&amp;#8217;, said Mr Ottoman-Sideboard, a part-time conspiracy theorist, &amp;#8216;and so I decided to renounce the entire industry and only use organic produce in my wardrobing.&amp;#8217; Mr Ottoman-Sideboard was reluctant to say where his organic products were sourced, but his estranged cousin and former business partner, Roger Flatpack, from Cheadle, was happy to speak to &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="quo"&gt;&amp;#8216;&lt;/span&gt;Tony&amp;#8217;s always been a bit of a leftie,&amp;#8217; said Mr Flatpack, now Minister for Chemical Affairs, &amp;#8216;and always stood out in our family. I&amp;#8217;m not one to eulogise on family history, but the great Statesman himself had no problems with mass-produced softwood fixtures.&amp;#8217; Mr Flatpack refused to elaborate&amp;nbsp;further.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The reason for Mr Ottoman-Sideboard&amp;#8217;s actions remain a mystery. B&amp;Q ceased the offending advertising campaign several years ago, and the company has since concentrated its efforts in claiming that they are the cheapest company around for all &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DIY&lt;/span&gt; purchases, whether the claim is true or&amp;nbsp;not.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Serial Killers “Very Sorry” for Mass Murder</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/business/serial-killers-very-sorry-for-mass-murder" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2009-02-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2009-02-11:business/serial-killers-very-sorry-for-mass-murder</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
Police recordings released under the Freedom from Information Act 2010 have revealed the surprising accounts of several convicted serial killers apologising for their&amp;nbsp;actions.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
In what some are calling a bold and unexpected move,
mass murderers such as Harold Shipman and Peter
Sutcliffe can be seen giving their heartfelt
apologies for the acts they committed and the lives
they&amp;nbsp;affected.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;I acted entirely out of my own selfish desires
and for that I am deeply, very sorry,&amp;#8221; an apologetic
Harold Shipman is heard to say on video footage
acquired by &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; through entirely legitimate&amp;nbsp;means.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
A remorseful Peter Sutcliffe says, &amp;#8220;I&amp;#8217;m incredibly
sorry for my actions and the lives they&amp;nbsp;affected.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Similar statements can be heard from Myra Hindley,
Fred West and Trevor&amp;nbsp;Hardy.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Whilst these statements have been a surprise to many,
many people have been calling it &amp;#8220;too little, too&amp;nbsp;late&amp;#8221;.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;I&amp;#8217;m not having it,&amp;#8221; says Jane Button, a caretaker
from Crewe. &amp;#8220;An apology this late is all well and good,
but it&amp;#8217;s not going to get my husband&amp;#8217;s pension
back or pay our&amp;nbsp;mortgage.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Will Fully-Ignorant, head of Lock Em Up &amp;#8212; a prison
advocacy group &amp;#8212; says he won&amp;#8217;t accept the apologies.
&amp;#8220;This is simply not good enough. It merely tells us
they knew full well what they were doing was wrong,
but they only cared about themselves. I&amp;#8217;m not
having it. Lock them up, that&amp;#8217;s what I&amp;nbsp;say.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The government is yet to release a statement on the
matter, but it believed that they will be looking
to divert even more tax money into bailing some of these
criminals out of&amp;nbsp;prison.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Famous Singer Caught Banking in Public Toilets</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/business/famous-singer-caught-banking-in-public-toilets" rel="alternate"></link><updated>1998-04-07T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,1998-04-07:business/famous-singer-caught-banking-in-public-toilets</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The entertainment industry shat itself this morning when reports leaked out that
a famous singer had been arrested last night for financial&amp;nbsp;indecency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The singer could not be named for aural reasons, but details of the case so far
indicate that the celebrity was found by authorities banking in the cubicle of
recently constructed public amenities near York&amp;nbsp;Minster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;The new York public toilet facilities were certainly not intended for such
use,&amp;#8221; rants Martin McBee, Head of the Flushable Facilities Department of York
council, speaking through an&amp;nbsp;interpreter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;Wee intend to flush out all of these types from our cistern. We will not duck
away from this toilet issue. This man may be a celebrity, but he made a fecal
mistake thinking we would not prosecute such behaviour.&amp;nbsp;Bogbrush.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Police sources have confirmed the man was found committing indecent financial
acts at approximately 23:02 last&amp;nbsp;night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;There were reports that people patronising the urinals could hear the distinct
sound of hard selling,&amp;#8221; confirms the first man we found wearing a policeman&amp;#8217;s&amp;nbsp;helmet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;A call was logged with the local constabulary and upon arrival, we apprehended
the man before his third return on&amp;nbsp;investment.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A official police statement released today reminds people that those wishing to
bank would be best advised to do it at&amp;nbsp;home.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry></feed>