<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>WAFTI News</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/feeds/entertainment.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://news.wafti.org.uk/</id><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><entry><title>40-Year-Old Beatles Songs Discovered In The Charts</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/entertainment/40-year-old-beatles-songs-discovered-in-the-charts" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:entertainment/40-year-old-beatles-songs-discovered-in-the-charts</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
Music pundits and the listening public alike were feeling fine today as Apple Corp announced the discovery of hundreds of Beatles songs in 
the upper reaches of the Top 40. However, experts have expressed doubts as to their&amp;nbsp;authenticity.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The initial announcement of the discovery was made by James Female, a hardback writer and part-time Conservative councillor from Upminster. &amp;#8216;I&amp;#8217;ve 
been an admirer of The Rolling Beatles for as long as I can remember,&amp;#8217; he told &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt;. &amp;#8216;I happened to be sitting at home browsing the interweb when I 
accidentally typed in the wrong website navigation code and found myself looking at the front screen of something called Amazon. And there I saw 
listed this huge box of rock and roll song-cycles by Ringo and the rest. I couldn&amp;#8217;t believe it, quite frankly, so I quickly pinged off an e-letter to 
Apple Corp and within minutes it was all over the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;RSSSSS&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;feeds.&amp;#8217;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class="sideinfo"&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Things that happened in the&amp;nbsp;60s&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1961: the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;USSR&lt;/span&gt; became the first nation to be transported into&amp;nbsp;space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1963: President Kennedy announces he is to have an&amp;nbsp;affair&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1965: Bob Dylan spots a cow at the Newport Folk&amp;nbsp;Festival&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1969: The 60s are finally outlawed as&amp;nbsp;pointless&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The Beatles were thought to be a band, invented in the early 1960s, although little else is known of their career and work. Folklorists&amp;#8217; writings and 
vagrants&amp;#8217; tales form much of the small amount of information available. Songs generally accepted to have been written by them include the far-sighted 
animal rights anthem &amp;#8216;I Am The Walrus&amp;#8217; and the wedding party favourite &amp;#8216;Hey, Bulldog&amp;#8217;. They are speculated, however, to have produced more than two 
songs; indeed, experts have said that one in every 8 people may have heard one at some point in their&amp;nbsp;lives.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
It is understood that the find, thought to be the first find of its kind, contains most of the Beatles&amp;#8217; back catalogue, but musicologists 
speculate that they may not, in fact, be authentic original recordings. &amp;#8216;My colleagues and I have been studying these records since they were first 
brought to our attention,&amp;#8217; said Dr Adrian Bong, of the London College of Music and a world expert on music. &amp;#8216;The mood at first was electric. We tried 
to act naturally, but, whatever. However, after a more analytical approach ensued, we realised that what we were hearing could not be&amp;nbsp;authentic.&amp;#8217;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Dr Bong theorises that the recordings may have been tampered with by some form of electronic agent, prior to being transferred onto separate media 
and sold on to the public. &amp;#8216;Although we have absolutely no way of knowing this for certain, we feel sure that the waveforms have been digitally 
tweaked, fixing holes, if you will,&amp;#8217; said Dr Bong, &amp;#8216;and hence, what can be heard on these discs is perhaps not identical to what the group originally 
laid onto tape. This, of course, does not affect in any way the sheer apathy of a large cross-section of the music-listening public to this&amp;nbsp;find.&amp;#8217;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
It is not known how long the collection will remain within the top 40, but the Met Office has speculated that a new girl band is showing signs of 
forming somewhere in the Southeast of the country within the next decade or so, which may have a significant impact on the masters&amp;#8217; placing within 
the 
hit&amp;nbsp;parade.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; has not been able to investigate, verify or establish via hear&amp;#8217;say any of the information previously stated in this article, but the board  
of directors of &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt;&amp;#8217;s parent organisation, &lt;span class="caps"&gt;HP&lt;/span&gt; Bulmer Ltd, is adamant that it&amp;#8217;s all&amp;nbsp;true.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>American TV Show Writers Accidentally Write Plot</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/entertainment/american-tv-show-writers-accidentally-write-plot" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>Carl</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:entertainment/american-tv-show-writers-accidentally-write-plot</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
While desperately searching for the next question,
writer Paul O&amp;#8217;Paulsky stumbled upon an answer. This 
weekend viewers of Ambigous Situation will find 
themselves in a slightly reduced state of bewilderment 
after they see the newest&amp;nbsp;episode.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;I guess it had to happen eventually,&amp;#8221; O&amp;#8217;Paulsky said in
a packed press conference. &amp;#8220;We had so many loose ends
flying around that when trying to write a new one, I 
accidentally wrote in some&amp;nbsp;continuity.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Network chief Milkit Ahlot played down the incident.
&amp;#8220;This doesn&amp;#8217;t diminish our ability to string out the 
show much longer than necessary. We will still be able
to bleed its originality dry before we have to cancel.
We aren&amp;#8217;t in danger of doing a &amp;#8216;Battlestar Galactica&amp;#8217; and
plugging the plot holes. Shareholders have nothing to
worry&amp;nbsp;about.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
It remains to be seen whether or not the viewing public
will stand for such shenanigans however. Unwelcome and
unexpected elements of shows, such as referencing past
events, have been known to upset the audience. Ambiguous 
Situation and especially lead characted Captain Standard
will need to get back to their hard-hitting mundanity sooner 
rather than later or their 24th season could be their&amp;nbsp;last.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Ashes Series In Chaos After Mishap</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/entertainment/ashes-series-in-chaos-after-mishap" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:entertainment/ashes-series-in-chaos-after-mishap</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
The Ashes test series between England and Australia was thrown into 
disarray this afternoon after it was revealed that the urn had been knocked over 
last night and its contents&amp;nbsp;lost.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The news was revealed at a joint press conference given today by the English and Australian team captains and their wives or partners, held in a 
multiplex cemetary near the Oval. Full details have yet to emerge of the dusty incident, but England captain Andrew Strauss attempted to play down 
fears of a&amp;nbsp;bloodbath.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;I can tell you that, at approximately midnight last night, the celebrated Ashes trophy, for which we have for over a century pitted our best 
cricketers against the fine Australian boys, was accidentally dis-uprighted and the filling inside was lost&amp;#8221;, said Strauss. &amp;#8220;Whilst this incident 
will no doubt come as a shock, we can categorically state that the ethic of the team will not be affected, and we will continue to go out onto the 
field and lose for our country, as we have been doing for many&amp;nbsp;years.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Neither Strauss nor Australian captain Ricky Ponting gave any indication 
as to the cause of the mishap, although some details have been leaked to &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; 
from a disenchanted spin bowler. The England team were attending a private party hosted at Longstanton Crematorium by Moira Stuart, having taken the 
urn with them to ward off bad luck. It is alleged that one member of the England party, having consumed a large quantity of alcoholic whiskey, picked 
up the urn to play with it. He then attempted to climb into the urn and paddle it across the local aquaduct, and subsequently got into&amp;nbsp;difficulties.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Shortly afterwards, he was observed capsizing the urn, emptying its contents into the canal. The source then stated that the player returned to the 
party and, with the aid of a caddy, attempted to refill the urn with ashes swept from the crematorium floor. They then replaced the urn. The 
deception was discovered the following morning by the crematorium&amp;#8217;s Urn Curator, who noticed that the urn had been replaced not into its display 
hemisphere, but between the breasts of a dozing Moira Stewart behind the&amp;nbsp;pulpit.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The offending team member&amp;#8217;s behaviour is described as &amp;#8216;not a complete surprise&amp;#8217; by our source, likely intended as a way of letting off steam after a 
very tense start to the series. &amp;#8220;We were under constant pressure through the afternoon&amp;#8221;, said Strauss. &amp;#8220;They tormented us with their swing-off back 
launch propagation until the 7th clause. By the time we&amp;#8217;d levelled the score to 154-53-6.666&lt;57, Collingwood had short-tailed out and under for a 
blimp, and Panesar and Cook just couldn't scrummage the dildo-transfer to a 7-under-4 until collapsing the stork at 23. From the 4th timequarter, we 
picked up a bag of gossamer hits, maintained the left stick and finished with a pair of bereavements to seal the switch-draw. Although of course, 
that is still no excuse for&amp;nbsp;silliness."
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Whilst the offending cricketer&amp;#8217;s name has not yet been made public, his identity will surely be known to the incensed England coach, Andy Flower. &amp;#8220;To 
be honest, when I heard the news, I was bowled over, literally hit for six&amp;#8221;, said Flower, his forehead creased. &amp;#8220;I&amp;#8217;m stumped as to how one of my team 
could get caught out in such a fashion. From what I&amp;#8217;ve heard, he bails on the party, runs out for a duck into the river and gets caught out sinking 
the urn. How&amp;#8217;s that going to look to the supporters? He really hit the boundary last night, I can tell you. He&amp;#8217;s had a good innings, that boy, but 
he&amp;#8217;s in for a sledging now. Severely tests my patience.&amp;#8221; Asked how the incident would affect the team&amp;#8217;s performance in the remaining matches, he 
said, &amp;#8220;Well, there&amp;#8217;s definitely a corridor of uncertainty now, and I don&amp;#8217;t know how the Duckworth-Lewis we are going to be able to perform at our 
peak. All we can do is give it a damn good&amp;nbsp;googly.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The &lt;span class="caps"&gt;MCC&lt;/span&gt; was unavailable for comment today; Lords knows&amp;nbsp;why. 
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Bruce Springsteen Declared Sharia Compliant</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/entertainment/bruce-springsteen-declared-sharia-compliant" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:entertainment/bruce-springsteen-declared-sharia-compliant</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;caption &amp;#8216;These are all mine,&amp;#8217; says&amp;nbsp;judge&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a major blow to shirt-wearing rifle patriots across the lower states, hero Bruce Springsteen was declared compatible with the teachings of the 
Koran by the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UK&lt;/span&gt;&amp;#8217;s foremost Sharia&amp;nbsp;court.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Boss was said to be &amp;#8216;intrigued&amp;#8217; by the fatwa, which will now permit the playing of one of his albums during Islamic bank holidays. His family 
are also said to be alive and well at time of going to &amp;#8216;the Gutenberg&amp;#8217;. &amp;#8216;This is a great big boon to us all,&amp;#8217; said Springsteen,&amp;nbsp;megalomaniacally. 
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The decree was somewhat surprising, in the light of past animosity towards Him by every non-American. This includes Muslims and possibly some 
parakeets. Parakeets were not noted as fans of Himself prior to the 1970s, which was presumably when he released his first records. It is speculated 
that he has released several albums since. Astonishment was also expressed by some Springsteen analysts at the fact that the American midwest 
gave an excreted monkey-toss about what the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UK&lt;/span&gt;&amp;#8217;s opinion might be on something. No explanation has yet been offered by the spokesman for the&amp;nbsp;midwest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The director of the Muslim Religion of Dudley, Dr Wang Ping, confirmed &amp;#8216;Something about this whole thing didn&amp;#8217;t strike us as kosher, which was the 
final straw that clinched the albatross brain-fart.&amp;#8217; He contradicted himself with an official press release via a Printmaster 3000, stating 
&amp;#8216;Islamists will welcome this decision by the Sharia Court of Britain to recognise the wonder and beauty of His&amp;nbsp;creations.&amp;#8217;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whilst the playing of His music will be permitted during public holidays, his fast songs must be confined to daylight hours. This is due to the 
fact that tempos above 130bpm (bodies per minaret) have been shown, via studies, to affect the geological structure of the bedrock in certain 
areas of the oil-rich states, something which America is keen to avoid. &amp;#8216;It is paramount that the middle eastern area is kept as stable as 
possible, and we will do anything within our power to ensure this,&amp;#8217; our American spokesman told&amp;nbsp;us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The news will be a blow to Yusuf Islam, who has actually been striving for this accolade for several years. Other artists known to have been 
shortlisted for potential Sharia compliance include Cliff Richard, the Israeli Breakfast Quartet and the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DJ&lt;/span&gt; Vishnu&amp;nbsp;Experience.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Sony Music Entertainment achieves UK Christmas #1</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/entertainment/sony-music-entertainment-achieves-uk-christmas-1" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:entertainment/sony-music-entertainment-achieves-uk-christmas-1</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
In a neck and neck dash for the country&amp;#8217;s most pretigious
award, Sony Music Entertainment finally came out on
top with the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UK&lt;/span&gt; best-selling single for Christmas over
close rival: Sony Music&amp;nbsp;Entertainment.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The surprise win was part of a campaign on Facebook
and other social networking sites to get Sony Music
Entertainment to the godly number one spot in protest
at yet another number one from Sony Music&amp;nbsp;Entertainment.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UK&lt;/span&gt; number one selling single was announced at 7pm on Sunday
by the Queen as part of her popular culture round-up of 2009 on
Radio Four. She remarked it as being a historic moment in the entire
Commonwealth and a real testament to the power of the people.
She noted it as dwarfing lesser events such as the
Storming of the Bastille and the miners&amp;#8217; strikes in the&amp;nbsp;1980s.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;Finally, after all the historic, but frankly rubbish, events
of people organising to make a difference to their world, we
have something we can hold up as a shining example of human
achievement. All those involved should pat themselves on the
back, but I suspect they already have, &amp;#8221; rambled her&amp;nbsp;Majesty.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;For the past five years, Sony Music Entertainment has
had that Christmas number one spot with its manufactured
pop music,&amp;#8221; says Richard Porcupine, founder of the group
&amp;#8220;Sod Sony; let&amp;#8217;s get Sony to number one!&amp;#8221; on&amp;nbsp;Facebook.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;It&amp;#8217;s refreshing to get Sony Music Entertainment to number one
instead as a fart in the face of crap music and capitalism. I
am proud to have spear-headed this campaign and I think
everyone who made the effort to download a whole &lt;span class="caps"&gt;MP3&lt;/span&gt; should be proud&amp;nbsp;too.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Fans and supporters of the group are said to be &amp;#8220;mental&amp;#8221; with
delight at the news. One fan tells &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt;: &amp;#8220;I&amp;#8217;m just so well glad
we&amp;#8217;ve made such a difference in our world tonight. I&amp;#8217;m proud
to bring up my children in a world with the majority
of the country agreeing with my personal taste in music. This
must be how the Germans felt when the Berlin Wall&amp;nbsp;fell.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Mr. Porcupine&amp;#8217;s group was the fastest growing group on Facebook,
far outdoing groups such as &amp;#8220;A campaign to end the war in
Afghanistan&amp;#8221;, &amp;#8220;People opposed to the Digital Economy Bill&amp;#8221; and
&amp;#8220;We support curing cancer, saving sick puppies, declaring world
peace and methods to convert human pollution into&amp;nbsp;gold.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;I think people latched onto our cause as the most worthy for backing,&amp;#8221;
drones Dick Porcupine over his Twitter account. &amp;#8220;People saw something
terribly wrong with our world and worked their hardest to
fix it. Until today, people had to endure the hardship of a song
they didn&amp;#8217;t like being the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UK&lt;/span&gt; number one&amp;nbsp;single.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
A press release from Sony Music Entertainment describes
the company as &amp;#8220;chuffed&amp;#8221; that they came out on top
against Sony Music Entertainment. &amp;#8220;The best way to win in
a free market is to get competition between two of your own
products,&amp;#8221; laughed fat cat, Simon Custard over a large
class of Château&amp;nbsp;Latour.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Killjoy tosspots formed an apathy-driven campaign
called &amp;#8220;We don&amp;#8217;t give a flying panda&amp;#8217;s testicle what the
number one is&amp;#8221; on Facebook, but not on Twitter as the title
alone exceeded the character limit for Twitter&amp;nbsp;posts.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Their campaign manager finally got back to our enquiries
last week with the statement: &amp;#8220;we really don&amp;#8217;t care.&amp;#8221; Critics
have called his words &amp;#8220;succinct&amp;#8221; and &amp;#8220;missing the&amp;nbsp;point.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Rumours have indicated that Richard Porcupine may be nominated
for the Nobel Prize for&amp;nbsp;twattery.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry></feed>