<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>WAFTI News</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/feeds/health.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://news.wafti.org.uk/</id><updated>2015-02-02T21:38:52+01:00</updated><entry><title>Leading Shampoo Brands now “More Nutritious than Cereal”</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/leading-shampoo-brands-now-more-nutritious-than-cereal.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-02T21:38:52+01:00</updated><author><name>Carl</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-02:leading-shampoo-brands-now-more-nutritious-than-cereal.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;News has emerged this morning that the nutritional content of shampoo is often higher than that of breakfast&amp;nbsp;cereals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Rising uses of vitamin-rich ingredients such as aubergine in hair cleaning products means taking a shower can now count as one of your&amp;nbsp;five-a-day&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Scurvy and&amp;nbsp;Dandruff&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Captain Cook was reputed to have used Panone, an early forerunner of the vaunted Pantene 
range, to prevent his sailors catching scurvy and to keep their flowing locks shiny 
and free of split ends. His exact recipe is still unknown; however leading shampoo
chefs are confident they have, if not an exact replica, something of equivalent benefit
to both hair and&amp;nbsp;digestion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1821, George Stephenson, inventor of rockets, created similarly tasty head-soap. He
invented a method of growing straight cucumbers, and the experimentation leading up to
his eventual success left him with a veritable gourd plethora. He used this excess to
create the first anti-dandruff shampoo exclusively for&amp;nbsp;babies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Shortage&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Great Everything Shortage of the late 19th century led to a schism in the industry,&amp;nbsp;however.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These days Pantene is very much &amp;#8220;pro-vitamin&amp;#8221;, in stark contrast to Kellog&amp;#8217;s anti-thiamin stance.
With the increased use of other minerals such as iron and pyrite as shampoo ingredients 
Kellog&amp;#8217;s are coming under increased pressure to reconsider their long disparaged&amp;nbsp;position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A spokesperson of the Flouride Advocacy Group was contacted for a statement,&amp;nbsp;however&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kellog&amp;#8217;s were unavailable for&amp;nbsp;comment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Here&amp;#8217;s The Nescience&amp;nbsp;Bit&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gerbins also warned people against interchanging the two products however.
&amp;#8220;We don&amp;#8217;t yet understand the long-term effects of cleaning your hair with
Crunchy Nut Cornflakes,&amp;#8221; he said, &amp;#8220;so we strongly advise against&amp;nbsp;trying&amp;#8221;.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Telescope Discovers Earth-Like “Sauna World”</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/telescope-discovers-earth-like-sauna-world.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-02T21:38:38+01:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-02:telescope-discovers-earth-like-sauna-world.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;An astronomical telesope in the Canary Islands has discovered the first known health spa on an extra-solar planet, it was reported this&amp;nbsp;week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The announcement is a shot in the arm for beleagured health chiefs, who have emerged as an unexpected casualty of the recent economic&amp;nbsp;downturn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="quo"&gt;&amp;#8216;&lt;/span&gt;As a result of the contraction of the economy in recent months, we have seen a dramatic decline in the number of people being sent to us 
requiring healing&amp;#8217;, said Dr Mehkmi Lesille, of the Kent Primary Care Trust, &amp;#8216;but we have been unable so far to fully capitalise on this. &amp;#8216;We&amp;#8217;ve
closed huge numbers of wards and spend vast amounts of money hiring, training and paying off managers over the last decade in preparation for
this, but we are still falling well short of government targets. What the health corporation in this country really needs now is to offload even 
more patients to lower class facilities, so we can continue our program of utter obliviousness to what Britain&amp;#8217;s ageing population needs. We hope 
that this new discovery may be the&amp;nbsp;key.&amp;#8217;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The discovery of the new health complex was a serendipitous event. Astronomers at the Galileo National Telescope complex in La Palma were scanning 
a sector of the sky known as &amp;#8216;sigma phi beta&amp;#8217;, which is known to contain above-average numbers of rocking-out party planets, but they have discovered
among them a new planet, whose surface is covered entirely by saunas. Its discovery was announced by an international coalition of scientists at a 
press conference in Tenerife, inexplicably hosted by Bob&amp;nbsp;Holness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="quo"&gt;&amp;#8216;&lt;/span&gt;Positive identification was difficult because of noise pollution within the sector,&amp;#8217; said Prof. Harlow Essex, the planet&amp;#8217;s co-discoverer. &amp;#8216;but we 
were able to make use of very recent noise-reducing algorithms and after that it was a piece of&amp;nbsp;piss.&amp;#8217;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The planet is located over 65 light-years from Earth, and scientists are currently investigating the best method of transportation. Due to its 
remote location, traditional space-travel methods like titanium escalators fall just too short of the required range, so researchers are studying the 
idea of simply throwing people there. &amp;#8216;Geoff Capes has already shown an interest in the task,&amp;#8217; said Prof. Essex, &amp;#8216;and we are investigating the 
feasibility of encasing overweight patients in hollow tree trunks to achieve good aerodynamic efficiency.&amp;#8217; Patients would be expected to provide 
their own entertainment for the long journey, likely to last millions of&amp;nbsp;years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for the sauna world itself, early indications suggest that it is likely to match the luxury of the best that Earth has to offer. Analysis has 
shown that the planet has large natural deposits of receptionists, and several thick layers of small, square towels around its equator. Researchers 
also say that they have tentative evidence suggesting the presence of German women, but this has been denied by project leaders. Health workers 
remain generally upbeat about the discovery, however. &amp;#8216;If we can offload all our ill people onto this planet and earn twice as much for the privilege, 
only then will I be happy,&amp;#8217; said Dr&amp;nbsp;Lesille.</summary></entry><entry><title>Police Constable sectioned in Nottingham</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/police-constable-sectioned-in-nottingham.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-02T21:38:26+01:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-02:police-constable-sectioned-in-nottingham.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
A member of the Nottingham Constabulary was today admitted to a local psychiatric ward after a series of reports questioning his state of&amp;nbsp;mind.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
It was revealed that Police Constable Frank Bang was confirmed by doctors
to be suffering from paranoia and delusional behaviour. Concerns were
first raised by senior officers as early as November last year when &lt;span class="caps"&gt;PC&lt;/span&gt; Bang
was showing &amp;#8220;significant signs of paranoia&amp;#8221; and &amp;#8220;repeated delusions of&amp;nbsp;conspiracy.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
According to colleagues, Frank increasingly seemed convinced of the
existence of a conspiracy to control his mind and his behaviour. &amp;#8220;He
kept telling us there as some group of people out there intent on
telling him what to say and think,&amp;#8221; said &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WPC&lt;/span&gt; Kelly Boson, a close colleague.
&amp;#8220;We would try and reason with him, but nothing would convince him&amp;nbsp;otherwise.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The paranoia eventually extended to the public side of Frank&amp;#8217;s work.
&amp;#8220;He came into work one day in November this year claiming that there
was some force intent on stealing Christmas,&amp;#8221; explained Sergeant Chris
Cross in an official press release. &amp;#8220;He attempted to start a campaign
to save it from being stolen and he was unswayed in the belief that
there was a brigade set out to stop him doing&amp;nbsp;so.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Calls for &lt;span class="caps"&gt;PC&lt;/span&gt; Bang to be sectioned finally came when his delusional
actions spread into writing letters fueled by his paranoia to the
publications &lt;em&gt;The Sun&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;The Daily Mail&lt;/em&gt;. He tried
to convince readers that &amp;#8220;They&amp;#8217;re trying to ban&amp;nbsp;Christmas.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;This was the final straw,&amp;#8221; said Sergeant Cross. &amp;#8220;This was a clear case
of a &lt;span class="caps"&gt;PC&lt;/span&gt; gone mad. The decision was taken to limit the damage from
Constable Bang&amp;#8217;s paranoia and see that he gets the help he&amp;nbsp;needs.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
It is believed that &lt;span class="caps"&gt;PC&lt;/span&gt; Bang is to be held for thorough diagnosis and
&amp;#8220;whether he is to be held for longer is unclear at this&amp;nbsp;stage.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry></feed>