<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>WAFTI News</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/feeds/politics.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://news.wafti.org.uk/</id><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><entry><title>Tory Party’s Nanny In Fraudulent Claims Kerfuffle</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/politics/tory-partys-nanny-in-fraudulent-claims-kerfuffle" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:politics/tory-partys-nanny-in-fraudulent-claims-kerfuffle</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
The Conservative Party&amp;#8217;s last remaining woman of toil has been forced to defend her conduct after it emerged that she has been 
accused of financial indiscretions regarding her second&amp;nbsp;home.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tiffany Castro, who is employed by all 193 current Tory MPs, is under accusation of gross misconduct by the Committee on Standards in Public Life 
after reportedly claiming a Social Security allowance while living in her second home after the Tory Party exploded her first&amp;nbsp;home.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="quo"&gt;&amp;#8216;&lt;/span&gt;My family have been living in this English country for eighty-seven years, and I have never known what was going on,&amp;#8217; said Castro today. &amp;#8216;I 
therefore took a job with a Tory &lt;span class="caps"&gt;MP&lt;/span&gt;. My duties at first were light bookkeeping and sometimes undertaking cleaning of places in the house, but I 
didn&amp;#8217;t really understand what was going on. Then he made me employable by his boy friend, another Tory &lt;span class="caps"&gt;MP&lt;/span&gt;. I soon was employed by many Tory&amp;nbsp;MPs.&amp;#8217;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
It has emerged this week that, following an unpublicised internal crackdown on MPs&amp;#8217; expenses claims, the Conservatives have been devising some 
inventive ways to save their brass, and despite her nonplussed demeanour, Castro&amp;#8217;s portfolio of clientele has rocketed. &amp;#8216;I recommended Tiffers like a 
shot. I even go as far as to occasionally call her Spiffers,&amp;#8217; said one grandee. &amp;#8216;I may be a racist, but I know a clean pot when I kick one,&amp;#8217; said 
another. At the peak of her client base, Castro was earning fuck&amp;nbsp;all.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
In July this year, however, Castro&amp;#8217;s council house in Balham, the Gateway to the South, was detonated by political mentalist Joshua Cheese-Pussy in a 
failed attempt to disprove the Big Bang theory and the place was reduced to smouldering rubble. She subsequently did not continue to live there any 
more, naturally. She overtook a new house moored on the Thames near Shadwell whilst continuing to generate hand-stitched monogrammed pants and 
produce vintage ports for her employers. Her cousin Lupejo, a 
professional Mexican, said, &amp;#8216;She really did some great things during 
her, as yet 
unterminated,&amp;nbsp;life.&amp;#8217;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Once the Tory party established via solid evidence and considered, empathetic thought that Castro was taking assistance from the state, they set out 
to discredit her by claiming that she was related to the notorious Communist dictator Nicolai Ceaucescu, before giving up and letting the Committee 
take&amp;nbsp;over.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The outcome of the Committee&amp;#8217;s investigation has yet to be announced but they&amp;#8217;re bound to come up with something or&amp;nbsp;other.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Ordinary Britons feel ‘swamped’ with anti-immigrants</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/politics/ordinary-britons-feel-swamped-with-anti-immigrants" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:politics/ordinary-britons-feel-swamped-with-anti-immigrants</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Large numbers of regular hard-working ordinary families complain that they feel
&amp;#8220;swamped&amp;#8221; and &amp;#8220;overrun&amp;#8221; with anti-immigration policy drives, a study by the
think-tank has&amp;nbsp;shown.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Policy and Legislation Examination Board (&lt;span class="caps"&gt;PLEB&lt;/span&gt;) has revealed in their
research that the majority of hard-working, ordinary, hard-working families feel
that the Britain’s cultural identity is being eroded by an increasing volume of
extreme-right anti-immigration&amp;nbsp;views.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;It’s just getting completely out of hand,&amp;#8221; said Tony Normal, a hard-working
worker from Workington. ‘You go into the town centre, go into Primark, and
everywhere you go there’s just anti-immigrant views. It makes me feel like a
stranger in my own&amp;nbsp;country.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;My daughter was brought up here, she’s being trying to get a job for months but
there’s nothing left,&amp;#8221; said Irene Bog-Standard, from Hull. &amp;#8220;She just wants a
normal job in Conservative policy research like any other girl, but they’ve all
been taken by these anti-immigration types who’ve come in and pushed out the
local people. It’s like an open door, isn’t&amp;nbsp;it?&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A similar picture is being seen in formerly chilled-out and bitchin’ places such
as Surrey in the south of England. &amp;#8220;I used to able to just walk in here for a
marguerita on a Wednesday afternoon and have a good chat about the benefits of
multiculturalism or the best way to make Baba Ganoush&amp;#8221;, says Bill Bowe, standing
outside the Woking Working Mens’ Club. &amp;#8220;But now I can’t even get to the bar.
It’s just full of smelly honkys with pints in their hands banging on about
stockbroking and white power.&amp;#8221; Asked what he thought was the cause of the change
in culture, he responds &amp;#8220;Well, they’re after the benefits aren’t they? They come
here, don’t contribute anything, just spend their time playing golf and living
off the state. And the way they talk, you can’t even understand them can you? I
mean, what the hell is a tax&amp;nbsp;haven?&amp;#8221;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Research undertaken by &lt;span class="caps"&gt;PLEB&lt;/span&gt; does seem to bear out these views. It has recorded a
sharp rise in anti-immigration across Europe, up 16 per cent on last year. The
underlying cause of the spike is unclear, but it is thought to be related to a
rise in grassroots activism in response to a knee-jerk irrational phobia of
brown&amp;nbsp;people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;New activist platforms have sprung up in the last few months, such as the
extreme-right pressure group &lt;span class="caps"&gt;NIMBYBBB&lt;/span&gt;, Not In My Backyard You Black Bastards
(B), formed after Not In My Backyard You Black Bastards (A) was disbanded
following confusion. In Europe, the German organisation Pergoda has recently
seen a surge in support, although when contacted, did not know what its policies&amp;nbsp;are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Professor Dominic Senile, an expert in culture studies at a university, believes
that countering the problem requires long-term commitment to the issue. &amp;#8220;Some
would say that the best solution would be the education of these Nazis and their
normalisation and integration into society. However, we have seen that other
countries have had success with aimless protest, lazy reactionism and complete
and utter ignorance. So before we think about killing, we should try&amp;nbsp;that.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Minister Criticised for “Bashing Bishop”</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/politics/minister-criticised-for-bashing-bishop" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-01-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-01-29:politics/minister-criticised-for-bashing-bishop</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Shock and awe spread throughout the House of Commons yesterday as the Minister
for Mammals, David Spert, was heard making derogatory remarks about a senior
member of the Church of&amp;nbsp;England.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The exact wording is yet to be confirmed by &lt;span class="caps"&gt;HP&lt;/span&gt; sources, but the minister&amp;#8217;s
comments are claimed to have been derisory towards the hat belonging to Bishop
John&amp;nbsp;Thomas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anglican officials are said to be &amp;#8220;deeply offended&amp;#8221; by the comments which they
claim to have asserted their hats to be &amp;#8220;almost as silly&amp;#8221; as their&amp;nbsp;faith.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;We can all take a joke as much as the next religion,&amp;#8221; claims Gregory Peck, a
church spokesman. &amp;#8220;But, we draw the line when the seriousness of our commitment
to dress sense is brought into&amp;nbsp;question.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some have compared the incident to comments made last year by the Home Secretary
over ill-fitting  Jewish footwear. A full apology was immediately demanded by
the Jewish Council, which was then only delivered sarcastically through a string&amp;nbsp;telephone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Church of England is yet to make a formal request for retribution, but
preliminary reports suggest they are likely to be&amp;nbsp;ignored.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;I won&amp;#8217;t be able to keep a straight face if they ask for an apology wearing
those silly hats,&amp;#8221; Mr. Spert is alleged to have said yesterday evening after
half a bottle of&amp;nbsp;Lambrini.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Environment Minister Admits “I Have No Idea What I’m Doing”</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/politics/environment-minister-admits-i-have-no-idea-what-im-doing" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2014-11-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2014-11-23:politics/environment-minister-admits-i-have-no-idea-what-im-doing</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;At a shiny press conference this morning, Vera O&amp;#8217;Rally-Spectacular, Minister for
the Environment, confessed that she had no clue as to how to  perform her role&amp;nbsp;effectively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She went on to admit she&amp;#8217;s not even sure how she got the job nor why she&amp;#8217;s been
able to stay in it for so long. A stunned and damp audience of  rampant
journalists immediately pounced on her, verbally. She was forced to admit that
she was given the job because she had been the only candidate  who did not get
lost on the way to the&amp;nbsp;interview.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;I was a complete failure at almost everything,&amp;#8221; she observed. Her former
headmaster, now her private secretary, agreed. &amp;#8220;Even on the journey here  today,
I tripped over seven times, and lost my housekeys twice. Further, these files in
my hand mean nothing to me. They might be important  government white papers for
all I&amp;nbsp;know.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This revelation has come about during recent criticism of the government&amp;#8217;s
attitude towards environmental issues. Pressure group Stupid Planes said &amp;#8220;We
have always maintained that this government thinks that the environment is
silly. This announcement today only provides further proof that  they have been
really naughty.&amp;#8221; Ms O&amp;#8217;Rally-Spectacular admitted herself that she was not
environmentally aware, having thought it was a  brand of cough medicine. When
asked about her hand in the decision to expand Heathrow Airport, the minister
simply responded, &amp;#8220;well, all those people  from the plane companies were awfully
nice. I didn&amp;#8217;t want to make them&amp;nbsp;sad.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The shadow Environment spokesman, Mr Frogsworth, remained adamant. &amp;#8216;This is
merely yet another blunder by this Labour government. I have  personally seen Ms
O&amp;#8217;Rally-Spectacular&amp;#8217;s school exam results, and she completely failed O-Level
Latin. I assure you that no Tory minister is  lacking in such a fundamental
qualification. Our Environment minister scored brilliantly on all the Classical
languages. He is, unlike most Labour  ministers, a brilliant academic, having
once heard Rachmaninoff&amp;#8217;s piano&amp;nbsp;concertos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Labour has yet to make an official announcement on the issue as Ms
O&amp;#8217;Rally-Spectacular has lost the keys to the Government and forgotten the 
password to the&amp;nbsp;computer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ms O&amp;#8217;Rally-Spectacular refuted suggestions that she was a moron, saying &amp;#8220;I have
voted Church of England all my&amp;nbsp;life.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Darling Budget Scuppers Plans to Run Cars on Cider</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/politics/darling-budget-scuppers-plans-to-run-cars-on-cider" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2010-03-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2010-03-24:politics/darling-budget-scuppers-plans-to-run-cars-on-cider</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The rising practice of circumventing &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UK&lt;/span&gt; fuel duty by converting vehicles to run
on cider has come under attack from Chancellor Alistair Darling in his final
Budget before the&amp;nbsp;election.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An increase of 10% above inflation has been announced for the duty on ciders
this&amp;nbsp;year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the last 12 months, several rural cider makers have supplemented their
incomes by selling off surplus amounts of their stronger products as an
alternative to&amp;nbsp;petrol.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Discovery was first made by Matthew Bramley during a gala in his home town
of Knobbed Russet, Sussex. He was notably not fond of green apples, but found
the red delicious, so would make cider from them. On first tasting of a new
batch, his wife Katy remarked that it tasted like&amp;nbsp;petrol.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The fruitful scheme requires some conversion work to be carried out on the core
of the car&amp;#8217;s engine, but a cider-powered family car saves its owner an average
of £20bn a year &amp;#8212; up to 50% of the average household&amp;#8217;s total credit&amp;nbsp;debt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, the latest measures laid out in the Darling Budget seek to close what
the Chancellor refers to as a &amp;#8220;loophole&amp;#8221; to avoid the tax on&amp;nbsp;petroleum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;If we allow people to use alternative materials as fuel, then we will lose
millions to fuel duty not paid,&amp;#8221; &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; assumes he&amp;nbsp;said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those most affected are companies based entirely on cider-fueled transporation,
such as Braeburn Buses &amp;#8212; a business based in Bedford, bringing biofuel benefits
to Bedfordshire-bound&amp;nbsp;beings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;It&amp;#8217;s daylight roggery,&amp;#8221; fumes Managing Director, John Yak, using the letter &amp;#8216;g&amp;#8217;
where he has run out of &amp;#8216;b&amp;#8217;s due to using up all of his in the company slogan.
&amp;#8220;I can&amp;#8217;t gelieve those gastards are trying to gleed more money out of us like
this. I don&amp;#8217;t like this one&amp;nbsp;git.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The public awaits a response from David Cameron on the report, which many
experts are predicting to be&amp;nbsp;&amp;#8220;untelligible&amp;#8221;.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Shadow Minister: Government has “eaten all the pies”</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/politics/shadow-minister-government-has-eaten-all-the-pies" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2010-02-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2010-02-05:politics/shadow-minister-government-has-eaten-all-the-pies</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Parliament yesterday erupted into chaos after a member of the shadow cabinet
accused the current Government of having eaten &amp;#8220;all the&amp;nbsp;pies&amp;#8221;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Such claims came from the right honourable David Mouse, &lt;span class="caps"&gt;MP&lt;/span&gt; for Taunton&amp;#8217;s cider
farms, in the light of recent controversy over the number of pies MPs have been&amp;nbsp;eating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Traditionally, every member of the house would be entitled to a pie every lunch
from the Westminster canteen, but documents leaked under the Freedom From
Information Act 2004 have shown that most MPs are claiming at least two&amp;nbsp;pies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;It makes a mockery of the whole system,&amp;#8221; claims Martin Mocherie, founder of the
&amp;#8220;Fewer pies, fewer lies&amp;#8221; campaign, a frugality and honesty advocacy&amp;nbsp;group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;At a time when pie stocks are at their lowest, these politicians are claiming
more pies than they&amp;nbsp;need.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The system was originally set up in 1968 when the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UK&lt;/span&gt; elected its first Houses of
Parliament representative from Melton Mowbray. It was voted that members of
parliament travelling to London from regions where pie consumption was normally
higher could claim more than the one statutory pie allowance, which benefitted
those coming from the far North and the West Country, as well as the larger
members from the Isle of&amp;nbsp;Wight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, there have been many calls over the last two weeks for the system to be
reviewed due to many members claiming a second pie they arguably do not&amp;nbsp;need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steven Kidney, &lt;span class="caps"&gt;MP&lt;/span&gt; for Crawley, defends MPs&amp;#8217; actions, stating that &amp;#8220;many members
travel some considerable distance to reach parliament and can be very hungry as
a&amp;nbsp;result.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;If our politicians are expected both to represent their local constituency and
attend parliament, they need to be able to claim as many pies as they&amp;nbsp;need.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. Mouse, who cannot be named in a normal voice, accuses the current Government
of going &amp;#8220;too far&amp;#8221; and says Britain is in a &amp;#8220;real danger&amp;#8221; of running out of pies
&amp;#8220;very&amp;nbsp;soon&amp;#8221;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;I fear the current Government is going to go down in history as the one that
ate all the pies,&amp;#8221; the minister tells &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; through a&amp;nbsp;straw.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An official response is to be made by the Prime Minister in the house tomorrow
after all the mess has been cleaned&amp;nbsp;up.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Local authorities remove oxygen from town centres</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/politics/local-authorities-remove-oxygen-from-town-centres" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2009-12-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2009-12-13:politics/local-authorities-remove-oxygen-from-town-centres</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Millions of proud Britons all over England, and some parts of Wales, have not
only been disallowed from celebrating Christmas by the government, but are now
being told that they are no longer allowed to respire with oxygen - our national
gas for&amp;nbsp;centuries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new measures were drawn up by a Labour think-tank in order &amp;#8220;not to cause
offence to the other gases now common in our country.&amp;#8221; It was revealed in a
report last year that our country&amp;#8217;s air is now less than 30% oxygen. Unfounded
reports have already come forward saying that Birmingham City Council has
renamed its air &amp;#8220;Diverse Mix of Gases&amp;#8221;, much to the outrage of the newspapers
fabricating these&amp;nbsp;reports.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;What I&amp;#8217;ve read in this morning&amp;#8217;s paper is unacceptable,&amp;#8221; says Norman
Housemartin, the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;BNP&lt;/span&gt; spokesperson for gases. &amp;#8220;This is an oxygen country and if
people don&amp;#8217;t like our gases, they can go back to the country where they came
from.&amp;#8221; When asked to cite the cases that enraged him the most, Mr. Housemartin
says &amp;#8220;I&amp;#8217;ve not seen any real cases of this name change myself, but anecdotally,
I think we have a real issue&amp;nbsp;here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A government spokesman denies any allegations of a proposed &amp;#8220;Anti-oxygenic
Task Force&amp;#8221; that will enter citizen&amp;#8217;s homes and ensure they aren&amp;#8217;t respiring any
oxygen. &amp;#8220;We just don&amp;#8217;t have that capability,&amp;#8221; admits Roger Flatpack, minister
for chemical affairs, &amp;#8220;if it were up to us, we&amp;#8217;d be able to invoke and enforce
bans with the efficiency of Oliver Cromwell himself. I don&amp;#8217;t think any of us
have achieved that, but certainly everyone in parliament aspires to the level of
the greatest Statesman in British&amp;nbsp;history.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;We&amp;#8217;ve seen these reports springing up everywhere that&amp;#8217;s we&amp;#8217;re bringing in
bans on our beloved gas, but the truth is we&amp;#8217;re just not competent enough to
carry through such plans. We did discuss plans to reduce the amount of oxygen in
our public areas to ease tensions from the nitrogen community, but we&amp;#8217;ve found
it near impossible to prevent people respiring as they will. In fact Birmingham
City Council themselves are respiring as much as&amp;nbsp;anyone.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span class="caps"&gt;BNP&lt;/span&gt; yesterday released an official statement citing these reports as
proof that &amp;#8220;The &lt;span class="caps"&gt;PC&lt;/span&gt; brigade have gone mad&amp;#8221; and called for anyone expressing any
form of sensitivity to anyone else to be sectioned under the Mental Health&amp;nbsp;Act.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Economics teaching under scrutiny in US</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/politics/economics-teaching-under-scrutiny-in-us" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2007-02-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2007-02-13:politics/economics-teaching-under-scrutiny-in-us</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Kansas school board came under significant pressure this week over the
content taught in economics lessons in its&amp;nbsp;schools.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Proponents of the so-called &amp;#8220;Intelligent Market&amp;#8221; theory have claimed that
current teaching methods are overly biased towards free market theories by the
likes of Adam&amp;nbsp;Smith.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;We respect work of people like Mr. Smith, but it needs to be understood that
works like &amp;#8216;The Wealth of Nations&amp;#8217; contain &lt;em&gt;theories&lt;/em&gt; and, as such, should not
be taught as if they are the only explanation for our economy,&amp;#8221; &lt;span class="caps"&gt;IM&lt;/span&gt; campaigner
tells &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; today. &amp;#8220;We think we owe it to our children to hear both sides of the&amp;nbsp;debate.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For years now, economics lessons have focused entirely on the idea that our
economy is driven by &amp;#8220;market forces&amp;#8221;; seemingly random decisions by directors
can be beneficial or detrimental to a company, which guides its development.
Free market economists say that pressures from the consumer base kill off
failing companies and help successful ones to&amp;nbsp;survive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Free market economists call this process of natural selection &amp;#8220;competition&amp;#8221;. The
limited resources and finances available nationwide means that every successful
company we see today has evolved from ancestor companies that at some point made
better decisions than the other ancient companies we longer see today. The only
record we have of such extinct companies today is fossilised annual tax returns
which researchers have been unearthing at varying layers of the Inland Revenue&amp;nbsp;archives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, supporters of the &amp;#8220;Intelligent Market&amp;#8221; model in the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;USA&lt;/span&gt; cite laws of
entropy as evidence that the market could not be as chaotic as it is today
through random decisions guided by market&amp;nbsp;forces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;It is clear to us now that such a high level of chaotic mess in our economy
could not have happened without some influence from a higher power,&amp;#8221; say a
controversial report from top researchers at the California Market Science
Institute. &amp;#8220;Such a complex level of disorder could not have been arrived at by
subtle forces alone. Our modern day economic state must surely be the result of
nearly eight years of tariff imposition, deficit spending and generally bad
decisions by a top-level&amp;nbsp;power.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The controversial issue is to be debated at emergency school board meetings
across 17 different states&amp;nbsp;tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry></feed>