<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>WAFTI News</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/feeds/science.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://news.wafti.org.uk/</id><updated>2015-02-02T21:46:10+01:00</updated><entry><title>Virgin birth prompts review of abstinence-only programmes</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/virgin-birth-prompts-review-of-abstinence-only-programmes.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-02T21:46:10+01:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-02:virgin-birth-prompts-review-of-abstinence-only-programmes.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Judean officials have confirmed reports of a pregnant
teenager giving birth today despite new abstinence-only
programmes now entering their second year of&amp;nbsp;running.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sources close to King Herod informed &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; that they
received news this morning that a teenager named Mary has
in fact successfully given birth in the small town of
Bethlehem, Gloucestershire. This birth is controversial
as the Bethlehem district has, for over 18 months now, been
a forerunner in the campaign for teenage abstinence as
a form of birth&amp;nbsp;control.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Judean governmental figures have long cited abstinence
as &amp;#8220;the only form of birth control to be 100% effective&amp;#8221;
and in August 2 B.C., the Herod administration brought in a
Judean-wide campaign to educate teenagers as to its&amp;nbsp;benefits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, protest groups have been claiming since the
programme&amp;#8217;s introduction that it is intrinsically flawed.
&amp;#8220;We&amp;#8217;ve said from the start: this programme is founded on
untruths,&amp;#8221; claims Helen Trout, head of Leave Your Hat On, a
pro-condom pressure group, &amp;#8220;The simple fact is that
if we are to promote real birth control, then we must
be educating our youngsters that they need to be safe whatever
decisions they choose to make. This incident is a kick in
the face to our government&amp;#8217;s ill-advised&amp;nbsp;schemes.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;It&amp;#8217;s a hard issue, certainly and, at a stretch, we could
see teenage sex figures going down, but when it comes down to it
our only shot at stopping this flow is to promote safe
usage of condoms. This incident has brought the issue to a head
and I hope now we see a push in the right&amp;nbsp;direction.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This morning&amp;#8217;s birth has certainly stirred a lot of controversy
and it remains to be seen how the government will move in light
of these revelations. A source close to King Herod informs
&lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt;, &amp;#8220;The King is deeply troubled by the birth of this child.
It is unacceptable that such an anomaly should be allowed to
ruin such a beneficial programme and King Herod has promised
to take whatever action is needed, however&amp;nbsp;drastic.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Prostitutes More Smarter Than Previously Thought</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/prostitutes-more-smarter-than-previously-thought.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-02T21:45:59+01:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-02:prostitutes-more-smarter-than-previously-thought.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;A group of some scientists have revealed that prostitutes have a 
sophisticated grasp of mathematics, including the discovery of concepts 
hitherto unknown to mainstream&amp;nbsp;research.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Research carried out by psychoscientists at Brixton University has 
demonstrated that prostitutes only ever congregate on street corners in 
prime numbers. Prior to this, it had long been assumed that prostitutes 
employed basic dynamic processes as an evolutionary consequence of 
dealing with drunken customers. Prof. Abject Poverty of the University&amp;#8217;s 
department said &amp;#8216;Hookers were always thought to have evolved to tout for 
business according to the logistic equation of population growth, and 
were therefore limited by the natural resources that a stretch of 
pavement could provide. However, these results suggest that some new, 
hidden, factors could be determining their&amp;nbsp;distribution&amp;#8217;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prof. Poverty and his colleagues have been able to show that the 
random walk process, when applied to slags, is intrinsically flawed, as 
they are subject to a previously unknown factor termed &amp;#8216;insubordinate 
dependence&amp;#8217;. This effect causes the women to be financially attracted 
towards supplies of narcotics, which distorts the mathematical things of 
the random walk theory. Prof. Poverty&amp;#8217;s team has observed that a 
superposition of prostitutes&amp;#8217; attractors bears similarities to the 
distribution of prime numbers, and may eventually lead to a more 
thorough understanding of non-integer-dimensional surfaces. 
&lt;p&gt;The results have aroused controversy in the scientific community, 
however. Dr Brian Awsh of &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UCL&lt;/span&gt; said &amp;#8216;the whole thrust of their argument 
is likely wrong. Their sample size of 412 prostitutes in the Milton Road 
area of Cambridge is far too small to be representative of the 
neighbourhood as a whole&amp;#8217;, while his colleague Dr James Ypres added 
&amp;#8216;Look at my face.&amp;#8217; However, Laris Hilson, of the Collectors&amp;#8217; Guild of 
Prostitutes, said &amp;#8216;This research may yield some interesting insights for 
the analysts of the sex industry. The idea that prostitutes could 
influence the proof of the Riemann hypothesis is not a new one, but a 
public vindication of their relevance in this field is long&amp;nbsp;overdue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is some way to go before the ladies of the night are able to 
provide any relevant research data. However, the identification of two 
previously unrelated branches of science has many researchers excited. 
&amp;#8216;Who knows what this could lead to?&amp;#8217; asked Prof. Poverty, questioningly. 
&amp;#8216;There is new research being undertaken on infinite series of 
prostitutes that should hopefully be able to provide further insight 
into what, I think, is a very attractive young area.&amp;#8217;&lt;P&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>“Things not what they used to be,” says study</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/things-not-what-they-used-to-be-says-study.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-02T21:45:47+01:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-02:things-not-what-they-used-to-be-says-study.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
A study recently commissioned by the British Legion has confirmed that several aspects of modern culture such as fashion, values and mainstream music have changed over the last six&amp;nbsp;decades.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Several claims have been made by aged pressure
groups for a number of years, but this is the
first time a comprehensive paper has been written
up with a notable amount of&amp;nbsp;rigour.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Conclusions drawn by the report include
indications that young
girls wear notably less clothing in public
situations as they did pre-1960 &amp;#8212; an act frequently deemed
unacceptably deplorable by elderly interest&amp;nbsp;organisations.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Other findings included a detailed confirmation that
music isn&amp;#8217;t the same as that being performed
between 1950 and&amp;nbsp;1959.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;They really knew how to sing a proper song back then;
music today is just too loud,&amp;#8221; concludes the first
chapter of the two chapter dossier, which sampled
2,500 music recordings from the last sixty years for
a thorough aural&amp;nbsp;examination.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;The youth of today don&amp;#8217;t know they&amp;#8217;re born,&amp;#8221; opens
the second and final chapter. Later, it reveals,
&amp;#8220;many years ago, one would be able to acquire
goods and services at lower&amp;nbsp;prices.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Perhaps the most surprising revelation to some
was the uncovering of how poor current
television programming is compared to how it has
been in that&amp;nbsp;past.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;Everything these days is all noise, sex and violence,&amp;#8221;
a concerned Patrice Loganberry, 68, tells &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; over
tea and biscuits. &amp;#8220;I spend 8 hours of each day watching
the telly and none of it is worth watching. Except
that Bruce Forsyth; he&amp;#8217;s&amp;nbsp;lovely.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
A parliamenary response to the report is still pending.
James Mandelbrot, the cabinet minister for nostalgia,
was no longer available to comment like he used&amp;nbsp;to.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Anniversary of Moon Landing Reignites Conspiracy Claims</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/anniversary-of-moon-landing-reignites-conspiracy-claims.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-02T21:45:28+01:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-02:anniversary-of-moon-landing-reignites-conspiracy-claims.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
Previously waning lunacy was in full view this month as the 40th anniversary of the Apollo 11 mission sparked up fresh controversy over whether or not the moon was&amp;nbsp;faked.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
On July 20th, 1969, the United States landed the first
white, male human beings on the surface of the Earth&amp;#8217;s
moon with an estimated 1 billion eyes witnessing the
historic moment. Despite these 500 million observers,
many conspiracy theorists maintain the accusation that
the entire moon is a hoax concocted by &lt;span class="caps"&gt;NASA&lt;/span&gt;, the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;US&lt;/span&gt;
Government and the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;TUC&lt;/span&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;There is absolutely no way for the moon to be possible,
let alone for a man to walk on it,&amp;#8221; scoffs Geoffrey Van Allen,
founder of Lunar Sceptics, a moon-denying interest&amp;nbsp;group.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;We have analysed 1000s of photographs taken of the moon
and every single one shows signs of tampering. The famous
shot of Buzz Aldrin taken on its surface could easily
have been taken in any Asda car park and touched up in a&amp;nbsp;studio.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Critics of the hoax claims point to the continuing
visibility of our lunar compadre as seen through
several devices such as telescopes, binoculars or&amp;nbsp;eyes.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;Look; it&amp;#8217;s right there,&amp;#8221; a scientist&amp;nbsp;explains.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The &amp;#8220;people&amp;#8221; of the conspiracy theory publication,
&amp;#8220;Moon? Yeah, right&amp;#8230;&amp;#8221; are still not convinced
by this salient&amp;nbsp;evidence.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;We have testimonies from several Hollywood experts
that expose a secret project experimenting with sky
projection technology capable of maintaining something
such as a picture of a moon in our skies perpetually.
We have hard evidence this project dates back years
before the moon itself,&amp;#8221; explains Chief Editor
Roy O&amp;#8217;Rovers in a drawn-out game of&amp;nbsp;charades.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Other attempts to debunk the claims point to evidence
from tidal patterns across the globe &amp;#8212; now known
by most outside of the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;USA&lt;/span&gt; to be due to the
gravitational effect of the moon and not&amp;nbsp;Poseidon.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;It&amp;#8217;s very clear that the wave machines used in
novelty swimming baths today were the side product
of the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;NASA&lt;/span&gt; tide project,&amp;#8221; continued Mr. O&amp;#8217; Rovers
fervently. &amp;#8220;We have detected the main points at
which &lt;span class="caps"&gt;NASA&lt;/span&gt; has stationed wave generators to force
a tidal effect &amp;#8212; all part of an elaborate scheme
to act as if there were a moon pulling on the&amp;nbsp;seas.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Most astronomers were too busy with real work to
respond to these claims, but a group of &lt;span class="caps"&gt;GCSE&lt;/span&gt;
Science students were able to tell &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; they
consider moon hoax proponents to be &amp;#8220;a bunch
of saddos[sic].&amp;#8221; Their parents were unavailable to&amp;nbsp;comment.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Were Vikings the first on the moon?</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/were-vikings-the-first-on-the-moon.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-02T21:45:14+01:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-02:were-vikings-the-first-on-the-moon.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
The authenticity of 15th century Viking map clearly depicting the moon five centuries before Neil Armstrong&amp;#8217;s arrival has been confirmed by a great&amp;nbsp;Dane.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The map has been terribly controversial since its discovery
in 1988, at which time it was dismissed as Roman Catholic
tomfoolery intended to discredit Christopher Columbus during
an intellectual property dispute. Lars Supper, grand
commissioner of the Danish Map School, claims that there
is no sign of&amp;nbsp;forgery.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;We have run extensive tests between games of Cluedo
and not once have we seen evidence this was Catholic
monkeyshines,&amp;#8221; Prof. Supper tells &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; via &lt;span class="caps"&gt;SMS&lt;/span&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The map shows Europe, Greenland and a large, round
entity labelled &amp;#8220;Møøn&amp;#8221;. The drawing is poor, but
historians are quick to remind that art teachers
were not invented until the Great Depression in the
1930s. Also, the distance between Greenland
and what we now know today as the Moon,
 is totally inaccurate compared to what we can
determine by modern &lt;span class="caps"&gt;GPS&lt;/span&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The settlement of the area has now been linked to the
Icelandic sagas of Norsemen under Leif &amp;#8220;Sony&amp;#8221; Eriksson
from around 1000 &lt;span class="caps"&gt;CE&lt;/span&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Despite these shortcomings, Prof. Supper maintains the map
is clear evidence the vikings were the first to send
a ship to the moon. However, many killjoy scientists
remain&amp;nbsp;sceptics.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Opponents have alledged that the ink used on the map
contains a substance known as mayonase titanium bromide,
which today is only used in felt-tip pens &amp;#8212; something
not invented until the 16th century. This has now
been disproved in light of recent discoveries
showing that Michaelangelo had used felt tips
on the ceiling of the Sistine&amp;nbsp;Chapel.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;It&amp;#8217;s clearly silly; everybody knows Christopher Columbus
was the first to discover America,&amp;#8221; hints Ronald Watermelon,
leading historian and director of Columbus Tours. &amp;#8220;Anything
to the contrary is just pissing in the&amp;nbsp;wind.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
A British archeologist first discovered the map hanging
from a telegraph pole in Basingstoke, Nottinghamshire in 1957.
It was then traded to the director of the British Museum
in 1965 for a David Beckham &amp;#8220;shiny&amp;#8221; during a lunch&amp;nbsp;break.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
There the map has remained until late 2008, when it was
released for study. Professor Lars Supper will present
his findings during the Coronation Street advert
break next&amp;nbsp;week.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>“Iced Rain” Baffles Scientists</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/iced-rain-baffles-scientists.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-02T21:44:57+01:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-02:iced-rain-baffles-scientists.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
Scientists in the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UK&lt;/span&gt; are still unable to explain the unusual shift in weather experienced throughout much of the country over the last&amp;nbsp;week.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The British Isles has always been home to much
wetness, but its residents were faced over the last seven days
with a rather
unusual difference. Since Monday last week, there
were several reports of a phenomon of white, icy
particles falling from the&amp;nbsp;sky.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;It&amp;#8217;s almost as if the rain froze before falling
to Earth,&amp;#8221; suggests Patrick Thistle, head of Water
Sciences at Nottingham Trent&amp;nbsp;University.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;There&amp;#8217;s no good explanation at this early stage,
but we&amp;#8217;ve been able to collect samples and are
running several tests. We hope to be able to
describe the origin of this phenonenom&amp;nbsp;soon.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Many of the country&amp;#8217;s roads and train lines have
been closed off as Gordon Brown declared a state
of emergency on Thursday. Many commuters complained
of unusual behaviour from their&amp;nbsp;cars.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;This stuff is really bizarre,&amp;#8221; reports Sid Cup from
Letchworth. &amp;#8220;I was doing my usual commute to London
and my car was sliding all over the road. My wife
tried to blame it on the white russians I had with
my cereal, but I know this stuff was involved&amp;nbsp;somehow.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Mary Snowflake, chairperson of the Milton Keynes council
informs she had to shut down the whole mass transit
system. &amp;#8220;We started getting reports of some bizarre,
white substance falling from the sky that was affecting
local drivers&amp;#8217; ability, so we decided to take no
risks. At a time where nobody should be out in their cars,
the most sensible thing to do is to shut down all&amp;nbsp;buses.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;All that is known so far is the substance appears to be
similar to or composed of ice, perhaps alike the ice
content of a&amp;nbsp;snowcone.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Many Milton Keynes residents have alikened the precipitate
to the ground covering inside the local indoor ski slope,
known as the &amp;#8220;&lt;span class="caps"&gt;SNO&lt;/span&gt;!zone&amp;#8221;. However, management
denies any&amp;nbsp;connection.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
What is known is that such a phenomenon has never been observed
in the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UK&lt;/span&gt; before. The Met Office has confirmed that its records
show much cold rain, but never anything comparable
to recent&amp;nbsp;events.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The government has sent a fact-finding group abroad to the
Bahamas to hope to acquire some scientific findings from
our international&amp;nbsp;partners.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Monkeys excel at grammar</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/monkeys-excel-at-grammar.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-02T21:44:44+01:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-02:monkeys-excel-at-grammar.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
Studies on monkeys have shown their grasp of grammar to outshine that of the average 14-16 year&amp;nbsp;old.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The journal Monkey Tales has today published
research in which cotton-top tamarins were
able to spot incorrect syntax and word usage
far better than the average &lt;span class="caps"&gt;GCSE&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;student.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
They familiarised the monkeys with introductary
reading to the works of Roald Dahl, Charles Dickens
and Jeffrey Archer as well as conversational
classes, then recorded their reaction to
Internet forums, Facebook profiles and a sample
of several Twitter&amp;nbsp;accounts.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
In the experiment, they were shown so-called
&amp;#8220;status updates&amp;#8221; as well as comment posts across
several websites. The aim was to investigate
the ability to spot flagrant misuse of words
as well as incorrect&amp;nbsp;spellings.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The monkeys were trained to indicate what
they deemed an abuse of the English language in mild
cases with a gesture of placing their palm over their
faces; larger mistakes were indicated with head-desk&amp;nbsp;interaction.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The same experiment was repeated with a sample of
British &lt;span class="caps"&gt;GCSE&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;students.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The results indicated that monkeys were 20% more
likely to recognise cases of &amp;#8220;of&amp;#8221; being misused
as a verb, 15% more likely to spot the incorrect
use of homophones such as &amp;#8220;there&amp;#8221; and &amp;#8220;their&amp;#8221; and
a staggering 89% more likely to know when
an apostrophe should and should not be&amp;nbsp;used.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;Simple temporal ordering is shared with non-human animals,&amp;#8221;
the lead researcher tells &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; News while drying his hair.
&amp;#8220;This means we&amp;#8217;d expect basic levels of language skill
to be achievable even to&amp;nbsp;monkeys.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;However, it seems such simple aspects escape the
generation now entering the workplace. It&amp;#8217;s a prospect
that is certainly cause for concern. If their language
skills are in fact lower than those of other primates,
then we could see them losing out on jobs to&amp;nbsp;them.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The government has yet to comment on pressure to
help protect British, human workers from losing
out to more competent immigrants from the same
biological&amp;nbsp;order.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;We need the government to put a stop to these monkey&amp;#8217;s
coming into our country and taking our jobs just
because they are willing to work for peanut&amp;#8217;s,&amp;#8221; rants
a red-faced member of the British Numpty Party on
a group called &amp;#8220;&lt;span class="caps"&gt;BRITTISH&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="caps"&gt;JOB&lt;/span&gt;&amp;#8217;S &lt;span class="caps"&gt;NOW&lt;/span&gt;!!!&amp;#8221; on social
networking site Facebook. &amp;#8220;Saying
their more qualified or more smarter is just &lt;span class="caps"&gt;PC&lt;/span&gt; gone&amp;nbsp;mad.&amp;#8221;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The European Union is assembling a panel to investigate
the research and its significance in light of recent
calls to expand the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;EU&lt;/span&gt; borders into the animal&amp;nbsp;kingdom.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Field Geologist Considers Lunch</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/field-geologist-considers-lunch.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-02T21:44:30+01:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-02:field-geologist-considers-lunch.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
Experienced geologist Dr Petro Logical, 46, revealed yesterday to his field colleagues that he was thinking about putting down his hammer and having 
some&amp;nbsp;lunch. 
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Dr Logical, based in Wapping, was in Canada at the time of the incident, investigating speciments of Nectocaris in part of the Burgess Shale 
Formation in British Columbia. At approximately 12.30pm, whilst he was separated from the rest of his party and just concluding a detailed study of a 
particularly well-preserved fossil of Nectocaris which he had been working on for several days, he shocked colleagues and co-workers by announcing 
that he was going to down tools and eat some&amp;nbsp;lunch.  
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The news sent longitudinal shock waves through the field party. &amp;#8216;In the 27 years that I have known Petro, he has never, to my knowledge, eaten food,&amp;#8217; 
said a colleague  working in the area, &amp;#8216;before 1pm.&amp;#8217; Others present were similarly amazed. &amp;#8216;I&amp;#8217;ve never heard of anything like this ever happening 
before,&amp;#8217; said another worker, understood to a be one of Dr Logical&amp;#8217;s research students. &amp;#8216;Some people are saying that he simply finished his morning&amp;#8217;s 
work earlier than usual, and decided to have an early lunch, but I just cannot accept&amp;nbsp;that&amp;#8217;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Breakfast at normal&amp;nbsp;time&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
It is understood that, prior to yesterday&amp;#8217;s incident, Dr Logical was a man of regular habit, having got out of bed nearly every day in the last 40 
years. The religiousness of his daily life was corroborated by another of his colleagues, Prof Adolf Hitlerino. &amp;#8216;Right from when I first knew him, 
Petro was never a man,&amp;#8217; said Prof Hitlerino, &amp;#8216;to do things spontaneously. We once worked together in Pompeii in 1978, and I can clearly remember that 
he always ate breakfast just after he got up. He never ate dinner after he had gone to bed, and his showers were always taken before he got to the 
office. He was just that sort of&amp;nbsp;guy.&amp;#8217;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; 
Much of the uproar surrounding the Doctor&amp;#8217;s early lunch stems from his reputation as an extremely dedicated worker. &amp;#8216;He has only two loves: geology 
and his medical experimentation,&amp;#8217; said a former aquaintance, who is unable to be named to due to a mistake. &amp;#8216;I can tell you that he spends all of his 
free time conducting medical tests on his favourite subject, who he married several years ago. If anything, that is his passion, rather than geology. 
It takes up all his time, bombarding her with gamma rays, spiking her with sticks, dosing her up with experimental drugs. He has no time for 
relationships; he&amp;#8217;s married to his&amp;nbsp;wife.&amp;#8217;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Sheer&amp;nbsp;terror&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Many of Dr Logical&amp;#8217;s friends and colleagues are too terrified to speculate as to what time he will take his lunch break tomorrow. &amp;#8216;It&amp;#8217;s just not 
something that I feel I can comprehend at this point in time,&amp;#8217; said Prof Hitlerino. &amp;#8216;The enormity of yesterday&amp;#8217;s events haven&amp;#8217;t quite sunk in yet. We 
are all hoping and praying that he won&amp;#8217;t bring out his lunchbox and thermos before at least five past one tomorrow. But I&amp;#8217;m just not confident. If he 
eats lunch early again, may God have mercy on us&amp;nbsp;all.&amp;#8217;
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Police Chief Calls For Abolition Of The Moon</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/police-chief-calls-for-abolition-of-the-moon.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-02T21:44:18+01:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-02:police-chief-calls-for-abolition-of-the-moon.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
The Metropolitan Police today called for the Moon to be removed from existence after numerous working problems were experienced by their&amp;nbsp;forces.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Coleman Balls, the Deputy Assistant Commissioner, called on
theorists to reconsider the position and effectiveness of the Moon,
as it was proving a threat to effective policing in the
London&amp;nbsp;area.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Mr Balls explained, &amp;#8216;The Moon is proving particularly
counterproductive to the safe policing of the capital&amp;#8217;s
streets, especially in conjunction with the Theory of
Special Relativity. As it is obvious that this theory
has withstood experimental test and cannot be reworked,
it has to be that the Moon must&amp;nbsp;go.&amp;#8217;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Asked by our correspondent to explain his position,
Commissioner Balls continued &amp;#8216;Einstein&amp;#8217;s theory
postulates that photons of light have momentum,
and that some of this momentum is imparted to an
object when they interact with it. At night, the
Moon pours photons down onto the criminals on the
streets, supplying them with extra momentum and
giving them the ability to outrun our dedicated
team of patrol officers.&amp;#8217; When asked to comment 
on why his officers did not feel the same benefits
of this effect as the criminals, he pointed out that
&amp;#8216;criminals are usually black. I mean, wear black.
Dark substances act as black bodies and absorb more
radiation, and therefore the effect is more pronounced
on these&amp;nbsp;scoundrels.&amp;#8217;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The Commissioner&amp;#8217;s idea would have important ramifications
if it was accepted by scientists. Without the Moon&amp;#8217;s
presence, the tides would fail, destroying sea life,
and the seasons would cease to meaningfully exist, and
the Earth may possibly spiral in towards the Sun,
causing certain death for all&amp;nbsp;Londoners.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The Home Office, when contacted, could not return our
calls. However, Commissioner Balls&amp;#8217; idea is sure to be
discussed at next week&amp;#8217;s Meeting of Scientists in&amp;nbsp;Cheshire.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry></feed>