<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>WAFTI News</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/feeds/technology.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://news.wafti.org.uk/</id><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><entry><title>Google Announces Web-Based Pie and Mash</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/technology/google-announces-web-based-pie-and-mash" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:technology/google-announces-web-based-pie-and-mash</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
Search engine giant Google has achieved another technological feat by unveiling the world&amp;#8217;s first online pie and mash&amp;nbsp;shop.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The announcement is being seen by analysts as another attempt by the software behemoth to cash in on gaps left open by its rivals, including 
Microsoft and Apple, in the new and emerging market of meat and vegetables. The product was revealed this morning in the canteen at the firm&amp;#8217;s 
headquarters in Mountain View, California, in Google&amp;#8217;s inimitably quirky style, with invited journalists and software executives handed pork pies in 
the shape of pork pie-shaped mounds of mashed&amp;nbsp;potato.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The new venture is intended to exploit the vegetable-loving habits of teenage children, which until now have been ignored by most major greengrocers 
and software corporations. Google&amp;#8217;s Director of Thinking, Jono Pfthan, said &amp;#8216;This announcement comes in response to a growing trend in America of 
people beginning to adore pies and mash. It follows the unveiling of our new operating system, Chrome, developed in response to a strong demand for 
operating systems from people who own PCs.&amp;#8217; &amp;#8216;We always aim to score&amp;#8217;, he added&amp;nbsp;mysteriously.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Google&amp;#8217;s new Cockney-esque website is designed to offer the authentic experience of East End cuisine from the convenience of your own cybercafe. The 
site currently offers around 17,000 varieties of pie, although Google have stated their intention to ramp up the product count going foward. The page 
also offers various varied varieties of vegetable side dishes, including bean sprouts, aubergines, avocados, peas, lentils, garlic bread,
brocolli, squash, samphire, spinach, peppers, mushrooms, kale, chinese cabbage, yams, split peas, zucchini, rutabaga, celery, lima beans, water 
chestnuts, rhubarb, monorail onions, lemongrass, chard, Mexican sour gherkins, winged beans, Malabar gourds, Davidson&amp;#8217;s radish, epicurian shallotts, 
okra and even potatoes. Carrots are also projected to be offered at a later date, subject to logistical&amp;nbsp;considerations. 
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The site is not yet fully developed, and is currently still in beta-carotene, but plans exist to introduce new techniques to channel foodstuffs 
directly to users&amp;#8217; PCs via VoIP (vegetables over &lt;span class="caps"&gt;IP&lt;/span&gt;). Google announced it has developed a test system which allows jellied eels to be hurled across a 
river, but have not released any further details. The company expects demands for its pie and mash products to be high, particularly from areas of 
the world traditionally associated with&amp;nbsp;food. 
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Microsoft have stated that they have no plans to introduce a rival to Google&amp;#8217;s latest offering, stating through a spokesdude that they were 
concentrating on maintaining their fiefdom in other, probably more evil, ways. Apple told &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; that vegetables are the company&amp;#8217;s natural enemy, and 
therefore they were going to run away and hide and invent a talking mattress in response. The Linux empire could not comment as it had gone to the&amp;nbsp;pub.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Virgin Broadband Customer Loads Google</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/technology/virgin-broadband-customer-loads-google" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T00:34:27+00:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-03:technology/virgin-broadband-customer-loads-google</id><summary type="html">&lt;P&gt;An ecstatic customer of a well-known internet service provider 
announced today to a packed press conference that Google had finally&amp;nbsp;loaded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The breakthrough, occuring at 01.30 this morning, could herald a new era for consumers, meaning they may soon be able to occasionally access 
basic websites in the very small hours. &amp;#8216;This could quite literally change my life, and many others&amp;#8217;, the mystery customer was heard to say between the
elbows of photographers. &amp;#8216;I confidently predict that I may now be able to conduct a Google search query by the middle of next&amp;nbsp;year.&amp;#8217;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This incident marks the first time that a consumer of what broadband companies term a &amp;#8216;service&amp;#8217; has been able to achieve a full page load without 
inducing severe foot-based damage to their machine, let alone the downloading of any material. In July 2008, a user in Pitlochrie reported the successful 
downloading of a small string of text, but was widely criticised for concocting the story for publicity&amp;nbsp;reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is understood that the customer, who did not want to be named, and the internet service provider in question, which could not bear to be named, 
have been affiliated which each other for several years. The affiliation has been described by acquaintances of the customer as a 
&amp;#8216;relationship of extreme inconvenience&amp;#8217;. Sources have informed &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; that there has been almost no contact between the two, the company 
seemingly having preferred to maintain a somewhat elusive presence. It is said to have employed various changes of identity in the last 
few years in order to avoid being tracked with swords. However, it is reported that the company has been less than thorough in covering its tracks. 
Observers point to the fact that, upon its last renaming, the company initiated a multi-million pound publicity campaign announcing the 
rebranding. &amp;#8216;If this company existed in compact physical form,&amp;#8217; said the customer, &amp;#8216;then I would throw it into a&amp;nbsp;pond.&amp;#8217;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;P&gt;The specific cause of the unnamed customer&amp;#8217;s dissatisfaction was evident, once identified. &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; has managed to track down a packet of 
the customer&amp;#8217;s internet traffic, after it was remanded for not following the standard internet protocol. The packet was observed acting irrationally at an 
optical-elecrical junction, shortly before it was intercepted by an entity acting for the company who would identify herself only as Janet. The 
suspect packet was evidently frustrated at being detained, and was observed quoting its quantum numbers forcibly several times. 
According to nearby datapackets employed by &lt;span class="caps"&gt;BT&lt;/span&gt;, the packet was initially cooperative, but after being refused a handshake several times was bundled 
violently to the floor and only managed to escape due to an unexpected quantum tunnelling&amp;nbsp;event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; managed to capture covert film footage of the confrontation, which was today described by experts as &amp;#8216;of little help.&amp;#8217; &amp;#8216;Our analysis 
suggests that &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt;&amp;#8217;s actions in viewing the incident resulted in alteration of the measurements recorded by the detecting equipment, which had the 
effect of making the situation appear much worse than it would otherwise have been,&amp;#8217; said an expert. However, other experts disgreed. &amp;#8216;It may be that 
&lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt;&amp;#8217;s timely intervention has prevented a catastrophe,&amp;#8217; claims one. &amp;#8216;Had this packet successfully reached its destination earlier in the 
evening, it could have spawned an influx of literally tens of this &lt;span class="caps"&gt;ISP&lt;/span&gt;&amp;#8217;s customers being able to access the internet, severely overloading the 
company&amp;#8217;s infrastructure and causing the internet to burn&amp;nbsp;down.&amp;#8217;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There has since been no comment or attempt at a pithy one-liner supplied by the company responsible. Sources quoting the president of the company 
referring to customers as &amp;#8216;one hundred percent cuboidal arsepiping&amp;#8217; have since been nearly all proven drunk or were confused by his beard. The story 
has not, in fact, been taken up by the Daily Mail, which has since not twisted the issue into a polemic piece on the state of the housing market 
or given it a Nazi-sympathetic twist. The &lt;span class="caps"&gt;ISP&lt;/span&gt; itself has not been contacted by &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt;, as they were considered too incompetent to respond with a 
statement that was not&amp;nbsp;patronising.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;We apologise for this broadband story being erroneously listed under &amp;#8216;Technology&amp;#8217;. This oversight will be corrected once our new 
section, &amp;#8216;Wagon Wheels: The Internet Of The 18th Century&amp;#8217;, is&amp;nbsp;complete.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry></feed>