<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>WAFTI News</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/feeds/uk.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://news.wafti.org.uk/</id><updated>2015-02-01T00:00:00+01:00</updated><entry><title>Britain’s worst criminal brought to justice</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/britains-worst-criminal-brought-to-justice.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-01T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2015-02-01:britains-worst-criminal-brought-to-justice.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Thames Valley Police put yet another feather in its cap after arresting a woman accused of 50 separate crimes shortly after brunch this&amp;nbsp;morning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anne Sheep, from Milton Keynes, was first reported to have been in charge of caring for her child without the appropriate Childcare Licence. Ofsted says looking after children this way without being registered and licenced contravenes the Nanny Act as the care lasted for longer than two hours and constituted receiving &amp;#8220;a&amp;nbsp;reward&amp;#8221;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;A neighbour reported Ms. Sheep saying she found raising her son &amp;#8216;very rewarding&amp;#8217; so this is in clear violation of the measures we put in place to protect children from their mothers,&amp;#8221; an Ofsted inspector wrote on his Myspace&amp;nbsp;blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Civil Liberties campaigners and other whingers were said to be outraged at the incident and have responded in full force by drawing Hitler moustaches on photographs of the Minister for Children, Roger&amp;nbsp;Duck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Livid&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In an interview over Facebook chat, Ms. Sheep told &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt;: &amp;#8220;When the inspector called, the first thing she did was wipe her feet. Then she distracted me with a card trick while another officer handcuffed&amp;nbsp;me.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She was then taken to the police station and only allowed one phone call and to be able to check Facebook for 10 minutes, whilst her child was taken into&amp;nbsp;protection.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Man arrested for killing his mother in Essex</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/man-arrested-for-killing-his-mother-in-essex.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2009-09-07T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2009-09-07:man-arrested-for-killing-his-mother-in-essex.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;An unbalanced man from the village of Tilty, Essex wanted for murdering his own mother in the county last week was picked up by Northumberland authorities today as he was attempting to flee to&amp;nbsp;France.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. Alan Tiledamage &amp;#8212; a Geography teacher at Braintree Upper School &amp;#8212; was a primary suspect after his mother, Sharon Tiledamage, was found dead in her home in Great Dunmow on Friday. He is currently being questioned by the Morpeth&amp;nbsp;constabulary. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. Sharon Tiledamage was found beaten to death by her own loofah in the pagoda in her back garden, just next to the prize-winning gardenias. The gardineas are to have statements taken by officers from Braintree in the next few&amp;nbsp;days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;aside class="sideinfo"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Where did it all go&amp;nbsp;wrong?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
      The name &amp;#8220;Essex&amp;#8221; derives from the Old English &amp;#8220;Ēast Seaxna&amp;#8221; which translates to &amp;#8220;Easy Sex&amp;#8221; and stems from the loose nature of the Saxon women who settled there so they could be close to London for the&amp;nbsp;shops.
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
    This reputation caused an influx of questionable characters from both the Saxons and the Angles&amp;nbsp;nearby.
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
      Due to lack of the numeracy required to read train timetables, few families have moved from the area leading to a small gene pool based on these medieval troublemakers and&amp;nbsp;slags.
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
    Essex County Council was formed in 1889, but by then it was too late and all hope was&amp;nbsp;lost.
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
    The boundary with Greater London was established in 1965 so that Londoners could disassociate themselves with their Essex&amp;nbsp;neighbours.
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/aside&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Morpeth police are yet to release a statement, except this&amp;nbsp;one:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;We can confirm that Mr. Tiledamage is being held in custody over the death of his mother in Essex. We are taking this matter very seriously as it&amp;#8217;s a dying shame for anyone to spend their final days in Essex,&amp;#8221; Sergeant Pepper reads from an edible press release at a press conference held during breaks in the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;US&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;Open.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Harsher penalties were brought in for murder in the county back in November 2008 after the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;EU&lt;/span&gt; Court of Human Rights declared it an &amp;#8220;affront to human dignity for anyone&amp;#8217;s last memories of life on Earth to be of Essex.&amp;#8221; Several petitions were circulated in Chelmsford to fight the legistlation, but few could write their own name on the&amp;nbsp;sheet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;It&amp;#8217;s well crap,&amp;#8221; Councillor Jodie Marsh, Conservative chair of the Essex Country Council, tells &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; during a glamour photoshoot. Defiant over the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;EU&lt;/span&gt; ruling, she adds, &amp;#8220;I never fort[sic] someone would kill their mum, but Essex is well nice and definitely the best place to do&amp;nbsp;it.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; sent several correspondents to Essex to get reactions from family and friends, but only one returned alive. We all wish him a speedy recovery from his injuries to report his findings in due&amp;nbsp;course.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Government looks to glasses ban to curb violence</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/government-looks-to-glasses-ban-to-curb-violence.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2009-08-31T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2009-08-31:government-looks-to-glasses-ban-to-curb-violence.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Despite protests from those not so keen on the idea, the Government squeezed out an early day movement this morning that looks to ban glasses in pubs by&amp;nbsp;2011.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Home Office insists the idea is &amp;#8220;fine&amp;#8221; and that they &amp;#8220;really know what they&amp;#8217;re doing&amp;nbsp;here.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year in England and Wales, 99% of attacks that took place in or outside public houses were committed by people who could see. The Home Secretary hopes that preventing visually impaired individuals from accessing corrective glasses will reduce this percentage&amp;nbsp;signficantly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The British Beer Drinking association were indignant, claiming such a measure would impact on their drinking as well as their ability to find the pub at&amp;nbsp;all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Not&amp;nbsp;impressed&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;For the bevvy aficionado, finding the pub is a top priority,&amp;#8221; chorused the regulars at the King&amp;#8217;s Prawns, Cheddington during a &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; school trip. &amp;#8220;I have no idea how I can even begin to get blind drunk without my glasses,&amp;#8221; added the&amp;nbsp;baritone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An unelected spokestenor went on to explain that they would most certainly not welcome any attempt to take away their glasses, threatening to create a spectacle if they were to attempt to do&amp;nbsp;so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;Why should we be punished when we&amp;#8217;re not causing any trouble at all? Us myopics cause the least amount of trouble around here &amp;#8212; whoever heard of someone with glasses getting into a fight? It&amp;#8217;s those 20-20 bastards you need to watch&amp;nbsp;closely.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Economic&amp;nbsp;pressures&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Prawns landlord &amp;#8212; a wonderful countertenor &amp;#8212; says he fears increased financial pressures would result from the proposed&amp;nbsp;legislation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;Half of those twats that come in &amp;#8216;ere are blind as bats without their specs,&amp;#8221; sings he, with an irreverent, yet melodic feel. &amp;#8220;There&amp;#8217;s bound to be extra spillages and breakages if they&amp;#8217;re prone to knocking over their drinking&amp;nbsp;vessels.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;This proposal is incredibly short-sighted and I don&amp;#8217;t think the Government is looking at the big picture. Our politicians really lack vision on these matters and I don&amp;#8217;t see how they think this will work. We&amp;#8217;ve had enough of them blindly throwing legislation about like&amp;nbsp;this.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Yeah,&amp;nbsp;whatever&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ministers behind the proposal were dismissive of all negative claims and are looking forward to seeing this measure&amp;nbsp;through.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;People forget there was a time when nobody wore glasses,&amp;#8221; explains Gavin Fairweather &lt;span class="caps"&gt;MP&lt;/span&gt;. &amp;#8220;We all had to adjust from not having glasses to having them, so in time we feel people will accept this paradigm shift. Besides, they can wear contact&amp;nbsp;lenses.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pub-goers are said to be &amp;#8220;furious&amp;#8221; at the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;MP&lt;/span&gt;&amp;#8217;s remarks. &amp;#8220;Contact lenses, my eye!&amp;#8221; exclaims the tallest&amp;nbsp;one.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>East London DIY Shop Reported As Difficult To Locate</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/east-london-diy-shop-reported-as-difficult-to-locate.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2009-08-17T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2009-08-17:east-london-diy-shop-reported-as-difficult-to-locate.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
The blackened, sooty streets of Shadwell&lt;br&gt;
Glowed in ochre, dingy dark&lt;br&gt;
and twisted, inky shades were formed&lt;br&gt;
with Lucifer&amp;#8217;s heretic mark&amp;#8230;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--BREAK--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Inert and silent stillness rested,&lt;br&gt;
Draped across the dampened ground&lt;br&gt;
And flitting, dancing figures flew&lt;br&gt;
Above me, all without a sound.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
A distant light came intermittent&lt;br&gt;
Struggling through the misty rain&lt;br&gt;
A traveller, a hardy fool&lt;br&gt;
Who&amp;#8217;d ventured far from his domain.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Approaching ever louder, brighter&lt;br&gt;
Bearing down with startling force&lt;br&gt;
And suddenly they fade away.&lt;br&gt;
I turn and leave the beaten course;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Amongst the dripping filth and moistness&lt;br&gt;
Hid by arches in the gloom &lt;br&gt;
I met a man whose life was done&lt;br&gt;
To listen to his tale of doom.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="quo"&gt;&amp;#8216;&lt;/span&gt;You&amp;#8217;re late!&amp;#8217; he spat. &amp;#8216;The midnight&amp;#8217;s past.&lt;br&gt;
Now, listen to my tale of doom.&lt;br&gt;
Your Auntie Enid&amp;#8217;s on to me&lt;br&gt;
&amp;#8216;bout doing up the old spare room.&amp;#8217;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
I seek a place, quite near to here;&lt;br&gt;
a vending place, for paint and paste.&lt;br&gt;
For &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DIY&lt;/span&gt;, in other words,&lt;br&gt;
Where I may rush with hen-pecked haste.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
I summoned you, oh nephew dear&lt;br&gt;
because you know this idle place&lt;br&gt;
and may, perchance, assist me in&lt;br&gt;
my half-arsed aim to save my face.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="quo"&gt;&amp;#8216;&lt;/span&gt;Oh, do you know of such a shop?&amp;#8217;&lt;br&gt;
he cried. &amp;#8216;Why yes,&amp;#8217; I reassured.&lt;br&gt;
&amp;#8216;I came upon it last week gone&lt;br&gt;
while I was wand&amp;#8217;ring, deathly bored&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
and waiting for the match to start - &amp;#8216;twas&lt;br&gt;
Ajax versus Feyenoord.&lt;br&gt;
And lo, there was I, visilin&lt;br&gt;
the subject of your previous words,&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
A merchant&amp;#8217;s house without compare,&lt;br&gt;
A smorgasbord of &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DIY&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;br&gt;
where any home-improvement scheme&lt;br&gt;
is possible!&amp;#8217; I hoarsly cried.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="quo"&gt;&amp;#8216;&lt;/span&gt;Oh, joy!&amp;#8217; he yelled. &amp;#8216;It must reveal&lt;br&gt;
Its manifold delights to me!&amp;#8217;&lt;br&gt;
I briefly thought to tease him but&lt;br&gt;
he touched me with his abject plea.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="quo"&gt;&amp;#8216;&lt;/span&gt;The place you seek is very near.&lt;br&gt;
You take a right, then left, and then&lt;br&gt;
you pass the demon traffic lights&lt;br&gt;
which are not fit for God nor men&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
and then proceed to yonder street.&lt;br&gt;
And there, Valhalla you will mark.&lt;br&gt;
&amp;#8216;You king of men!&amp;#8217; he thanked me, and&lt;br&gt;
we parted in the dingy dark.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>OED to remove word “gullible”</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/oed-to-remove-word-gullible.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2009-06-29T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2009-06-29:oed-to-remove-word-gullible.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#8217;s been the time-honoured joke of the schoolyards, workplaces and even safari parks: &amp;#8220;gullible is not in the dictionary.&amp;#8221; The irony stems from the fact that only the gullible would believe such a claim, but the Oxford English Dictionary team are seeking to bring an end to this long-running mirth&amp;nbsp;device.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As part of their ongoing fun-prevention campaign,
the makers of the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;OED&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#8212; a long-standing lexicographic
institution &amp;#8212; have voted 14 to 3 to remove the
word gullible from the pages of the great word&amp;nbsp;tome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;The joke has gone on long enough,&amp;#8221; explains Colin
Waterman, &lt;span class="caps"&gt;OED&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="caps"&gt;CEO&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;span class="caps"&gt;OBE&lt;/span&gt; and brother to star of
1970s police drama &lt;em&gt;The Sweeney&lt;/em&gt;,
John Thaw. &amp;#8220;It amused a few of us when the joke
first started, but we&amp;#8217;ve decided it has to come to an
end. We&amp;#8217;ve removed the word altogether so if
anyone does fall for it again, they will be ones
in the right, thus negating the&amp;nbsp;whimsy.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whilst futurists are speculating a reduction in
lexicographic tomfoolery in 2010, several groups
are claiming the move by the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;OED&lt;/span&gt; will not solve
the&amp;nbsp;problem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;It&amp;#8217;s obvius, innit?&amp;#8221; claims the Minister for Education,
&amp;#8220;peeple will jst make jokes bout uther werds.&amp;#8221; Several
comedy pressure groups have also suggested that
the joke may invert itself with proponents
simply telling their victims the word &amp;#8220;gullible&amp;#8221; has been
returned to the&amp;nbsp;dictionary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The origins of the original joke are speculative at worst
and at best, pretty well-known. According to banter
historians, the joke dates as far back as 1584 when Sir
Walter Raleigh was known to use it as an ice-breaker
on encountering people native to the Americas. On first contact,
while trying to establish communication, he would joke
that our language had no word for gullible. Once they
understood the joke, it was said to have helped ease colonial&amp;nbsp;tensions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even the word itself is said to be coined by the explorer. As
a small boy, he would perform magic tricks to seagulls in Cornwall
and found that out of all sea birds, they were the easiest
to fool. Thus, he would talk about &amp;#8220;gulling&amp;#8221; people who were
easy to trick and referred to them as&amp;nbsp;&amp;#8220;gullable&amp;#8221;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 1814, the first Edition of The Times was printed, but with
poor timing as news had yet to be invented. The writers for the
paper had to resort to filling pages with their shopping lists,
anecdotes from their holidays and the rest was padded
out with pages and pages of the letter &amp;#8220;A&amp;#8221; over
and over. This caused a great shortage in the
letter A for other publications, thus many words ending in &amp;#8220;able&amp;#8221;
were changed to &amp;#8220;ible&amp;#8221; &amp;#8212; along with &amp;#8220;gullible&amp;#8221; &amp;#8212; giving
the modern spelling as we know it&amp;nbsp;today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new edition of the Oxford English Dictionary
will be out in time for Christmas and is said
to be the first edition with the word removed altogether.
Language scholars are yet to comment on whether this
will affect day to day conversation as they are all on&amp;nbsp;holiday.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Fire Chief Warns Over Miniature Fire Truck Danger</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/fire-chief-warns-over-miniature-fire-truck-danger.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2009-04-10T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2009-04-10:fire-chief-warns-over-miniature-fire-truck-danger.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;
The head of the fire service in England and Kent has expressed his reservations over the deployment of 4-foot fire engines in the fight against&amp;nbsp;conflagrations.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Sir Malcolm Burnley told &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; that the Labour government&amp;#8217;s plans to 
deploy miniature fire trucks filled with little weak shrunken men to man 
them could seriously affect the fire service&amp;#8217;s effectiveness in doing 
whatever it is they&amp;nbsp;do.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="quo"&gt;&amp;#8216;&lt;/span&gt;The Home Secretary has clearly not thought this one through&amp;#8217;, said 
Sir Malcolm, on the eve of his wife&amp;#8217;s birthday yesterday. &amp;#8216;Anyone who&amp;#8217;s 
ever seen Thunderbirds  will know that most fires will easily reach the 
height of an average interstellar spacecraft, and in this day and age, 
we need bigger fire trucks, not smaller&amp;nbsp;ones.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The initiative is understood to have been introduced in response to 
sweeping budget cuts flying across Whitehall. &amp;#8216;Simple mathematics 
dictates that when the dimensions of a solid are reduced by a factor of 
2, its volume will decrease by a factor of 8&amp;#8217;, said a Home Office 
spokescomedian. &amp;#8216;Therefore, by merely halving the length of a fire 
truck, the government can reduce its expenses by nearly 88 per&amp;nbsp;cent.&amp;#8217;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="quo"&gt;&amp;#8216;&lt;/span&gt;Of course, this will mean that they will only be able to carry one 
eighth of the water that they could previously carry, and all of the 
personnel would have to speak in high-pitched voices and brandish their 
fists regularly at no-one in particular, but we do not feel that the 
service will be compromised at all.&amp;#8217; When asked to justify this clear 
lie, he declined&amp;nbsp;loudly.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; understands that, if successful, the downsizing scheme could be 
rolled out to the other emergency services, and possibly then to theatre 
producers such as Andrew Lloyd Webber and Cameron Mackintosh. There is 
even understood to be rumours about the Home Office of the entire 
country being shrunk in order to fit into the middle of France, allowing 
the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UK&lt;/span&gt; to save billions on the renting of expensive prime real estate in 
the eastern Atlantic&amp;nbsp;Ocean.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; has since discovered that these rumours in fact came from 
&amp;#8216;Chemotherapy Bob&amp;#8217; of Borough High&amp;nbsp;Street.
&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>World’s Youngest Baby Born</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/worlds-youngest-baby-born.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2009-04-03T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2009-04-03:worlds-youngest-baby-born.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;A dilapidated hospital earmarked for destruction was celebrating today after hosting the birth of the world&amp;#8217;s youngest ever&amp;nbsp;baby.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guy&amp;#8217;s Hospital in London was, until today, scheduled to be blown up in the government&amp;#8217;s anti-hospital white paper 
published last week. Standards have been falling consistently over the last several decades, as a result of shabby 
work practices and some annoying syringes. But the staff and patients&amp;#8217; malais turned to jubilation this morning as a 
baby was born that could spell the end of the hospital&amp;#8217;s&amp;nbsp;woes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;My husband and I had lots of sex about nine months ago&amp;#8221;, said Tracy Smithford from her bed, &amp;#8220;but it was still quite 
a shock when I found out I was pregnant. So I travelled here to Guy&amp;#8217;s in the Toyota. Before I came here, I just 
assumed that I&amp;#8217;d be having a normal, boring baby, and I never even imagined that I&amp;#8217;d give birth to such a little&amp;nbsp;miracle.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doctors monitoring the baby&amp;#8217;s progress estimated that a few minutes after birth, the child was only a couple of 
minutes old, one of the youngest babies ever to have been born. Subsequent research showed that, prior to this, the 
baby was likely to have been less than one minute old for a brief period, thus claiming the title of youngest baby 
ever recorded. Speculation that the baby could have been exactly 0 minutes old for an infinitesimal period was rife 
among mathematicians, and confirmation is expected within a few&amp;nbsp;days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The accolade has delighted management at Guy&amp;#8217;s Hospital, who are hoping that the notoriously bandwagon-jumping Labour 
government will reverse their closure decision, pump millions of pounds into new equipment and staff and paint 
the building in nice gold paint. An order is expected to be placed for a large banner device to be dangled from the 
exterior frontage of the building in commemoration of the Gulf&amp;nbsp;War. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;We love that this couple chose to have their baby here&amp;#8221;, said senior nurse Colin Wang Tang. &amp;#8220;We&amp;#8217;ve all been 
wondering what this child will achieve in its life, after this great 
start it&amp;#8217;s had,&amp;#8221; said his colleague, head porter 
Vicenzo Chianti. &amp;#8220;My view is that he&amp;#8217;ll attend one of the great public schools, graduate from Oxford Brookes, and run 
a successful shipping law firm, before losing his fortune on the horses and late-night pay-per-view and ending his 
life in a ditch in Guildford on&amp;nbsp;fire.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Following the record-breaking birth and the money and publicity that it brought, parents everywhere are now likely 
to be humping maniacally in the hope of claiming the title for their little child. At this stage, however, experts 
suggest that the likelihood of a baby being younger than one minute old, even for a few seconds, is just a pipe dream 
for&amp;nbsp;most.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Punctuation Error Causes Train Derailment</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/punctuation-error-causes-train-derailment.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2009-03-20T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>ChrisH</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2009-03-20:punctuation-error-causes-train-derailment.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;17 people were injured, some lightly, when a commuter train derailed at Tring this morning, causing widespread delays across the entire rail 
network and to some shipping&amp;nbsp;lanes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;London Midland train company couldn&amp;#8217;t believe it today when the 06.48 service from Northampton left the rails just north of Tring station with 948 
people compressed on board. The cause of the accident is speculated to have been a punctuation error in the recent London Midlands timetable. Arnie, 
of London Midland, said &amp;#8216;The train was approaching Tring station when it left the track at approximately 08.23. We immediately shut down the 
surrounding area and summoned emergency personnel to the site to coordinate a press release. We are unable to comment further at this&amp;nbsp;time.&amp;#8217;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whilst the damage to infrastructure was significant, injuries seemed to be slight. A passing hospital reported a small number of walking 
wounded attending A&amp;E, with afflictions ranging from damaged wallets to an amalgamated orgasm. One passenger was admitted with advanced head cancer, 
although this is thought to be unrelated to the accident. No-one is believed to have been killed in the crash, but a number of people were seen 
wandering the track, confused and dazed and unsure what to do. Network Rail denied reports that engineers were at work on the line that&amp;nbsp;morning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;London Midland have, apparently, begun an inquiry into the incident. Alexander Domestic-Appliances, editor of the suspected timetable, told &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt;, 
&amp;#8216;It appears that a full stop was accidentally inserted into the Northampton to Euston section of the timetable, immediately after the word &amp;#8216;Tring&amp;#8217;. 
This ad hoc punctuation was detected by our train&amp;#8217;s Automatic Semantics System, &lt;span class="caps"&gt;ASS&lt;/span&gt;, and caused the train to bounce off of the rails at this point. 
Whilst we regret the loss of dignity suffered by our passengers, this does show that the system is operating as designed.&amp;#8217; Asked whether the 
offending timetables will be withdrawn and corrected, Mr Domestic-Appliances lit a cigarette and leaned against a nearby fridge&amp;nbsp;casually.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The incident has raised concerns over London Midland trains&amp;#8217; &lt;span class="caps"&gt;ASS&lt;/span&gt;. The crash recalls an incident on a British Rail train in 1985, which collided 
with an emu near Chipping Sodbury after a performance of &amp;#8216;Die Fledermaus&amp;#8217; at a local theatre interfered with the trackwork. In both of these cases, 
the train&amp;#8217;s technology responded to something stupidly unlikely to affect passenger safety. As a result, a recent resurgence in the popularity of light 
opera and grammar in the Home Counties has caused lesser publications to speculate on the likelihood of a much more serious accident in the near 
future. Network Rail has been unable to comment until it has completed its internal investigation of the tracks and signalling in the area, and has 
initiated engineering work to ensure that the Straussian conductivity of the rails is within the limits specified by some government&amp;nbsp;guy.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Runcorn Honoured in Video Game Legacy</title><link href="http://news.wafti.org.uk/runcorn-honoured-in-video-game-legacy.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2009-03-02T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>Ross</name></author><id>tag:news.wafti.org.uk,2009-03-02:runcorn-honoured-in-video-game-legacy.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Locals to the Cheshire town of Runcorn today received news of an accolade of a very high order as they were chosen as the namesake of a new character in the Pokemon video game series, produced by&amp;nbsp;Nintendo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nintendo will be releasing &lt;em&gt;Pokemon: The Silver Jubilee Edition&lt;/em&gt;
in Autumn this year which will be 26th in the
series of video games in which players battle with
small, fictional creatures called &lt;em&gt;Pokemon&lt;/em&gt;,
which is short for &amp;#8220;Pokey&amp;nbsp;Monsters&amp;#8221;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was said that the Japanese games giant had
shortlisted several &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UK&lt;/span&gt; settlements to be
the inspiration for the new character
introduced in the latest game in the&amp;nbsp;franchise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amongst the towns that didn&amp;#8217;t make the final
choice were Gateshead, Slough and Chipping Sodbury.
It is understood that the town of Skegness was
also approached, but declined to be shortlisted
on moral&amp;nbsp;grounds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;Naturally, we&amp;#8217;re delighted,&amp;#8221; gleeful Runcorn
councillor Peter Chu tells &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WAFTI&lt;/span&gt; in his first
interview since parole. &amp;#8220;This is going to be
a tremendous boon for all the people of&amp;nbsp;Runcorn.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Early estimates forecast an approximate
growth in tourism of 1.41% when the new
video game appears in the shops on 31st
October. Walking down the High Street,
it can be seen that local businesses are already
celebrating the&amp;nbsp;honour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;This is the best thing to happen to
the town since the building of the
Bridgewater canal,&amp;#8221;
gushes Agnes Cream, a local travel agent
who is already negotiating discounted
B&amp;amp;B rates in the area for any Japanese&amp;nbsp;visitors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A special parade will be held through the town
this Sunday, but those taking part are
struggling with the fact the nearest Pokemon
costume shop is in&amp;nbsp;Manchester.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dquo"&gt;&amp;#8220;&lt;/span&gt;The parade will most definitely go ahead,&amp;#8221;
confirms Gareth Silo, head of the town council,
adorning full Pikachu&amp;nbsp;dress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A spokesperson from Nintendo adds they
chose Runcorn after a painfully rigorous
decision process and they look forward
to having the town&amp;#8217;s namesake spearhead
the latest game as its star&amp;nbsp;character.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He tells us that &amp;#8220;Runcorn is the perfect
pokey town for our&amp;nbsp;pokemon.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry></feed>